<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1543406820864">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">28.11.2018 12:07:00 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.162jnn52yrui</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Have you got any qualifications? &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.purplecreativedesign.co.uk/sportmedlv-5884.pdf#mane&quot;&gt;ars-med.lv darba laiks&lt;/a&gt;  The number of ads sold in the second quarter fell 2 percent while the price-per-ad dropped about 12 percent, highlighting a recurring problem despite other signs of progress under Mayer&apos;s leadership.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://public-admin.co.uk/banish-tonsil-stones-free-pdf-3c8d.pdf#seam&quot;&gt;diane puttman banish tonsil stones pdf&lt;/a&gt;  &amp;ldquo;Newspapers should not apologise to politicians for being robust. We need a free press that is robust, raucous and, by definition, will sometimes offend,&amp;rdquo; Mr Gove, whose wife writes a weekly column for the Mail, said.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://worldnewsnetwork.co.in/medicationrehabcom-08d2.pdf&quot;&gt;medicationrehab.com&lt;/a&gt;  Even though banning fun is a total party pooper move that makes Tomlin sound like Roger Goodell&amp;#8217;s long-lost coaching cousin, this is the right call to make. The Steelers can&amp;#8217;t afford a Gramatica-like injury celebration to one of the few offensive weapons on the team.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://starbizzcon.com/costco-pharmacy-mission-viejo-ca-45db.pdf&quot;&gt;shoppers drug mart pharmacist online learning&lt;/a&gt;  The better the Left behaves, the greater a risk it poses to Merkel by becoming more attractive to the SPD, which will not enjoy watching Gysi preach from the opposition while the SPD compromises its own campaign pledges.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.greenlam.com/index.php/effexor-or-pristiq-for-anxiety-7741.pdf#heaven&quot;&gt;effexor or pristiq for anxiety&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;Richemont has a long-standing policy of not commenting onmarket rumours. Exceptionally in this case, Richemont wishes tomake it clear that The Net-A-Porter Group is not for sale,&quot; thecompany said in a statement.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
