<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542608869977">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 06:27:49 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.crsp1glznur</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I&apos;ve just graduated &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.layeredonline.com/best-drugstore-bronzer-and-blush-dd54.pdf#crying&quot;&gt;online pharmacy for sale uk&lt;/a&gt;  Funny, kind of, but mostly infuriating. In this day when nearly every charity, fund drive, corporate outreach, government program, volunteer effort, community outreach, etc. is directed to minority, predominantly black, recipients, I get angry when I see people talking about &amp;#8220;civil rights&amp;#8221;. These programs are never overtly named or earmarked for any one demographic, but the code words of &amp;#8220;under-privelged&amp;#8221;, &amp;#8220;urban youth&amp;#8221;, &amp;#8220;low-income&amp;#8221;, &amp;#8220;inner-city&amp;#8221;, &amp;#8220;disadvantaged&amp;#8221;, etc. all mean &amp;#8220;black&amp;#8221;. I simply do not know how much more can be given to &amp;#8220;black America&amp;#8221; without actually going to work and turning over our paychecks, homes, cars, and possessions to race-baiting, poverty pimps like this looking to make a name for themselves fighting a perceived injustice that is actually the direct opposite of what they want their willing followers to believe. How about some true equality for a change, you know, work and personal responsibility, keeping your &amp;#8220;own communities&amp;#8221; decent and livable, promoting education and respect, teaching right and wrong (yes this is a valid concept). Civil rights is an obsolete term, lets realize that and stop trying to play the blame game ad infinitum.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.infocalcbba.edu.bo/microzide-pharmacy2us-9e88.pdf&quot;&gt;microzide pharmacy2us&lt;/a&gt;  When the NFL learned of that, it launched an investigation, the report said, into both Miller and the collection company, Drug Free Sport. When it was over, the star-struck collector had lost his job and Miller’s suspension — after a lengthy negotiation, apparently — had been increased from the standard four to six games.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://sjofartsbygningen.no/medsinorg-7ef0.pdf#wound&quot;&gt;med.place&lt;/a&gt;  &amp;ldquo;One would think that technology is moving forward fast but it has taken 35 years to get from the fourth generation fighter jet to the fifth generation. I believe the next generation fighter will evolve no earlier than in 15 years,&amp;rdquo; Bogdan said in a statement earlier this month.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sarah-hyland.net/kamagra-oral-jelly-serios-79a8.pdf&quot;&gt;kamagra uputstvo za upotrebu&lt;/a&gt;  Some supporters are concerned that Women of the Wall are giving up too much by agreeing in principle to move to a third section of the Wall, instead of continuing their quest to change the current set-up. Hoffman reveals one of the group&amp;rsquo;s 10 board members is thinking of leaving, while other founding members have accused her of selling out.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://contactconsultoria.com/index.php/reliable-generic-suppliercom-a511.pdf#luxurious&quot;&gt;reliable-generic-supplier.com&lt;/a&gt;  The confirmations in the Democrat-controlled chamber mark the end of a contentious political battle over NLRB nominations. Republican lawmakers, who have accused the agency of activist decision-making, had refused to reconfirm two current board members whose appointments are being challenged in a case before the U.S. Supreme Court.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
