<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1543406299017">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">28.11.2018 11:58:19 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.ropzl8sd1t8e</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Free medical insurance &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.aicpuglia.it/compare-viagra-prices-online-2397.pdf&quot;&gt;viagra reviews young men&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;With the amount of support the president and the White House have from Silicon Valley, you would think they&apos;d be able to nip these problems in the bud. They could call up any of these people and ask for their assistance. Why not put together a blue ribbon panel with all the guys from Google and Twitter? This should have been done beforehand.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://pixelbedlam.co.uk/olagligt-med-kamagra-65ef.pdf#roller&quot;&gt;kamagra express delivery&lt;/a&gt;  Jefferies analyst Sandy Morris expressed doubts about a GKNacquisition of Spirit. &quot;My personal view is that perhaps onedivision of Spirit may be for sale, and that would be the wingsystems division. I think that that&apos;s much more likely,&quot; Morrisadded.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bombeirodf.com.br/cost-deer-antler-spray-50f8.pdf&quot;&gt;deer antler spray trial&lt;/a&gt;  While the government closure has already had repercussions from frustrated tourists turned away from national parks to cancelled stops on Obama’s Asia trip, the deadline for raising the nation’s debt limit poses a much graver risk.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ssvoverath.de/enlarged-prostate-drugs-list-c3db.pdf&quot;&gt;prostate drinking water&lt;/a&gt;  LOS ANGELES, Sept 29 - Following are the top 10 movies atNorth American box offices for the three days starting Sept. 27,led by &quot;Cloudy With a Chance of Meatballs 2&quot; according to studioestimates compiled by Reuters.1 (*) Cloudy With a Chance of Meatballs 2 $ 35.0 million2 (1) Prisoners...........................$ 11.3 million3 (*) Rush................................$ 10.3 million4 (*) Baggage Claim.......................$ 9.3 million5 (*) Don Jon.............................$ 9.0 million6 (2) Insidious: Chapter 2................$ 6.7 million7 (3) The Family..........................$ 3.7 million8 (4) Instructions Not Included...........$ 3.4 million9 (6) We&apos;re the Millers...................$ 2.9 million10 (7) Lee Daniels&apos; The Butler.............$ 2.4 million(*) = new releaseCUMULATIVE TOTALS:We&apos;re The Millers..............................$ 142.4 millionLee Daniels&apos; The Butler........................$ 110.3 millionInsidious: Chapter 2...........................$ 69.5 millionPrisoners......................................$ 39.0 millionInstructions Not Included .....................$ 38.6 millionCloudy With a Chance of Meatballs 2............$ 35.0 millionThe Family.....................................$ 31.7 millionRush...........................................$ 10.6 millionBaggage Claim..................................$ 9.3 millionDon Jon........................................$ 9.0 million &quot;Cloudy with a Chance of Meatballs 2&quot; was released by SonyCorp&apos;s movie studio. &quot;Rush&quot; was released by Universal Pictures, a unit of ComcastCorp.&quot;Prisoners&quot; and &quot;We&apos;re the Millers&quot; were distributed by WarnerBros., a unit of Time Warner Inc. Privately heldFilmDistrict released &quot;Insidious: Chapter 2.&quot; &quot;Don Jon&quot; and &quot;TheFamily&quot; were distributed by privately held Relativity Media. &quot;Baggage Claim&quot; was released by Fox Searchlight, a unit of 21stCentury Fox.&quot;The Butler&quot; is distributed by the privately held Weinstein Co. &quot;Instructions Not Included&quot; is distributed by Pantelion, a jointventure of Hollywood studio Lionsgate Entertainment andMexican media giant Televisa.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bombeirodf.com.br/pharmacie-des-tourettes-37-50f8.pdf&quot;&gt;horaires pharmacie des tourettes sollies toucas&lt;/a&gt;  As season three kicks off next Sunday, it doesn&apos;t help that many TV eyes will be fixed that day on the final episode of &quot;Breaking Bad,&quot; the gritty AMC show that snatched the best drama Emmy and the attention from &quot;Homeland.&quot;
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
