<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542348465014">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">16.11.2018 06:07:45 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.nxscwixz5m0f</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Wonderfull great site &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.greenlamindustries.com/blog/stmap_0bae0.html?penisole.metoprolol.cialis&quot;&gt;rogaine generic versions&lt;/a&gt;  Thank you Carl. We’re very pleased with our Q3 results meeting or exceeding all of our key goals for the quarter. We’re executing the plan we have shared with you and the year continues to play out as we expected. Q3 total reported revenue growth of 14% year-over-year was above the midpoint of our guidance range. License revenues of $564 million were up 15% year-over-year and exceeded the upper end of our guidance. Excluding pivotal and all divestitures total revenues grew 19% year-over-year in Q3 accelerating from 15% in Q2 and 13% in Q1, license revenue growth accelerated to 17% year-over-year up from 5% in Q2 and 1% in Q1. Overall services revenue grew 13% year-over-year excluding pivotal and all divestitures services revenue grew 20% year-over-year. Moving to operating expenses and profitability. Unless otherwise noted, all references to our expenses and operating results are on a non-GAAP basis and are reconciled to our gap results in the press release tables and posted on our investor relations website.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
