<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542537869486">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 10:44:29 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1t0yvr42q1fmj</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I hate shopping &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.artistparama.com/wwwzoloftcom-5168.pdf#whirl&quot;&gt;www.zoloft.com/&lt;/a&gt;  The new software addresses the problem of incompatibilityamong video formats on various devices, allowing customers toupload a video which can then be viewed and shared on a PC, atablet, an iPhone, an Android device or a TV set.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tarokasongbad.com/tannerpharmacom-e3c4.pdf&quot;&gt;medicalcitydoc.com&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;I am lucky to have retired on my terms. My opportunities were getting less but I could have ridden for another year. But if people are forced to retire through lack of opportunities, or age, or injury, then they might struggle.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://oporajeyo.com/delaymaxx-uk-bf45.pdf&quot;&gt;delaymaxx uk&lt;/a&gt;  Now, meanwhile, the supreme leader has issued a fatwa against the development of nuclear weapons, and President Rouhani has just recently reiterated that the Islamic Republic will never develop a nuclear weapon. So these statements made by our respective governments should offer the basis for a meaningful agreement. We should be able to achieve a resolution that respects the rights of the Iranian people while giving the world confidence that the Iranian program is peaceful.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lovemycase.com/largagenix-f2c2.pdf#secretly&quot;&gt;largagenix&lt;/a&gt;  The move follows weeks of speculation that the Frenchmedia-to-telecoms conglomerate was looking for ways to pull someof the $4.3 billion in cash sitting on the balance sheet of theworld&apos;s largest video games publisher as part of a widerrestructuring aimed at cutting debt and refocusing its business.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lucky-websolutions.com/woodrivermedicineshoppecom-0a7b.pdf#refuse&quot;&gt;isomeds.de&lt;/a&gt;  Homebuilders felt even more optimistic for the coming months with the gauge of expectations for single-family home sales for the next six months accelerating to 67 from a revised 60, while the component on prospective buyer traffic increased 5 points to 45. Both sub-indexes strengthened to levels not seen since late 2005.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
