<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542359125152">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">16.11.2018 09:05:25 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1ov4u4nnz5te4</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Where are you from? &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.proguaru.com.br/stmap_76840.html?zithromax.lexapro.viagra&quot;&gt;dapsone webmd&lt;/a&gt;  Europe&apos;s broad FTSEurofirst 300 share index was up0.1 percent by 0745 GMT and the euro edged off athree-month low as investors shrugged off falls in French andDutch manufacturing data and a rating downgrade of Italy.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.elegantandwild.co.uk/stmap_75b30.html?cipro.pilex.levitra.zerit&quot;&gt;rapaflo silodosin capsules side effects&lt;/a&gt;  As growth slows in the world&apos;s largest auto market from break-neck speeds over the past decade, GAC aims to have exports of its Trumpchi brand account for a fifth of total sales in five years. It currently sells just a few hundred cars overseas. Last year, GAC earned a profit of 1.1 billion yuan on sales of around 13 billion yuan ($2.12 billion).
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://virtual-operations.com/stmap_92e20.html?viagra.omnicef.cloxacillin&quot;&gt;www.heb.com/pharmacy/&lt;/a&gt;  The first concrete sign of agreement came when the Senate, on a vote of 71-29, with 17 Republicans joining all 52 Democrats and two independents, cleared the way for an up-or-down vote on Obama&apos;s choice of Richard Cordray to serve as director of the Bureau of Consumer Financial Protection.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://accentresurfacing.com/stmap_41100.html?levitra.ivermectin.hoodia&quot;&gt;gold leaf nutritionals geneseeker&lt;/a&gt;  The RSPB is concerned that if children do not understand wildlife, they will be less inclined to protect nature when they reach adulthood. This makes sense. And there is reason to be concerned: earlier this year, a report by 25 wildlife organisations, including the RSPB, found that 60 per cent of the species studied have declined in the last few decades. Yet is it any wonder that children do not understand wildlife when it is presented in such an unrealistic way and when every death and non-birth is elevated to a national tragedy?
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.layeredonline.com/stmap_dd540.html?viagra.singulair.norvir.casodex&quot;&gt;miracle plus skin tag remover reviews&lt;/a&gt;  The ability to assume a role, rather than simply witness actions, is part of the medium&amp;#8217;s great (if woefully unexplored) potential, enabling us to inhabit the lives of people who don&amp;#8217;t necessarily share our beliefs, values, or systems of behavior. In the award-winning 2008 game Braid, for example, the player becomes a suit-wearing stalker chasing down an ex-lover. In the 2013 independent game Papers, Please, you play as a zealous immigration inspector at a border checkpoint for a fictitious Eastern-bloc country, refusing entry to refugees. In the recent game Cart Life, you play as one of three downtrodden protagonists working a low-paying job in America. An enormously effective game that reflects the struggle of many people who live on the poverty line, it&amp;#8217;s essentially a fictionalized documentary that illuminates the subject in a way that is possible only in a video game, compelling the player to experience the forces and choices that someone earning minimum wage struggles with. In this way, game designers, like novelists or filmmakers, can create truly transgressive works. A skillfully designed game might use this participatory perspective for artistic purpose&amp;#8212;offering profound, affecting statements about the human condition. As in a film, this means that there&amp;#8217;s the potential for a kind of onscreen violence that is not merely permissible but valuable. Unfortunately, it&amp;#8217;s still a rarity: much scripted violence in games is psychopathically repetitive and presented without broader commentary or consequence. But the opportunity for a courageous designer is there.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
