<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542536078448">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 10:14:38 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.12yj36awdd0qj</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Could you please repeat that? &lt;a href=&quot;https://accentresurfacing.com/mikah-pharma-llc-4110.pdf&quot;&gt;mikah pharma&lt;/a&gt;  At the White House, White House press secretary Jay Carney sidestepped questions on whether President Obama would attempt to restart his push for tighter gun laws in the aftermath of Monday&apos;s mass shootings
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://theglobalelite.org/children39s-motrin-equivalent-69bc.pdf&quot;&gt;ibuprofen dosage child mg&lt;/a&gt;  A super stylish twist on a traditional structured coat and one of AW13&amp;#39;s key trends, an oversized cape is a must-have for the new season, with the likes of Valentino, Mulberry and Raoul all reinventing the traditional topper. What&amp;#39;s more, camel is the colour to invest in this season, as it was almost ubiquitous on the winter catwalks, and is a super chic alternative to black.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://globalelite.tv/permethrin-cream-to-treat-head-lice-b1c8.pdf#lock&quot;&gt;where do you buy permethrin&lt;/a&gt;  Transmission studies conducted by Kawaoka&apos;s group in ferrets—animals that, like humans, infect one another through coughing and sneezing and that are a standard model for studies of influenza in mammals—showed that one of the H7N9 strains isolated from humans can transmit via respiratory droplets, though not as efficiently as human influenza viruses. The limited aerosol transmission observed in ferrets adds to concerns about the potential threat as avian flu viruses typically lack that ability, Kawaoka notes.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lovemycase.com/how-often-can-you-apply-permethrin-for-scabies-f2c2.pdf#writing&quot;&gt;permethrin biomo lsung 0 5&lt;/a&gt;  “But you always make mistakes on these things. When the machine tries to do the table with numbers, or the dog comes up and says, ‘Oh, you didn’t do this thing right,’ Microsoft Bob-style. A long time ago we tried a little personality that was definitely premature. I think it will re-emerge, but perhaps with a bit more sophistication. We were just ahead of our time, like most of our mistakes.”
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.infocalcbba.edu.bo/pill-identifier-metoprolol-50-mg-9e88.pdf&quot;&gt;metoprolol er succinate 25mg side effects&lt;/a&gt;  The 2013 laureates join a roster of past winners who include U.S. playwright Arthur Miller, British artist David Hockney, Canadian architect Frank Gehry and a host of other household names in the arts over the 25 years they have been awarded.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
