<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1543404863698">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">28.11.2018 11:34:23 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.ptndp50fhcac</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>perfect design thanks &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sensors.co.uk/bactroban-pomada-precio-sin-receta-9874.pdf#naughty&quot;&gt;prezzo bactroban pomata&lt;/a&gt;  Zero hours contracts could be viewed as a means to create more working opportunities, as a stepping stone from unemployment by offering an entry point into the work place. The other advantage of a zero hours contract is that it helps the employer get through tough economic times as it enables an efficient use of workers, as the flexibility offered by these contracts keeps costs down and boosts productivity.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.greenlam.com/index.php/vandykpharmacoza-7741.pdf#knelt&quot;&gt;vandykpharma.co.za&lt;/a&gt;  Colombia&amp;rsquo;s success relative to Peru means that the debate over forced eradication is far from clear cut. Bogota&amp;rsquo;s strategy is also based on forced eradication, but combines vastly greater resources dedicated to fighting the drug trade.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.aicpuglia.it/womenshealthsebritney-2397.pdf&quot;&gt;womenshealth.se&lt;/a&gt;  It was the first time Israel&apos;s Iron Dome missile defense system successfully intercepted a rocket attack on the resort of Eilat, the military said. The incident came after days of heightened tension along the Egypt-Israel border.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://pixelbedlam.co.uk/adapalene-differin-65ef.pdf#advance&quot;&gt;differin acne worse&lt;/a&gt;  He spotted Martin, became suspicious, called police, was told he didn&apos;t need to follow him, was only out of his car to give the authorities an address, was jumped and then pummeled by Martin and as he was being punched and having his head knocked into the ground, Martin went for Zimmerman&apos;s firearm and Zimmerman shot him once in the chest.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bombeirodf.com.br/pharma-clinical-sag-50f8.pdf&quot;&gt;pharma clinical development&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;I&apos;ve never done any exercise, except hard farmwork,&quot; said 86 year-old Wang Kailu, who lives in a simple concrete shack with his wife Wu Aihe. The couple said they married the day after Japan&apos;s World War Two surrender, 68 years ago.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
