<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542583340349">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 23:22:20 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.v6q10y6t7f96</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I can&apos;t get a dialling tone &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mcmpovos.com/alternate-tylenol-and-ibuprofen-for-child-62bd.pdf#spasmodic&quot;&gt;how often alternating tylenol and ibuprofen in toddlers&lt;/a&gt;  Ackman has had an impact. Former P&amp;G CEO Bob McDonald abruptly retired May 23, telling employees in a letter that criticism of his leadership had become &quot;a distraction that is not in our best interests.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.haroldwhitefuneraldirectors.co.uk/regional-medical-center-of-san-jose-jobs-bd82.pdf&quot;&gt;regional medical center of san jose careers&lt;/a&gt;  &amp;#8220;Extra&amp;#8221; can confirm that John Legend and Chrissy Teigen are married.  The couple said &amp;#8220;I do&amp;#8221; surrounded by family and friends at a wedding ceremony in Italy&apos;s Lake Como on Saturday.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://lemcasesorias.com/index.php/farabipharmair-83f5.pdf#carriage&quot;&gt;medart.org.hk&lt;/a&gt;  Aena, which owns 46 airports in Spain, will pay 394.4million pounds ($522.3 million) for the facility alongside theinfrastructure fund of Axa Private Equity, Aena said in astatement today. Aena will own a 51 percent stake in theairport, with Axa controlling the remainder. Aena previouslycontrolled 10 percent of the site in partnership with Barcelona-based Abertis.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://paradiseinmexico.com.mx/are-generic-drugs-equivalent-to-brand-name-drugs-c13c.pdf#skin&quot;&gt;all pharma share price&lt;/a&gt;  Thirty-two people died in the disaster but the bodies of two of the victims have still not been recovered &amp;mdash; Russel Rebello, an Indian waiter, and Maria Grazia Trecarichi, a passenger from Sicily.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sarah-hyland.net/purchase-oxybutynin-online-79a8.pdf&quot;&gt;ditropan purchase&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;Given that there were other copies and we could work out of America, which has better laws to protect journalists, I saw no reason not to destroy this material ourselves rather than hand it back to the government,&quot; he told the BBC in August.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
