<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542529046791">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 08:17:26 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.wh0o1021ynkp</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>It&apos;s funny goodluck &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.greenlamindustries.com/blog/doterra-copaiba-uses-0bae.pdf#captain&quot;&gt;doterra copaiba uses&lt;/a&gt;  Powerball tickets are sold in 43 states, the District ofColumbia and the U.S. Virgin Islands. Five states - Kansas,Maryland, Delaware, North Dakota and Ohio - allow the winners toremain anonymous, according to the Multi-State LotteryAssociation. (Additional reporting by Tom Brown in Miami and David Bailey inMinneapolis; Editing by Barbara Goldberg and Jeffrey Benkoe)
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.chris-cancercommunity.com/healthexpressse-flashback-b01a.pdf#gaily&quot;&gt;healthexpress.se flashback&lt;/a&gt;  Shares in Lloyds Banking Group were among the worstperformers in London after the UK said it would sell part of itsstake in the lender, which it had to bail out with taxpayers&apos;money during the financial crisis. Lloyds fell 2.2 percent to75.65 pence, aligning with the government&apos;s placing price of 75pence per share for the sale of a 6 percent stake in the bank.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.elegantandwild.co.uk/oc-pharmacy-75b3.pdf&quot;&gt;oc pharmacy sjc&lt;/a&gt;  The ruling is a victory for companies like Coca-Cola, PepsiCo and Dr Pepper Snapple, which argued that the law would do little to address obesity while imposing unnecessary costs. The restaurant industry and several business groups also had filed papers in support of the lawsuit.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dollingstownfc.com/protein-water-costco-6865.pdf#fetch&quot;&gt;ready nutrition protein water ingredients&lt;/a&gt;  The evidence here is clear. There’s a difference between sugary soda and other food and drink. Namely, large quantities of the stuff can be consumed without sating the appetite. That drives thousands to become overweight — and, as a result, suffer from a host of health problems.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://muv.asia/forte-fitness-orlando-reviews-bf28.pdf&quot;&gt;forte fitness chattanooga&lt;/a&gt;  Said her Republican opponent, Robert E. Lee: &quot;I&apos;ve covered this district by foot, by car, by air. This is something that takes a strong, healthy man. ... A socialite is not going to do this district any good in Congress.&quot;
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
