<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542552111307">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 14:41:51 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.bdvx1m9q57bs</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I&apos;m on holiday &lt;a href=&quot;https://accentresurfacing.com/wwwflyingdoctororgauemergency-numbers-4110.pdf#peeves&quot;&gt;flyingdoctor.org.au&lt;/a&gt;  Boyd, 31, is a partner at fund management firm Smith &amp; Williamson who was in the same St Andrews hall of residence as the couple during their first year, and studied history of art with Kate.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://archieandtherug.com/landkarte-hochschulmedizinde-9392.pdf#sell&quot;&gt;landkarte-hochschulmedizin.de&lt;/a&gt;  Meanwhile, more than 130 people — shooting victims and their relatives — have sued the U.S. government for damages, claiming that warnings that Hasan had become radicalized were repeatedly ignored because of “political correctness.”
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://newscvm.com/voltaren-resinat-novartis-pharma-preis-e9bb.pdf&quot;&gt;voltaren gel cena dr max&lt;/a&gt;  Sabathia had handed the Rays a six-spot — including five runs with two outs — before Soriano even came to bat for the first time. The Rays rapped three doubles and three singles in the second inning, with one of their runs scoring on a throwing error by catcher Austin Romine.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cabanadolago.com.br/index.php/powermedsnet-reviews-ab8a.pdf&quot;&gt;powermeds.net reviews&lt;/a&gt;  One theory being considered by investigators is that Maria, who is aged between five and six, may have been a victim of an extensive child trafficking network and was left at the settlement in Farsala, 200 miles north of Athens after plans to sell her into illegal adoption fell through.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lovemycase.com/viagra-recept-nlkl-olcsn-f2c2.pdf&quot;&gt;viagra male enhancement distributors&lt;/a&gt;  Manuel&amp;#8217;s daughter was in the train and is in hospital with minor injuries. He told euronews: &amp;#8220;I was coming down here to the bar to have a glass of wine, and saw the wagon in the open field, and my daughter was the first thing I saw&amp;#8230; she was outside&amp;#8230; the neighbours were heroes, total heroes&amp;#8230; I don&amp;#8217;t really know how I feel&amp;#8230; nervous I guess. I can&amp;#8217;t sleep now&amp;#8230;&amp;#8221;
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
