<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542360057019">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">16.11.2018 09:20:57 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.879qm5q33tgs</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Where are you calling from? &lt;a href=&quot;https://muv.asia/stmap_bf280.html?itraconazole.trimethoprim.viagra&quot;&gt;orlistat generico precio espaa&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;I have paid $15,000 for someone to smuggle me to Germany,&quot; says Ahmad Wali, a Kabul university graduate, showing me his passport. &quot;I really don&amp;#039;t want to be a victim of 2014 and civil war.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.chris-cancercommunity.com/stmap_b01a0.html?clozaril.levitra.rogaine&quot;&gt;liverdrugs.com&lt;/a&gt;  The U.S. government partially shut down for the first time in 17 years on Tuesday as a standoff between President Barack Obama and congressional Republicans over healthcare reforms closed museums and national parks and slowed everything from trade negotiations to medical research.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lucky-websolutions.com/stmap_0a7b0.html?cialis.cytotec.famciclovir.tadadel&quot;&gt;onlinepharmacy.me&lt;/a&gt;  Malloy signed one of the nation&apos;s strictest gun-control bills into law on April 4, the day after it was approved by both the state Senate and House of Representatives. The law bans the sale of more than 100 types of military-style rifles, penalizes gun owners who don&apos;t register with the state police by January 1, and limits large-capacity magazines to 10 bullets.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cabanadolago.com.br/index.php/stmap_ab8a0.html?viagra.atomoxetine.abana.tromethamine&quot;&gt;revatio uk&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;I have a feeling of great hope as a result of our mingling and meeting the officials here in (North) Korea,&quot; he said before departing. &quot;I feel we&apos;ve accomplished a lot because of the appearance of mutual hope between us and the North Koreans.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dollingstownfc.com/stmap_68650.html?phenergan.levitra.danazol&quot;&gt;north park pharmacy charlotte nc&lt;/a&gt;  The customer refused telling her it was her tip. He then made her sign the ticket so no one but Kephart could cash the ticket in for the winning money. She went to the lottery and cashed in her tip, but she did give the man a percentage of the ticket, she said she wouldn’t have it any other way.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
