<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542728615098">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">20.11.2018 15:43:35 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.in5rev22guaj</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Can you hear me OK? &lt;a href=&quot;https://digital-matchbox.com/loginspotonmedicsnl-5522.pdf&quot;&gt;login.spotonmedics.nl&lt;/a&gt;  So there&apos;s no rules of civility, but if someone would have joked about fire fighters or people on a military plane crashing, there would undoubtedly be people all over this site hating them and ready to kill, and it would be some of the same people who think it&apos;s so funny now.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.infocalcbba.edu.bo/wwwconsettmedicalcentrecouk-9e88.pdf&quot;&gt;consettmedicalcentre.co.uk&lt;/a&gt;  It&apos;s as close to back to basics as someone of his stature can plausibly come (were he a rock star this would probably be the point in his career where he goes on the road with just a battered acoustic guitar for company). But what the evening lacked in brain-melting production values was more than compensated for by the untrammelled ferocity of Jay-Z&apos;s wordplay. Drawing heavily on Magna Carta, a shaggy rumination on the downsides of fame in a paparazzi plagued world, the bare-bone setting allowed the songs to bristle in a way they didn&apos;t in the studio, so that his broadsides against the vicissitudes of global celebrity were unexpectedly censorious and powerful.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mcmpovos.com/benzocaine-ester-62bd.pdf&quot;&gt;benzocaine vs benzocaine hydrochloride&lt;/a&gt;  Rusbridger said that on 22 July, two days after the Guardian complied with a government request to destroy computer hardware containing encrypted GCHQ files from Snowden, a former CIA employee, executives at the newspaper directed the UK government towards the New York Times and ProPublica, US publishers with whom the paper had shared secret material from GCHQ.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://laser-eye-surgery-reviews.org/benicar-hct-coupon-card-6a83.pdf&quot;&gt;benicar hct coupon card&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;I hope they&apos;re just waiting for the typhoon to pass and will show up as soon as the weather clears,&quot; he said. A higher number of missing had been reported earlier, but some of the fishermen have returned home.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://contactconsultoria.com/index.php/crossroadstreatmentcenterscom-a511.pdf&quot;&gt;localmed.com&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;Obviously the report doesn&amp;#039;t make pleasant reading for anybody - we don&amp;#039;t want to be in this position - we wish we weren&amp;#039;t in this position - but what we need to do now is to accept the report in full and use it to move the school forward.&quot;
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
