<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542643233829">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 16:00:33 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.ytjhqp08c7xo</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I do some voluntary work &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.klevermedia.co.uk/imedstoretop-31f1.pdf&quot;&gt;imedstore.top&lt;/a&gt;  Property taxes, which make up almost all local revenue, were $91.9 billion. That was &quot;not statistically different from property tax revenue of $90.1 billion in the same quarter of 2012,&quot; the Census found.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.proguaru.com.br/tiger-fitness-prime-nutrition-eaas-7684.pdf#assembly&quot;&gt;tiger fitness prime nutrition eaas&lt;/a&gt;  Obama&apos;s announcement Thursday that the United States was canceling joint military exercises with Egypt was the first significant U.S. move to penalize Egypt&apos;s military rulers after the ouster of Mursi. Previously, the U.S. government had announced a decision to halt delivery to Egypt of four U.S.-made F-16 fighters.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.elegantandwild.co.uk/adphorg-75b3.pdf#bonus&quot;&gt;adph.org/wic&lt;/a&gt;  If there&apos;s a BART strike, transit agencies are planning to add bus and ferry service, keep carpool lanes open all day and even give away coffee gift cards to encourage drivers to pick up riders. They&apos;re also encouraging workers to avoid peak traffic hours or telecommute if possible.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://theglobalelite.org/bluemercury-logo-69bc.pdf&quot;&gt;bluemercury spa services&lt;/a&gt;  The report said Snowden, now living in temporary asylum inRussia, attended the conference of the so-called Five Eyesintelligence-sharing network between the United States, Britain,Canada, Australia and New Zealand.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.greenlamindustries.com/blog/meclizine-rxlist-0bae.pdf#english&quot;&gt;meclizine rxlist&lt;/a&gt;  Ague, who has a German shepherd of his own and described himself as &amp;#8220;a huge animal lover&amp;#8221; (he had petitioned for a canine department in his police force last year) said he never thought of doing anything besides saving Mya.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
