<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542640901566">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 15:21:41 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.k8my34hm3pey</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Jonny was here &lt;a href=&quot;https://laser-eye-surgery-reviews.org/airline-carry-on-rules-prescription-drugs-6a83.pdf&quot;&gt;airline carry on rules prescription drugs&lt;/a&gt;  &amp;#8220;He got his revenues,&amp;#8221; Mr. Boehner said on ABC, referring to the deal Congress approved at the beginning of the year to roll back tax cuts for people making more than $400,000. &amp;#8220;We&amp;#8217;re not raising taxes.&amp;#8221;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://reflectiveteens.com/aricept-cena-213a.pdf#aware&quot;&gt;harga obat aricept&lt;/a&gt;  Their work in Pakistan had just been completed when the attack on Malala became headline news. Within 24 hours of the shooting, Pakistan&apos;s Army Chief, who was taking a keen interest in Malala, asked for their professional opinion on what she needed.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.techdesighn.com/fuelshaker-pro-productions-b26f.pdf#reins&quot;&gt;fuelshaker pro products&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;Although we would expect furloughs to continue shrinking in an extended shutdown, the longer the delay in authorizing spending, the greater the incidence of negative spillovers to private activity will be,&quot; said Robert DiClemente, Citigroup chief U.S. economist.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://leotoys.cl/adecur-terazosina-2206.pdf#disgust&quot;&gt;adecur terazosina&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;Nothing&apos;s ever happened like this,&quot; he said. &quot;We just have to wait for the police. People who came to the party, they are good people. We don&apos;t know what kind of problems (the shooter had) or what caused it. We just had no idea.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://oporajeyo.com/catuaba-rx-bf45.pdf&quot;&gt;catuaba tea&lt;/a&gt;  Temperatures in the Blue Mountains, a popular weekend getaway for Sydneysiders, are expected to reach up to 30 degrees Celsius (86 degrees Fahrenheit). In Sydney itself they could hit 35 degrees Celsius (95 Fahrenheit).
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
