<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542366549862">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">16.11.2018 11:09:09 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.24xfxhguw0h4</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Canada&gt;Canada &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mikasafloors.com/stmap_bdec0.html?zyban.cialis.deltasone.duloxetine&quot;&gt;bupropion hcl xl 150 mg and alcohol&lt;/a&gt;  The company, the No. 2 automaker in terms of U.S. sales, earned $1.8 billion excluding special charges, up 52% from year earlier. Revenue rose 14% to $38.1 billion as the number of vehicles sold worldwide rose 16%. The earnings and sales both beat analysts&apos; forecasts.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.md-interiors.co.uk/stmap_a6a40.html?dimenhydrinate.levitra.amlodipine.azathioprine&quot;&gt;rocketremedies.com&lt;/a&gt;  Gold skidded 1.8 percent to $1,342.56 an ounce, its weakest since mid-August while Brent crude added about 0.8 percent to $112.40 as investors watched diplomatic efforts to place Syria&apos;s chemical weapons under international control stepped up.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.haroldwhitefuneraldirectors.co.uk/stmap_bd820.html?vasodilan.cialis.crixivan.mononitrate&quot;&gt;where can i buy estradiol&lt;/a&gt;  In the end, Republican House of Representatives Speaker John Boehner blinked, and allowed a vote on a Senate plan that included a short-term increase in the debt ceiling and governing funding through January 15. The measure got 82 Republican votes - enough to secure its passage.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://digital-matchbox.com/stmap_55220.html?virecta.levitra.testosterone&quot;&gt;changzhou yuekang medical appliance co&lt;/a&gt;  Irish voters decided to retain the upper house of the country&apos;s legislature, dealing a surprise blow to Prime Minister Enda Kenny, who had called for its closure on the grounds that it cost too much to run and did too little.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://archieandtherug.com/stmap_93920.html?levitra.myambutol.droxia&quot;&gt;lamotrigine 25 mg po tabs&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;The president nominates people he supports and believes in, and it will be two people who believe as strongly as Block and Griffin that workers&apos; rights matter in the 21st century whether they have a union or not, and most don&apos;t,&quot; Cohen said.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
