<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542619263905">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 09:21:03 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.cp3y8d3ynb3e</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I hate shopping &lt;a href=&quot;https://laser-eye-surgery-reviews.org/newtown-medical-group-fax-number-6a83.pdf&quot;&gt;newtown medical group patient portal&lt;/a&gt;  Human Rights Watch says that 200 Alawite villagers are still being held hostage by the rebels. It has called on the United Nations Security Council to engage the International Criminal Court to make clear to all the parties involved in the Syria conflict that they will be held to account for crimes.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lucky-websolutions.com/can-i-buy-morning-after-pill-in-tesco-pharmacy-0a7b.pdf#infectious&quot;&gt;prescription drugs effects on the economy&lt;/a&gt;  Ward, former chief policy advisor to Labour Party leader the Rt Hon John Smith and later one of Mosley&apos;s key advisors at the FIA, confirmed yesterday that he was considering standing, if only to generate &quot;a debate&quot; about how the governing body should be run.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.greenlamindustries.com/blog/kidshealthorg-stress-0bae.pdf#deserted&quot;&gt;kidshealth.org stress&lt;/a&gt;  As part of a £37 million package of investment in electric vehicles in the UK, the government offers a 75 per cent grant for the provision of domestic charging points.  This subsidy applies to the BMW i Wallbox, bringing the installed cost down to £315 incl. VAT*.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.anupamdebashisroy.com/hydroxycut-price-in-malaysia-f2ef.pdf&quot;&gt;hydroxycut sx 7 black onyx ingredients&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;It takes a very particular mind to want to run with public money a public institution. You have to have the right kind of energy and I&amp;#039;m not sure who has that. You&amp;#039;ve got to do your budgets proper. And you are now a public officer. You can&amp;#039;t indulge your fantasies, you must indulge London&amp;#039;s fantasies. That&amp;#039;s a very different order of things.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ascfinancialadvisers.co.uk/wo-kann-ich-gnstig-viagra-kaufen-5553.pdf&quot;&gt;is viagra used for performance anxiety&lt;/a&gt;  âIâm doing this to show my brother and all the other people inside that we support them and we will do what it takes to get them out,&quot; 16-year-old Sandy Estrada of Phoenix told Not One More Deportation.  &quot;I want the president to know that everyone deserves to be with their families and that he can stop our pain.â
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
