<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542561031424">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 17:10:31 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1i9fx9rpzmqk4</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>How would you like the money? &lt;a href=&quot;http://reflectiveteens.com/westfield-indiana-kroger-pharmacy-hours-213a.pdf&quot;&gt;kroger pharmacy jobs indiana&lt;/a&gt;  Since the Defense of Marriage Act was found unconstitutional on Wednesday, talk of same-sex marriage -- and divorce -- has dominated the news. NBC 5 in Chicago took a look at recent census data and found that states that legally allow gay marriage actually have lower divorce rates than states that only allow heterosexual unions.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://laser-eye-surgery-reviews.org/pharmunitoiturl4itcom-6a83.pdf#refuge&quot;&gt;prescriptionglasses123.com&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;The law is clear,&quot; says Shadi Hamid, a fellow at the Saban Center for Middle East Policy at the Brookings Institution. &quot;It is only complicated when we are willing to ignore the law in the name of politics, which sets a very negative precedent and sends a negative message to those watching U.S. policy.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.elegantandwild.co.uk/eyequeue-kenya-75b3.pdf#higher&quot;&gt;eyequestion sensory software&lt;/a&gt;  Nidal Hasan collected nearly $300,000 in his military salary while awaiting trial. His civil attorney, John Galligan, wouldn&apos;t disclose any information about the charities or proof that donations had been made. An Army spokesman told the Associated Press the military can&apos;t get back the money because Hasan, like any other service member charged with a crime, continued to receive his military salary until he was convicted last month.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.casadeadoracao.com.br/index.php/sinopharm-capital-limited-bac9.pdf#critical&quot;&gt;sinopharm chemical reagent&lt;/a&gt;  Phablets, a cross between a phone and a tablet, have been ona roll since late 2011 as tech-savvy consumers, particularly inAsia, devote more time browsing data-heavy Web pages anddownloading media content. Even Samsung&apos;s flagship Galaxy S4smartphone, released in April this year, has a 5-inch screenthat puts it squarely in the phablet category for some analysts.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.elegantandwild.co.uk/webmailimedorgbr-75b3.pdf&quot;&gt;epimed.org&lt;/a&gt;  He was arrested in May in Oceanside, north of San Diego, and charged with a count of soliciting the murder of his wife, Meggan Lambesis, who had filed for divorce a year earlier. They had been married eight years.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
