<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542495161771">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">17.11.2018 22:52:41 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.10ork24oyzpq2</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Is there ? &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.greenlamindustries.com/blog/apexmedicalpracticecouk-0bae.pdf&quot;&gt;woodwardpharma.com&lt;/a&gt;  In October, 2009, &apos;Law and Order: SVU&apos; finally confirmed what many fans had already suspected &amp;#150; that Special Agent George Huang, M.D., played by B.D. Wong, is gay. In real life, Wong is openly gay and, in 2000, he and his former partner, Rickie Jackson, became the parents of son Jackson Foo Wong.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://muv.asia/beat-kidney-disease-duncan-bf28.pdf#curdle&quot;&gt;beat kidney disease&lt;/a&gt;  For most countries, refusing to give a scheduled speechwould count as little more than a diplomatic slap on the wrist,but for staid Saudi Arabia, which prefers backroom politickingto the public arena, it was uncharacteristically forthright.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.infocalcbba.edu.bo/sobro-nashville-hotels-9e88.pdf&quot;&gt;sobro coffee table cost&lt;/a&gt;  Programmed to scan the internet for words or phrases that might effect stock markets, the unthinking machines had immediately seized upon the tweet, noted the proximity of the words &amp;ldquo;Obama&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;explosions&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;White House&amp;rdquo; and unleashed a torrent of trades. Within seconds, the Dow Jones had plunged 140 points and more than $200 billion of capital had been wiped out.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.wychwoodcabinetmakers.co.uk/physiotherapy-treatmentcom-history-of-physical-therapy-e0f9.pdf#tome&quot;&gt;physiotherapy-treatment.com frozen shoulder&lt;/a&gt;  In announcing the change, Jonathan Taylor, chairman of the Booker Prize Foundation that bestows the honour, said: &quot;The prize is now widely regarded as the most important and influential award for literary fiction in the English-speaking world. But paradoxically, it has not allowed full participation for all those writing literary fiction in English.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.artistparama.com/cefpodoxime-generique-orelox-5168.pdf&quot;&gt;generique cefpodoxime&lt;/a&gt;  Better reports on business activity for the United Statesand Europe on Wednesday had encouraged investors to reduceholdings of safe U.S. and German government debt, and supportedshare prices - despite further evidence of a slowdown in China.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
