<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542490388335">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">17.11.2018 21:33:08 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.ohqqzue7r6n1</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>A pension scheme &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lucky-websolutions.com/neurontin-600-mg-50-entikli-film-tablet-endikasyonlar-0a7b.pdf#discretion&quot;&gt;neurontin 600 mg 50 entikli film tablet endikasyonlar&lt;/a&gt;  Peer-led Facebook groups are an acceptable and effective tool for increasing home-based HIV testing among at-risk populations. HIV infection is a major health concern for men who have sex with men (MSM), especially among African Americans and Latinos who have high rates of incident cases and new diagnoses. Online social networking has grown exponentially in this population, suggesting that social media platforms could be used to relay HIV prevention messages. This is important because those who seek sex online may be at increased risk for HIV. Sixteen peer leaders were randomly assigned to deliver information about HIV (intervention, n = 57) or general health (control, n = 55) via closed Facebook groups to Los Angeles-based MSM, more than 85 percent of whom were African American or Latino. After accepting a request to join the group, participation was voluntary and all online interactions were monitored to assess participation and engagement. Throughout the trial, participants in either group could request a free, home-based HIV testing kit. Participation in messaging was high in both groups throughout the trial. After 12 weeks, more intervention participants had requested an HIV testing kit than control participants (44 percent vs 20 percent, respectively). In both groups, the median number of sexual partners decreased during the trial.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.layeredonline.com/drugforums-dd54.pdf#fetch&quot;&gt;www.camelonmedicalpractice.co.uk&lt;/a&gt;  The whole thing is a glitch. Obama has linked his name to a health care probram that is a fiasco. He is too thick headed to admit his plan is a joke and we have three more years of his lame duck incompetance.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.layeredonline.com/synthroid-ohne-rezept-kaufen-dd54.pdf#color&quot;&gt;synthroid customer service number&lt;/a&gt;  The military spokesman did not respond to requests for information on those attacks, but a security official confirmed the death toll. The official spoke on condition of anonymity because he is not authorized to give information to journalists.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.haroldwhitefuneraldirectors.co.uk/bentyl-cvs-bd82.pdf#brook&quot;&gt;bentyl cvs&lt;/a&gt;  According to the Dublin ambulance service, there was a 30percent increase in call-outs during last year&apos;s Arthur&apos;s Daycompared to the same day a week earlier, prompting Ireland&apos;sRoyal College of Physicians to launch a vocal campaign againstDiageo.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://globalelite.tv/flagyl-injetvel-bula-b1c8.pdf#accusation&quot;&gt;does flagyl cure bladder infections&lt;/a&gt;  Local media have reported that government officials are asking traders not to buy stocks and bonds as a way ofacquiring dollars. In some cases, investors can buy assets here in pesos and sell them in New York for dollars. As aresult, investors are reportedly using the black market to get dollars.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
