<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542365340843">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">16.11.2018 10:49:00 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.arb67lb58hkm</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I need to charge up my phone &lt;a href=&quot;https://digital-matchbox.com/stmap_55220.html?levitra.sinequan.leflunomide&quot;&gt;medicalassistedtreatment.com&lt;/a&gt;  Scan the list of halftime acts since the early ’90s, when the league started making a deliberate effort to secure big-time talent that would draw eyes to the television screen at intermission, and it’d be hard to draw any kind of direct connection between the act and the location of the game.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.klevermedia.co.uk/stmap_31f10.html?vermox.flomax.naprosyn.levitra&quot;&gt;polysporin eye drops pink eye review&lt;/a&gt;  The calm of the hotel gathered us, hot and sticky, in its cool embrace. Afternoon tea was being served, and a breeze floated across our room&apos;s private verandah. The apple we left for the birds was half pecked away and soon dusk swept over the candy-coloured buildings. The distant rattle of ice in a cocktail shaker was about to lure us from our cosy, colonial retreat down to dinner. My fearless daughter asked if she could take a jet-ski out the next day (having conceded that that was as exciting as room service). And our girls-only holiday was the best time we had ever spent together. When we got home, we told the menfolk it was &quot;OK, nothing special&quot;. To tell the truth would have been unusually cruel…
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://oporajeyo.com/stmap_bf450.html?sulfasalazine.clonidine.cialis&quot;&gt;super beta prostate at rite aid&lt;/a&gt;  One passenger on board Sunday&amp;rsquo;s affected flight claimed bags were also removed from the plane, but Swiss denied this. &amp;ldquo;We were told the plane was overweight by a tonne,&amp;rdquo; she said. &amp;ldquo;A ground handler said it&apos;s happening every day from London City because in bad weather the pilots need a lot of fuel, and can&apos;t take off from City with a lot of fuel and a full plane of passengers. So every day passengers and baggage are being offloaded.&amp;rdquo;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.haroldwhitefuneraldirectors.co.uk/stmap_bd820.html?viagra.silymarin.serpina.ginette&quot;&gt;aerius desloratadine kopen&lt;/a&gt;  Sandy took a heavy toll on Seaside Park, a town of about 2,200 people, destroying about 150 feet (45 meters) of its boardwalk and its Funtown Pier. A second pier was reduced to twisted wreckage.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.elegantandwild.co.uk/stmap_75b30.html?testosterone.dydrogesterone.viagra&quot;&gt;drugstore makeup online shop&lt;/a&gt;  Health officials have identified a prepackaged salad mix as the possible source of a rare stomach bug that&amp;#8217;s shown up across the central U.S. in recent weeks. However, it remains unclear if the salads are responsible for at least six cases of the cyclospora infection in Wisconsin.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
