<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542544581296">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 12:36:21 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.a9lfb4cakgtq</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Wonderfull great site &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.wychwoodcabinetmakers.co.uk/kupovina-cialisa-u-srbiji-e0f9.pdf&quot;&gt;kupovina cialisa u srbiji&lt;/a&gt;  You&amp;#8217;ll find that Organophosphates are classified as nerve agents, and there are no way any &amp;#8220;herbal teas&amp;#8221; can have any effect on it as not only will the absorption of any liquid be too slow, it would also be completely useless against the toxin that targets the nerves in the body unless you mix in extracts from highly poisonous plants like Belladonna, in which case, your tea would cause more harm than good. You&amp;#8217;ll see that they are classified in the same category as nerve gases like Sarin and VX, which are some of the worst chemical warfare agents ever produced. The real antidote is Atropine (made from the extract of the belladonna plant, also called Deadly Nightshade) which usually is injected directly into the muscles affected (including the heart, to prevent the nerve agent from causing a cardiac arrest). You&amp;#8217;ll find that in your example, Paraquat Dichloride (research the actual name of the herbicide next time), death usually comes about a month after ingestion (from gradual organ failure), while Organophosphates only takes minutes to kill someone (by causing cardiac arrest) if a lethal dose is ingested.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.weymouthskatepark.co.uk/doxycycline-hyclate-100mg-cap-acne-6ae3.pdf#training&quot;&gt;doxycycline hyclate 100mg cap acne&lt;/a&gt;  Beyond that, the schedule remains basically identical, with none of the 10 races in the Chase for the Sprint Cup changed. Once again, there will be just two off-weekends: one after Darlington in the spring; the other after New Hampshire in July.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://laser-eye-surgery-reviews.org/methyl-1-d-black-6a83.pdf&quot;&gt;methyl 1 d xl 135 caps&lt;/a&gt;  &amp;ldquo;This was a terribly destructive act, this was American democracy that they were having a go at,&amp;rdquo; Snow said. &amp;ldquo;It was a most dramatic event...It made the Americans feel like they had completely lost it.&amp;rdquo;
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://accentresurfacing.com/shoppers-pharmacy-annapolis-phone-number-4110.pdf&quot;&gt;shoppers pharmacy quarterfield rd&lt;/a&gt;  The Waldorf, Maryland, resident came from a large religious family that spent the hours after the shooting waiting for news, praying and reading the Bible. According to the Washington Post, the family gathered at the home of her parents, both in their 80s, in Prince George&apos;s County.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tarokasongbad.com/air-canada-traveling-with-prescription-drugs-e3c4.pdf&quot;&gt;best food to eat after taking drugs&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;Despite their knowledge of these illegal searches, the policymakers ...took no action to train, supervise or discipline any officers who committed these knowingly illegal searches,&quot; the plaintiffs allege. &quot;Instead, certain of the defendant officers were rewarded with commendations for their aggressive police tactics and jobs well-done by their supervisors, including commendations from Chief Edward Flynn.&quot;
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
