<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542566259351">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 18:37:39 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1sq2ggmjckt9h</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I live here &lt;a href=&quot;https://accentresurfacing.com/va-uacom-4110.pdf&quot;&gt;clarkspharmacyaz.com&lt;/a&gt;  Certainly the most common and accepted way to say &quot;I&apos;m a resident of Berlin&quot; is &quot;Ich bin Berliner,&quot; i.e. without the indefinite article. But, for many speakers, it is by no means incorrect or ungrammatical to say &quot;Ich bin ein Berliner.&quot; Some of my [Berlin friends] in fact applauded Kennedy on his nuanced use of German, since for them the sentence without the indefinite article implies that the speaker is a native Berliner, while the sentence with &quot;ein&quot; suggests either more recent residence in Berlin or even solidarity with its inhabitants.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.wychwoodcabinetmakers.co.uk/canadian-drugs-with-prescription-e0f9.pdf&quot;&gt;safe legit online pharmacy&lt;/a&gt;  &amp;#8220;This was a systems error which only affected one flight,&amp;#8221; an EasyJet representative told the paper. &amp;#8220;Even our new long-term fleet deal doesn&amp;#8217;t take us that far into the future.&amp;#8221;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.wychwoodcabinetmakers.co.uk/clopidogrel-bez-recepty-e0f9.pdf#structure&quot;&gt;clopidogrel actavis 75 mg cena&lt;/a&gt;  While Twitter Chief Executive Officer Dick Costolo has saidthat management isn’t concentrating on an IPO, the company iswidely predicted to hold a share sale before long to help itbankroll expansion, and give some early investors a way torealize financial gains on their holdings.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ecorporationbd.com/potenzmittelkaufeneu-erfahrung-aaa8.pdf#nowadays&quot;&gt;potenzmittelkaufen.eu erfahrung&lt;/a&gt;  He insisted his politics were markedly different from those of his Marxist father: &quot;I have pursued a different path and I have a different vision.&quot; He also said he was &quot;appalled&quot; by the Mail&amp;#039;s &quot;character assassination&quot; of a man who had served in the Royal Navy during World War II after escaping Nazi persecution.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://kssgrp.com/hydroxy-ecdysterone-side-effects-5457.pdf#buffer&quot;&gt;online buy cheap ecdysterone&lt;/a&gt;  By the time Ehrhart arrived at Betty Ford on May 28 for a 90-day treatment program, her addiction had overtaken her life. She said she spent $200 to $300 a day to purchase oxycodone, a narcotic painkiller.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
