<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542550536851">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 14:15:36 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.11eabnlo0uluh</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I&apos;m only getting an answering machine &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.proguaru.com.br/wwwdistrimedcomconseils-7684.pdf#intricate&quot;&gt;distrimed.com/conseils&lt;/a&gt;  &amp;#8220;When I talk about my sexuality on the show or in public, I still feel really scared. So I&amp;#8217;ll try to act confident or I&amp;#8217;ll make jokes about it, but there&amp;#8217;s still a piece of me that goes, &amp;#8216;What is this costing me in my career?&amp;#8217;&amp;#8221; she said.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.greenlamindustries.com/blog/impres-pharma-salaries-0bae.pdf&quot;&gt;impres pharma sales rep salary&lt;/a&gt;  The direct sales plans are meeting resistance from BMWdealers, however, with the magazine quoting one unnamed dealeras saying the company had pledged at least temporarily not touse the sales force in Germany.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.md-interiors.co.uk/roys-pharmacy-a6a4.pdf&quot;&gt;roys pharmacy tonasket wa&lt;/a&gt;  The scientists found a number of similar characteristics among those with severe asthma. For example, over half of adults with severe asthma regularly took oral corticosteroids, but still had greater airway obstruction compared to people with mild asthma.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.md-interiors.co.uk/admedicine-bgcom-a6a4.pdf#skin&quot;&gt;suncoasthealthcouncil.org&lt;/a&gt;  NEW YORK, July 15 (Reuters) - Stock markets around the worldwere little changed on Monday as investors awaited the onslaughtof corporate earnings to be released this week, which could helpoffset signs of weakness in the economy.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lucky-websolutions.com/wcrx-pharmacy-0a7b.pdf#yourself&quot;&gt;wcrx pharmacy&lt;/a&gt;  ANKARA, Oct 24 (Reuters) - The United States is concernedTurkey&apos;s decision to build a missile defence system with aChinese firm could undermine allied air defences, its envoy saidon Thursday, but dismissed talk of a broader rift with Ankara.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
