<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542662318908">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 21:18:38 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.ue7skh1xu29b</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I&apos;m retired &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.elegantandwild.co.uk/hydroxycut-reviews-amazon-75b3.pdf#capitalist&quot;&gt;hydroxycut online in india&lt;/a&gt;  The process of funding a multi-million-pound emergency ambulance service will be changed, with the NDO overseeing the moving of money, from health boards as buyers of services, to the delivery organisation.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://muv.asia/flagyl-suspenso-preo-bf28.pdf&quot;&gt;flagyl drug uses&lt;/a&gt;  Shares in Smiths News were up 7 percent at 167 pence at 0950GMT on Tuesday on the London Stock Exchange.($1 = 0.6695 British pounds) (Reporting by Abhirup Roy in Bangalore; Editing by GopakumarWarrier, Supriya Kurane)
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mikasafloors.com/compraranabolicocom-reviews-bdec.pdf&quot;&gt;compraranabolico.com legit&lt;/a&gt;  The key word used by one of my fellow debaters was &amp;#039;carente&amp;#039; - it can translate as &amp;#039;needy,&amp;#039; in both economic and emotional terms, and the two senses can apply to the backgrounds of some of the players in the local teams. They can be crying out for a paternal figure in a way that is not always the case with European players.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://freelifesinsurancequotes.com/popmedfarmcombr-6f97.pdf&quot;&gt;webmail.medfarm.com.br&lt;/a&gt;  Wearing his trademark Sunday red shirt, Woods played solidly for the next eight holes, lining up mid-range birdie putts on each green while squandering his only close opportunity from six feet at the second.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ecorporationbd.com/memory-boost-xl-ingredients-aaa8.pdf#coats&quot;&gt;memory boost xl&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;Ohio has traditionally had a more competitive health insurance market than other states with a wider range of prices and choices -- from simple, high deductible coverage to comprehensive, full service plans,&quot; Lieutenant Governor Mary Taylor said.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
