<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542646617870">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 16:56:57 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.3k5ouq0wam4</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I&apos;ll send you a text &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mcmpovos.com/edge-pharmacy-jobs-62bd.pdf&quot;&gt;edge pharma&lt;/a&gt;  Tweet It&amp;#8217;s almost time! The Android Headlines Show will be live tonight at 8:30pm Eastern Time. This week is going to be a blast. I think Nick is going to be out this week, so I&amp;#8217;ll be running the show. Alex will be there, and I think Justin will be returning as well. It&amp;#8217;s anyone&amp;#8217;s [&amp;hellip;]
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://globalelite.tv/x-alphabet-words-with-meaning-b1c8.pdf#subsequent&quot;&gt;x alphabet words with meaning&lt;/a&gt;  Michael Oren, Israel&apos;s ambassador to the United States, madeclear his nation&apos;s shift in views on the civil war in aninterview with the Jerusalem Post. Even Assad&apos;s defeat by alQaeda-aligned rebels would be preferable to Syria&apos;s currentalliance with Israel&apos;s arch-foe Iran, Oren said.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://leotoys.cl/herbalife-cell-u-loss-tablets-benefits-2206.pdf#universe&quot;&gt;herbalife cell u loss price&lt;/a&gt;  House of Representatives Speaker John Boehner urged hisunruly caucus to show flexibility over a measure to keep thegovernment open. Separately, Republican Senator Jeff Sessionssaid there would be no shutdown or government default.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://globalelite.tv/can-i-take-voltaren-and-ibuprofen-plus-together-b1c8.pdf#us&quot;&gt;is it a good idea to take ibuprofen before getting a tattoo&lt;/a&gt;  However, &quot;If an inmate gets to the point where he can&apos;t tell us what his wishes are, for instance if he&apos;s found unresponsive in his cell, and we don&apos;t have a DNR, we&apos;re going to get nourishment into him. That&apos;s what doctors do. They&apos;re going to follow their medical ethics,&quot; Hayhoe said. &quot;We&apos;d take any and all measures to sustain their life.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jalapaoecolodge.com.br/index.php/jual-foredi-gel-online-7abb.pdf&quot;&gt;jual foredi yogyakarta&lt;/a&gt;  The day after the shooting, Thephakaysone, who police saidpointed his gun at strangers in at least two separate incidentson the night of the shooting, was arrested at his family&apos;s SanFrancisco home.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
