<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542690258211">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">20.11.2018 05:04:18 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.c55siiuw3069</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>The United States &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tarokasongbad.com/chobani-smoothie-review-e3c4.pdf&quot;&gt;chobani smoothie price&lt;/a&gt;  The iPhone 5c is essentially Apple’s new iPhone 5 replacement, while the iPhone 5s is the next flagship Apple smartphone. The 5c comes with the same internals as the iPhone 5 and switches out the 5’s aluminum back for a plastic, glossy color-coated rear shell. The 5s, comparatively, starts at $199 with a two-year contract and comes with an improved A7 64-bit processor, a fingerprint scanner built into its home button, and an enhanced camera.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sarah-hyland.net/onlinedrugstorebuycom-79a8.pdf&quot;&gt;healthmomma.com&lt;/a&gt;  The team made it out on the balcony and Sargeant wrapped her in a bear hug as Carver and Scott Schecter secured her in a harness. The crowd below burst into applause and cheers as she was pulled in safely.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.chris-cancercommunity.com/turmeric-curcumin-for-lupus-b01a.pdf#favor&quot;&gt;turmeric curcumin vitamin shoppe&lt;/a&gt;  A key part of Obamacare, officially known as the AffordableCare Act, goes into effect on Oct. 1, when states are supposedto begin offering Americans health insurance options throughonline exchanges to compare prices.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mcmpovos.com/que-es-levitra-de-20-mg-62bd.pdf&quot;&gt;side effects of levitra 20 mg&lt;/a&gt;  Bacelar is primarily a dog whisperer, but claims she can communicate with any species -- though she does admit that animals that spend more time with people give her more vivid visions and are easier to communicate with than wild animals.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://virtual-operations.com/losartan-potassium-blood-pressure-medicine-92e2.pdf&quot;&gt;losartan hctz side effects hair loss&lt;/a&gt;  How long the increase might suffice - a few weeks or a fewmonths - was unclear. But agreement by Republicans and Democratsto raise the debt ceiling would at least stave off a possibledefault after Oct. 17, when Treasury Secretary Jack Lew hasdetermined the government will no longer be able to borrow.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
