<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542357714464">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">16.11.2018 08:41:54 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.7a3fk6ja08da</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I&apos;m afraid that number&apos;s ex-directory &lt;a href=&quot;https://oporajeyo.com/stmap_bf450.html?tadasoft.indapamide.cialis&quot;&gt;what is tamsulosin prescribed for&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;After the last statement by the king of Morocco which revoked the pardon, the Spanish and Moroccan ministries of justice are in contact to decide what to do, how to proceed now,&quot; a Spanish foreign ministry spokeswoman told AFP.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mcmpovos.com/stmap_62bd0.html?amlodipine.aleve.mevacor.levitra&quot;&gt;iso fuzion gfriend&lt;/a&gt;  The clashes with riot police, known for cracking down hard on dissent, added to political tension not seen for years, already heightened by the discovery of a bomb and some grenades around the city on Friday.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.haroldwhitefuneraldirectors.co.uk/stmap_bd820.html?vidalista.nexium.cialis&quot;&gt;micardis 80 mg side effects&lt;/a&gt;  The Pope&amp;rsquo;s remarks about youth unemployment will resonate far beyond South America &amp;ndash; jobless rates among the young in Greece and Spain are near 60 per cent and are almost as dire in countries like Italy and Portugal.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.weymouthskatepark.co.uk/stmap_6ae30.html?ibuprofen.permethrin.viagra.tadalis-sx&quot;&gt;aripiprazole 2 mg goodrx&lt;/a&gt;  Dell&apos;s fortunes remain closely tied to PC sales, despite $13billion in acquisitions since 2008 to expand into everythingfrom software to networking. PC sales, which have been shrinkingfor the last three years, still yield half of revenue.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lovemycase.com/stmap_f2c20.html?cialis.capoten.captopril&quot;&gt;csc health and safety&lt;/a&gt;  Mee’s lawyer, John Trevena, argued that his client was not involved in the robbery and said she suffers from Tourette’s Syndrome, which may have contributed to her erratic behavior at the time of the murder.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
