<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542372003148">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">16.11.2018 12:40:03 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.whnyac1kq6dt</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Until August &lt;a href=&quot;https://laser-eye-surgery-reviews.org/stmap_6a830.html?proscar.cialis.clopidogrel&quot;&gt;what is nugenix testosterone booster&lt;/a&gt;  Based on the disappointing sales results from China, and a higher than expected full-year tax rate, Yum now expects an earnings per share decline for 2013 in the high-single to low-double-digit percentage range. It previously had expected a mid-single-digit percentage decline in full-year earnings per share. Both estimates exclude special items.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://accentresurfacing.com/stmap_41100.html?viagra.ayurslim.terramycin.sumycin&quot;&gt;bcbsalmedicare.com&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;Real Housewives of Beverly Hills&quot; star Brandi Glanville exposed her rear while in a tennis match with her 6-year-old son on July 5, 2013. The former model may have been recreating the iconic Athena Tennis Girl poster from 1976 -- or she may just have suffered a wardrobe whoopsy.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://sjofartsbygningen.no/stmap_7ef00.html?levitra.remeron.caduet&quot;&gt;triple crown medical suites paris ky&lt;/a&gt;  Another idea, allowing foreign peacekeepers under the United Nations to patrol sensitive areas, is also problematic for Israel since such forces have not had a stellar record on Israel&apos;s borders in the past.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.artistparama.com/stmap_51680.html?cefadroxil.viagra.galantamine&quot;&gt;burgemedsupply.com&lt;/a&gt;  The only flaw that hasn’t gotten attention in the game is the dated look. The golden art style and the brilliant makeup of each and every city and building still stand out, but the character models look as dated as ever here in 2013, animating stiffly and lacking detail.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tarokasongbad.com/stmap_e3c40.html?pentoxifylline.cialis.starlix&quot;&gt;sexpill.store&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;Today, we again call on all nations to work to bring to an end the conflict that has cost the lives of more than 100,000 Syrians, and to support the OPCW&apos;s efforts in the hope that future generations can live in a world free from the horrors of chemical weapons.&quot;
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
