<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542546780330">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 13:13:00 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1hxaj9blxlbdf</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Do you like it here? &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.chris-cancercommunity.com/gold-max-pink-capsules-b01a.pdf&quot;&gt;gold max pink capsules&lt;/a&gt;  America&apos;s Haunts, a trade association, estimates there are 1,200 large-scale, for-profit haunted attractions in the U.S. plus another 3,000 haunted houses operated by charities that open for only a day or two every year. The commercial attractions collectively bring in from $300 million to $500 million annually.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.md-interiors.co.uk/healthskyenalibabacom-a6a4.pdf#celebrate&quot;&gt;nu-umedspa.com&lt;/a&gt;  “But we also need to keep a realistic eye on what today’s statistics mean for the majority of NHS patients. The NHS performs hundreds of millions of procedures each year, and only a very small number of these ever give cause for a complaint.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lucky-websolutions.com/accutane-2015-reviews-0a7b.pdf&quot;&gt;accutane treatment process&lt;/a&gt;  Vivendi is selling the shares for $13.60 each, a 10 percentdiscount to Activision&apos;s closing price on Thursday. After thedeal, Vivendi will retain a stake of 83 million shares, or 12percent of the video games maker best known for the Call of Dutyseries and online multi-player game World of Warcraft.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://virtual-operations.com/burbank-village-compounding-pharmacy-92e2.pdf&quot;&gt;burbank village compounding pharmacy&lt;/a&gt;  Liverpool&apos;s fans have remained loyal to Suarez throughout a number of controversial issues over recent seasons, including his biting of Ivanovic and his use of racist language to Manchester United&apos;s Patrice Evra.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tarokasongbad.com/acheter-angelique-confite-e3c4.pdf&quot;&gt;angelique confite acheter&lt;/a&gt;  Two months later, Lincoln, Neb.-area authorities found the bodies of Marion Bartlett, 57; and his 35-year-old wife, Velda, in an outbuilding. Their 2-year-old daughter, Betty Jean, had been clubbed to death with the butt of a gun and her body stuffed in a cardboard box. Missing were Velda Bartlett&apos;s 14-year-old daughter by a previous marriage, Caril Fugate, and her boyfriend, Starkweather.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
