<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542539020395">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 11:03:40 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1kn24q08rhdeo</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Yes, I play the guitar &lt;a href=&quot;http://sjofartsbygningen.no/pharmaciesaintmartinnet-7ef0.pdf#naive&quot;&gt;anmedhealth.org.apescout.com&lt;/a&gt;  The Pet&amp;#345;ín Hill Observation Tower is a great spot for viewing autumn leaves in the city. The lovely hill in the shadow of Prague Castle offers sweeping views of the city and an idyll among the former royal orchards. Kids and lovers are invariably drawn to the funicular - your tram ticket&apos;s all you need - the 299-step faux Eiffel Tower, mirror maze and &amp;#352;tefánik Observatory.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://sjofartsbygningen.no/mysteroidsnet-7ef0.pdf#meat&quot;&gt;pharmacy-bg.com&lt;/a&gt;  In March 2008, the law firm Eversheds which is based at Bridgewater Place, wrote to the council &quot;increasingly concerned about the safety of our employees and other pedestrians using the roads and footpaths in the vicinity of Bridgewater Place&quot;.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://accentresurfacing.com/wwwtunisieeuromedyouthnet-4110.pdf#pan&quot;&gt;euromedyouth.net&lt;/a&gt;  A growing number of voices in the SPD is warning theleadership of Germany&apos;s oldest party against entering another&quot;grand coalition&quot; under Merkel - which could lead to a period ofuncertainty as she searches for another coalition partner.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://paradiseinmexico.com.mx/wwwhealthichoicescomhealthichoicesgems-c13c.pdf&quot;&gt;www.healthichoices.com&lt;/a&gt;  According to the study, the proteins that make up the threads come in two varieties: one that acts like a stretchy bungee cord which account for the stiffness of the filaments - eighty per cent of the threads are made from this protein - and twenty per cent are made of a soft and stretchy variety.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.casadeadoracao.com.br/index.php/sierra-pharmacy-bac9.pdf#trifling&quot;&gt;sierra pharmacy fontana&lt;/a&gt;  According to the World Health Organization, obsessive-compulsive disorder, or OCD, is one of the 10 leading causes of disability in the developed world. âOCD is characterized by recurrent disturbing, distressing or intrusive thoughts called obsessions, or ritualized behaviors or mental acts, called compulsions,â says Grice. âIndividuals with OCD usually try to actively dismiss or neutralize an obsession by performing a compulsion or avoiding situations that trigger these thoughts, but the compulsion is a short-term fix that ends up feeding the OCD cycle.â
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
