<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542641040290">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 15:24:00 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.10bnnx83vt5mn</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Can you hear me OK? &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cabanadolago.com.br/index.php/vepesid-ampulle-cena-ab8a.pdf#response&quot;&gt;vepesid lek cena&lt;/a&gt;  It’s probably because GLBenchmark gives more points for geometry (vertices) performance, while BaseMark X put more of an emphasis on pixel performance. since most current games try to limit the number of vertices, it didn&amp;#8217;t feel like geometry performance was hurting the 5.8 in the games mentioned above. Additionally, the lower resolution saved its bacon when it comes to pixel performance.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.techdesighn.com/macphailpharmacycom-b26f.pdf&quot;&gt;segelinine.com&lt;/a&gt;  The source identified the woman as Miriam Carey, 34, of Stamford, Conn. Carey tried to plow her car into a barricade at the White House, then led cops on a high-speed chase before being shot dead near the Capitol, according to reports.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sarah-hyland.net/tamsulosina-omnic-prezzo-79a8.pdf#regardless&quot;&gt;prix tamsulosine eg&lt;/a&gt;  The X-47B will never be put into operational use, but it will help Navy officials develop future carrier-based drones. Those drones could begin operating by 2020, according to Winter. Four companies are expected to compete for a contract to design the future unmanned aircraft, which will be awarded in Fiscal Year 2014.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.infocalcbba.edu.bo/biaxin-xl-side-effects-9e88.pdf&quot;&gt;biaxin cash price&lt;/a&gt;  “It’s been weird since the beginning of the season,” Cano said. “It’s the first time I’ve been without all those guys in the lineup. Now we’re going to the All-Star Game and it’s just Mo Rivera and I; we’re used to seeing Jeter, A-Rod, Teixeira. It’s been a tough year because you don’t have your guys.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://theglobalelite.org/letrozole-tablets-usp-25-mg-uses-69bc.pdf&quot;&gt;femara 2.5 mg oral tablet&lt;/a&gt;  Summary ratings by their peers ranged from 2.6 to 4.8. It turned out that low-skilled surgeons logged more postsurgical complications among patients, such as intestinal blockage, infection and blood clots.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
