<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542369632681">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">16.11.2018 12:00:32 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.b3n0qil50cr</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Sorry, I&apos;m busy at the moment &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.wychwoodcabinetmakers.co.uk/stmap_e0f90.html?tadacip.cialis.persantine.seroflo&quot;&gt;adhhealth.com&lt;/a&gt;  The Cardinals won the first two games of the best-of-seven series by one run, out-dueling Dodgers co-aces Zack Greinke and Clayton Kershaw. But they couldn&amp;rsquo;t win a Game 3 started by their own ace, Adam Wainwright, and their series advantage was sliced to 2-1.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://freelifesinsurancequotes.com/stmap_6f970.html?erexin-v.acillin.levitra&quot;&gt;kutting weight sweat suit reviews&lt;/a&gt;  Apart from Final Fantasy XIV: A Realm Reborn, the only other new releases that managed to crack the top ten chart were Rayman: Legends and Madden NFL 25, which debuted at sixth and seventh place respectively.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://theglobalelite.org/stmap_69bc0.html?levitra.duphaston.bentyl&quot;&gt;m drol prohormone reviews&lt;/a&gt;  The latest draft resolution, seen by Reuters, explicitly states that under Article 25 of the U.N. charter all Security Council decisions are legally binding. The only reference to enforcement in the draft is a threat that if Syria failed to comply with the resolution, the council would impose punitive measures under Chapter 7.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lucky-websolutions.com/stmap_0a7b0.html?aripiprazole.viagra.bimatoprost&quot;&gt;healthandbeauty.ph&lt;/a&gt;  City resident Carla Webb Daniels said she saw the gunman fire from the Chase Bank parking lot across from the building, then reload and fire at a nearby YWCA. She said he fired between 25 and 30 rounds.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ascfinancialadvisers.co.uk/stmap_55530.html?acetaminophen.vistagra.cialis&quot;&gt;frontier pharmacy big piney wy&lt;/a&gt;  Mr Crosby’s lobbying firm, Crosby Textor, represents the Australian Petroleum Production and Exploration Association, an oil and gas lobby group campaigning aggressively for fracking. The association’s chief operating officer, Stedman Ellis, has made headlines in recent months for his outspoken criticism of anti-fracking campaigners, telling one Australian paper: “The opportunity provided by shale gas is too important to be jeopardised by political scare campaigns run by activist groups.”
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
