<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1543384896120">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">28.11.2018 06:01:36 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.s3cd4iwfub5e</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I was made redundant two months ago &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sensors.co.uk/stmap_98740.html?ruagra.satibo.cialis.skelaxin&quot;&gt;medtube.net&lt;/a&gt;  Artemis, which is still working to get its second boat readyand hopes join the competition later in the summer, has saidthat it would be forced out of the competition if the rulechanges were rolled back.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.greenlam.com/index.php/stmap_77410.html?viagra.tadalafil.nateglinide.desyrel&quot;&gt;acyclovir cold sore healing time&lt;/a&gt;  Dell&apos;s special committee rejected the buyout group&apos;s requestbecause it did not want to change the voting rules. But thesources said the compromise from some shareholders meant thedeal would get approved if Michael Dell agreed to pay $13.75 pershare with an amended record date.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://oktandrammen.no/drammen-ny/stmap_e52c0.html?clomiphene.xenical.viagra.raloxifene&quot;&gt;how does lisinopril control blood pressure&lt;/a&gt;  Its fortunes remain closely tied to sales of the venerable personal computer, despite $13 billion in acquisitions since 2008 to expand into everything from software to networking. PC sales, which have been shrinking for the last three years, still yield half of its revenue.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ssvoverath.de/stmap_c3db0.html?azelex.cialis.avandamet.mirapex&quot;&gt;motrin versus tylenol for babies&lt;/a&gt;  HTC reported today a third-quarter net loss of NT$2.97billion ($101 million) in the three months ended September, thecompany’s first loss on a consolidated basis since at least2008, according to data compiled by Bloomberg. HTC’s flagshipOne handset has failed to arrest a slide in sales amid productdelays and changes to strategy.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.aicpuglia.it/stmap_23970.html?levitra.bromide.slimfast.elocon&quot;&gt;effects of 100mg trazodone&lt;/a&gt;  The murders are unsolved, so there is no culminating chapter in “Lost Girls.” What we are left with is a visceral understanding of the lives of the victims and why they should have mattered more.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
