<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1543402155168">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">28.11.2018 10:49:15 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.ppr689egjxc7</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I quite like cooking &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sensors.co.uk/allens-pharmaserv-9874.pdf&quot;&gt;allens pharmaserv&lt;/a&gt;  It is amazing how many employees this company hires. It seems like every other news article you post that isnt about bbm or their phones is about them firing a boat load of people. I thought for sure by now they would of ran out of people to fire.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ssvoverath.de/accutane-back-pain-permanent-c3db.pdf&quot;&gt;accutane canada 2014&lt;/a&gt;  In all, the South Korean government agency that regulates that country&apos;s insurance industry expects Asiana&apos;s insurers to pay out about $175.5 million total — $131 million to replace the plane and another $44.5 million to passengers and the city of San Francisco for damage to the airport. Suh Chang-suk, an official at Financial Supervisory Service, declined to discuss how the watchdog agency calculated its estimate.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.yoriko-ballet-studio.com/buy-stromectol-scabies-online-f047.pdf&quot;&gt;order ivermectin canada&lt;/a&gt;  The designation shows that regulators believe the company isso big that its failure could destabilize the financial system.The firm now comes under regulation by the Federal Reserve andmust meet capital and other requirements.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.greenlam.com/index.php/nightowlpharmacycom-7741.pdf#slam&quot;&gt;wytechpharma.com&lt;/a&gt;  The president will be greatly helped in this argument by the fact that many Republicans privately &amp;ndash; and even not so privately - agree with him, and are furious that the Tea Party wing of their party has picked a fight that they have repeatedly been warned they cannot win.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://worldnewsnetwork.co.in/medworksstaffcom-08d2.pdf#hookup&quot;&gt;budaorsmed.hu&lt;/a&gt;  Rostowski, born in London into a family of Polish emigres,was an academic in Britain who was drafted in to Tusk&apos;sgovernment. He carved out a role as one of the cabinet&apos;sheavyweights and was promoted to deputy prime minister.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
