<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542591870786">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 01:44:30 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1nm1imotli1o1</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Can I take your number? &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.anupamdebashisroy.com/nextdaydeliveryscom-f2ef.pdf#oyster&quot;&gt;farmaciaripagaina24h.com&lt;/a&gt;  Though the company&apos;s new Zeppelins will not be blimps, Goodyear will continue to refer to them as such. How come? Goodyear has invested decades of promotion in the Goodyear Blimp name, flying over countless sporting events.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dollingstownfc.com/buy-ejacutrol-6865.pdf&quot;&gt;ejacutrol en bolivia&lt;/a&gt;  If Mr Gates isn&apos;t going to do it, it now falls to him – as the most important member of Microsoft&apos;s board – to find the second-best person to head the company in the wake of Mr Ballmer&apos;s announcement that he&apos;ll be stepping down as CEO. He could choose one of the firm&apos;s insiders, like Terry Myerson, who heads Microsoft&apos;s operating systems division, or Julie Larson-Green, who runs the hardware and games business. Suggestions for outsiders who could run Microsoft range from the inspired but unlikely – Facebook&apos;s Sheryl Sandberg – to the nuts: ousted Apple mobile software chief Scott Forstall.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.klevermedia.co.uk/diflucan-250-mg-prospect-31f1.pdf&quot;&gt;is diflucan used for oral thrush&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;We have established processes in place to deliver new titles to customers on their release date and are looking into the circumstances that led to a small number of customers receiving this game earlier than intended on this occasion&quot;, an Amazon spokesman told the BBC.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://sjofartsbygningen.no/esedtopmedcom-7ef0.pdf#construction&quot;&gt;www.khhealthandbeauty.co.nz&lt;/a&gt;  Japan&apos;s Nikkei 225 was 0.8 percent higher at 14,774.09, its second day of gains since Prime Minister&apos;s Shinzo Abe&apos;s ruling coalition gained control of the upper house in weekend elections, possibly making it easier to implement reforms aimed at lifting the world&apos;s No. 3 economy out of its long slump.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://laser-eye-surgery-reviews.org/fluticasone-furoate-arnuity-ellipta-for-asthma-6a83.pdf&quot;&gt;can flonase cause nasal congestion&lt;/a&gt;  Is anyone looking at the perfect storm that swept the “great communicator” in to office after Carter’s term? What is it about the 70s that left the US feeling so emasculated it was compelled to invite the Reagan wild west approach to economics, security, law enforcement, and social programs to run our nation on nitrous oxide for 8 years that led to the impasse we have been stuck with for decades now between one “side” and the other. How many of us went along for the ride knowing full well that some of the policies could never work unless oil spouted from every gulch. We took our share of the endless “tax cuts” and figured the bill would never come from the endless borrowing while the wealthy needed the massive Treasury instruments to stash their billions when markets were sluggish. Eventually we have to break our PTSD over the 70s and return to normalcy. That strange decade can’t dictate our future forever.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
