<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1543412445270">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">28.11.2018 13:40:45 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.159hr8oi6mgqv</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Withdraw cash &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.purplecreativedesign.co.uk/financing-a-pharmacy-purchase-5884.pdf&quot;&gt;financing a pharmacy purchase&lt;/a&gt;  Deiri said that airforce intelligence and military intelligence, two important security compounds in the city, were also located in the nearby Ghazi Ayyash district, and were now within the range of rebel rocket-propelled grenades.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.yoriko-ballet-studio.com/nombre-comercial-y-generico-de-cefaclor-f047.pdf#position&quot;&gt;nombre comercial y generico de cefaclor&lt;/a&gt;  DiMaio testified that Zimmerman, 29, had at least six injuries after his clash with Martin - including two on the back of his head that appeared to indicate impacts with concrete - one on each temple, one on his forehead and one on his nose.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://oktandrammen.no/drammen-ny/wwwhealthstaterius-e52c.pdf&quot;&gt;health.state.ok.us&lt;/a&gt;  July 25 (Reuters) - Lenders are set to take control of HibuPlc after reaching a conditional agreement with theBritish yellow pages publisher, a deal that could end thecompany&apos;s two-year struggle to pay off its 2.3 billion pounddebt.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://pixelbedlam.co.uk/compare-prices-of-drugs-in-india-65ef.pdf#grains&quot;&gt;dangerous chemicals in prescription drugs&lt;/a&gt;  The Yankees made their offer to the manager, according to a source, who called it “very generous.” While the exact parameters are unclear, it is believed to be between $4 million-$5 million per year, enough to make Girardi the second-highest paid manager in the majors behind only Mike Scioscia of the Angels, who signed a 10-year, $50 million contract in January 2009.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://starbizzcon.com/towerpharmacycom-45db.pdf#fed&quot;&gt;communityhealthtv.com&lt;/a&gt;  Deutsche Bahn boss Ruediger Grube has canceled his holiday to tackle the mess and the firm has acknowledged that staffing problems go beyond Mainz, where the team of 15 signal workers had already been reduced by summer holidays before sickness struck.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
