<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542596294385">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 02:58:14 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1wnjxzoap7sv2</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>How many weeks&apos; holiday a year are there? &lt;a href=&quot;https://contactconsultoria.com/index.php/new-venture-pharmacy-total-eyewear-outlet-a511.pdf#muttered&quot;&gt;new venture pharmacy total eyewear outlet&lt;/a&gt;  Soriano clubbed his 17th homer in 52 games with the Yanks with a solo shot against reliever Guillermo Moscoso in the sixth. Soriano became the fifth player in MLB history to have at least 50 RBI with two different teams in the same season, joining Matt Holliday (2009), Manny Ramirez (2008), Carlos Beltran (2004) and David Justice (2000).
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.weymouthskatepark.co.uk/robert-riesenberg-md-atlanta-center-for-medical-research-6ae3.pdf#caricature&quot;&gt;atlanta center for medical research&lt;/a&gt;  Republican leaders plan to make remarks to reporters onThursday at 11 a.m. (1500 GMT) but it was uncertain whether theywould be prepared to unveil anything concrete then. The party&apos;sleadership has proven unable to control rebellious conservativesin the House, who have sufficient power to squelch any deal theydislike.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.elegantandwild.co.uk/medicalrepin-75b3.pdf&quot;&gt;medyemek.com&lt;/a&gt;  The statement doesn&amp;#39;t explicitly call for military action against Syria, which President Barack Obama has been lobbying for. But administration officials say the statement is an implicit endorsement because the U.S. is publicly discussing potential military strikes.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://paradiseinmexico.com.mx/dapsone-acne-reddit-c13c.pdf&quot;&gt;dapsone acne reddit&lt;/a&gt;  Western powers back the opposition but have been reluctant to fully commit to an Arab Sunni-backed revolt increasingly overtaken by Islamists linked to al Qaeda. Yet they have said the large-scale use of widely banned chemical weapons would be a game changer.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dollingstownfc.com/videovulgaris-medicalcom-6865.pdf&quot;&gt;sampoornhealthcare.com&lt;/a&gt;  Using the sun&amp;#8217;s rays, the lighting of the Olympic flame for the Winter Games in Sochi went off without a hitch in Greece on Sunday. It will be carried across Russia&amp;#8217;s nine time zones and even take a trip to space before the Games start.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
