<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542496951060">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">17.11.2018 23:22:31 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.683np3qqw2v9</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Directory enquiries &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.greenlamindustries.com/blog/nelsons-pharmacy-brownfield-0bae.pdf&quot;&gt;nelsons pharmacy brownfield&lt;/a&gt;  Federal prosecutors have launched a preliminary investigation into possible civil rights violations in the fatal shooting of an unarmed National Guardsman by an NYPD cop, the Daily News has learned.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.haroldwhitefuneraldirectors.co.uk/iqos-buy-dubai-bd82.pdf#disturb&quot;&gt;iqos buy online australia&lt;/a&gt;  The country&apos;s debt problems shot into the spotlight thismonth when its state oil firm Naftogaz narrowly escaped default-- not through lack of cash but because of action by aU.S.-based creditor which successfully petitioned a UK court toseize a bond coupon payment in lieu of an old $22 million debt.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.klevermedia.co.uk/mhp-amidren-burner-31f1.pdf&quot;&gt;mhp amidren burner&lt;/a&gt;  The MP also revealed he had been approached by senior Tories apparently seeking to recruit him to the party. He declined an invitation to meet Grant Shapps, saying he had no desire to defect to the party and that any meeting with the Tory chairman could be misinterpreted.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://leotoys.cl/expired-albuterol-inhaler-side-effects-2206.pdf&quot;&gt;albuterol sulfate pediatric dosage&lt;/a&gt;  By law, the cost-of-living adjustment is based on the Consumer Price Index for Urban Wage Earners and Clerical Workers, or CPI-W, a broad measure of consumer prices generated by the Bureau of Labor Statistics. It measures price changes for food, housing, clothing, transportation, energy, medical care, recreation and education.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.infocalcbba.edu.bo/flagyl-500-mg-in-iv-solutions-9e88.pdf&quot;&gt;flagyl treatment bv&lt;/a&gt;  The government took a nine percent stake in UBS as part ofthe bailout, which saw UBS receive a 6-billion-Swiss-franc shotin the arm. Switzerland sold the stake less than a year later ata 1.2 billion franc profit.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
