<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542357975005">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">16.11.2018 08:46:15 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.7q7za5nbydyo</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Do you like it here? &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.infocalcbba.edu.bo/stmap_9e880.html?viagra.cardizem.haridra&quot;&gt;foto gambir serawak&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;The U.S. shutdown is a central point for the markets, but as long as the hope for just a temporary shutdown exists, it will not be a strong burden for equities,&quot; Christian Stocker, equity strategist at UniCredit said.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://muv.asia/stmap_bf280.html?vigora.flagyl.vytorin.levitra&quot;&gt;awardmedals.com&lt;/a&gt;  Bulgaria, seeking to avoid legal action from Brussels, has increased the size of an officially protected area in the zone on the Black Sea coast, which is also crossed by pelicans, eagles, buzzards and cranes.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.artistparama.com/stmap_51680.html?viagra.maxalt.escitalopram&quot;&gt;divalproex medscape&lt;/a&gt;  Let there be no further assertions that Netanyahu is not really and truly interested in reaching a two-state deal. Placing his political capital on the line, he made clear that this Israeli government stands ready to endure pain in the interest of persuading the Palestinians to cease hostilities.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.greenlamindustries.com/blog/stmap_0bae0.html?cymbalta.olmesartan.viagra.abacavir&quot;&gt;vyvansesavings.com&lt;/a&gt;  After the Yankees dropped two of three games against the lowly Padres over the weekend, they arrived in Chicago and were greeted by the A-Rod circus. Hundreds of media types descended on U.S. Cellular Field to cover the Rodriguez story, a potential distraction that appeared to be one of the reasons Girardi decided to call the meeting.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.weymouthskatepark.co.uk/stmap_6ae30.html?nortriptyline.prograf.viagra&quot;&gt;test propionate masteron cycle&lt;/a&gt;  Oakland first baseman Brandon Moss was in the starting lineup against a left-hander for the first time since May 12 at Seattle, when Joe Saunders struck him out all three times he faced him. Moss was 0 for 2 with two strikeouts and a walk against Wilson, and is batting .185 with 29 strikeouts against lefties this season.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
