<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542370468603">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">16.11.2018 12:14:28 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.14mootiw00ngc</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Can you hear me OK? &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.md-interiors.co.uk/stmap_a6a40.html?minoxidil.norvir.alli.cialis&quot;&gt;airlinepilotforums.com&lt;/a&gt;  Netanyahu has had months to find a replacement for thehighly regarded Stanley Fischer, who announced in January thathe would step down at the end of June, two years early afterspending eight years in the job.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lovemycase.com/stmap_f2c20.html?cialis.silagra.mygra.tri-cyclen&quot;&gt;steroidthailand.com review&lt;/a&gt;  Though their main home will be the newly refurbished Kensington Palace, the royal couple are also expected to take up their country retreat Anmer Hall, on the Queen&amp;#039;s private Sandringham estate in Norfolk, later this year.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ipepalmas.com.br/stmap_7fc80.html?mexitil.levitra.malegra-fxt&quot;&gt;caverta online uk&lt;/a&gt;  The original Surface Pro, released last fall, started at $799. The Surface RT, which will continue to be sold along with the new models, will remain priced at $349 to start. Models with more memory cost more.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.artistparama.com/stmap_51680.html?zovirax.cycrin.cialis.purim&quot;&gt;cost of chemo drugs for dogs&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;LMAO Star Magazine!&quot; she wrote, calling out the gossip mag&apos;s claim. &quot;I don&apos;t know if you (doctored) the pics or (pick) the worst one you can find, but I&apos;m far from pregnant &amp; just dropped a jean size.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jalapaoecolodge.com.br/index.php/stmap_7abb0.html?viagra.fexofenadine.adefovir.penegra&quot;&gt;anavar price 2015&lt;/a&gt;  The second group claims, expansively, that its protest touches not just on energy but also on “health services, housing, education, food, transport and the freedom of movement”. Its members seem easily distracted: before going to Balcombe they were meant to set up at a power station in Nottinghamshire. At their site activists sat on bales of hay or lolled in the grass in the sun. “This is not a festival,” one protester reprimanded others, ordering them to clean up after their lunch.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
