<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542646695823">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 16:58:15 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.a2ph4w2log7x</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Recorded Delivery &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dollingstownfc.com/harga-xylocaine-gel-2-6865.pdf&quot;&gt;xylocaine sprey fiyat nedir&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;(The extrajudicial killings) make Muslims realize or sympathize with Al Shabaab because they see a Christian government killing Muslims and they sympathize with them,&quot; added Shariff, whose assets have been frozen by western powers.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.elegantandwild.co.uk/extreme-stamina-pdf-75b3.pdf#beach&quot;&gt;extreme stamina pdf free download&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;Consumers have very little to go on when trying to select a hospital for surgery, not knowing which ones do a good job at keeping surgery patients safe and which ones don&apos;t,&quot; says Lisa McGiffert, director of Consumers Union&apos;s Safe Patient Project. &quot;They might as well just throw a scalpel at a dartboard.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.klevermedia.co.uk/avokeittin-sisustus-31f1.pdf&quot;&gt;avokela siiman laitto&lt;/a&gt;  &amp;ldquo;He was a very brave defender who read the game well and whose team-mates described him as a real fighter who kept spirit in the team,&amp;rdquo; explained Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s football communications chief, Oleksandr Glyvynsky.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mikasafloors.com/24h-drugstorecom-bdec.pdf&quot;&gt;garudamed.com&lt;/a&gt;  This headline is misleading and a play to misrepresent the truth.  The fact is all premiums will be going up along with your annual deductibles (amount you pay before the insurance starts paying) and co-pays.  These are hidden costs to you until you need the insurance.  
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tarokasongbad.com/viagra-100mg-india-e3c4.pdf&quot;&gt;using generic viagra&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;This action by the Venezuelan government is clearly an effort to distract from its domestic problems and is not a serious way for a country to conduct its foreign policy,&quot; White House spokesman Jay Carney said.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
