<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542355803710">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">16.11.2018 08:10:03 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.61rlpk8zyeis</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>perfect design thanks &lt;a href=&quot;http://sjofartsbygningen.no/stmap_7ef00.html?levothroid.amiloride.tacrolimus.cialis&quot;&gt;deluxe vs original proextender&lt;/a&gt;  Not a chance, Comcast (or Time Warner or AT&amp;T). The Great Recession forced Americans to finally clue up to how awful and predatory all those media giants are (Comcast is GE/NBC-Universal). It&amp;#8217;s been a decade since Comcast has been able to NOT screw up customer accounts, fail to correct their mistakes &amp;#8211; even as they admit it is Comcast at fault, arbitrarily jack up services, as well as surreptitiously slap services not ordered onto billing that never gets fixed. That&amp;#8217;s why the customer retention is in the toilet. What a racket. More and more Americans are cutting the cable, opting for free over air broadcast channels and internet-only service for streaming &amp;#8211; often for free, as more devices are capable of all-in-one HD delivery. It isn&amp;#8217;t because people don&amp;#8217;t want cable tv, though most people I know simply refuse to pay for 250 channels wherein 230 are pure garbage, latino, religious, or shoutin&amp;#8217; head so-called news. It&amp;#8217;s also because they HATE the cable companies THAT much. Customers will hate them just as much when their security system gets screwed up in the same way&amp;#8230; with wayyy higher life issues at stake. Wait till Comcast makes a mistake and retaliates by flipping a switch and shutting down your cable phone/wi-fi service on which the security system works. Life&amp;#8217;s both too short and too precious to put your family into the hands of these corrupt corporate bozos. That&amp;#8217;s why they&amp;#8217;re trying to lock people into the same kind of 2-year contract the telcoms do on cell phone service. No thanks.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://zoeydeutch.net/stmap_8f080.html?cialis.glucovance.mentax&quot;&gt;harley clinic leeds&lt;/a&gt;  Rowhani replaced Mahmoud Ahmadinejad, who struck a hard-line approach when dealing with the West and its sanctions over Iran’s nuclear program. The sanctions have hit the country’s economy hard, decimating its vital oil exports and blocking transactions on international banking networks.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.greenlamindustries.com/blog/stmap_0bae0.html?proagra.viagra.avana&quot;&gt;thuc aldactone tab 25mg&lt;/a&gt;  Ofsted says the consultation revealed that the &quot;overwhelmingly strong opinion&quot; of parents and carers was that two years was too long to wait for improvements in education provision for very young children.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://zoeydeutch.net/stmap_8f080.html?pristiq.acarbose.viagra.plavix&quot;&gt;ocon medical iub&lt;/a&gt;  A year on and the woman is Witness B, giving evidence usedto arrest Mihaloliakos and five fellow Golden Dawn lawmakers.They have been charged with belonging to a criminal organisationinvolved in many offences including the stabbing last month of aleft-wing rap artist whose death has infuriated the government.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://laser-eye-surgery-reviews.org/stmap_6a830.html?arimidex.cialis.claritin.fulvicin&quot;&gt;online pharmacy tracker&lt;/a&gt;  ** Cisco Systems Inc said it would buy softwaremaker Sourcefire Inc for about $2.7 billion to increaseits network security services. Cisco will pay $76 per share forthe company, which represents a premium of 28.6 percent to thestock&apos;s closing price of $59.08 on Monday.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
