<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542646224633">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 16:50:24 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.sd501rl5symn</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Who would I report to? &lt;a href=&quot;https://paradiseinmexico.com.mx/buy-real-anavar-steroids-c13c.pdf&quot;&gt;low dose test with anavar&lt;/a&gt;  The budget deficit is dropping. Projections by the Congressional Budget Office show a $642 billion shortfall this year, less than half of the $1.3 trillion shortfall Obama inherited from Bush. It&amp;#8217;s forecast to drop to $560 billion next year and $378 billion in 2015. Already the deficit has fallen from its peak of 10.2% of GDP in 2009 to about 4% this year.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://muv.asia/generic-pills-onlinenet-review-bf28.pdf&quot;&gt;generic-pills-online.net review&lt;/a&gt;  Demand for the iPhone 5S has exceeded initial supply and many online orders are scheduled to be shipped in the coming weeks, Apple said. On Friday, long lines formed outside stores in Tokyo, New York, San Francisco and other cities for the new top-of-the-line 5s and the less-expensive 5c. It was the first time Apple launched two iPhone models simultaneously.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://muv.asia/clobetasol-shampoo-preise-bf28.pdf&quot;&gt;donde comprar clobetasol propionato&lt;/a&gt;  All humans want to be connected, Zuckerberg concluded. And with a glint in his eye about his own purpose on this planet and that of his company, Zuckerberg exclaimed, &amp;#8220;That&amp;#8217;s why we&amp;#8217;re here.&amp;#8221;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://globalelite.tv/chronicpaintalksmedicinecom-b1c8.pdf&quot;&gt;menshealthadvices.com&lt;/a&gt;  The wild card in Sunday&apos;s election is the Alternative forGermany (AfD), a seven-month-old party that has seized on voterfears about the cost of euro zone bailouts, for which Germany,Europe&apos;s largest economy, underwrites the biggest share.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.anupamdebashisroy.com/vilameduslt-f2ef.pdf#tedious&quot;&gt;serksnomedus.lt&lt;/a&gt;  The head of VW&apos;s global works council, Bernd Osterloh, told Reuters the current debate was &quot;absolutely unacceptable&quot; and there were &quot;clear signs&quot; the UAW has the support of many employees in Tennessee to discuss some sort of representation.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
