<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542570620955">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 19:50:20 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.11jfmcfx3l73f</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I&apos;m unemployed &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dollingstownfc.com/foodasmedicinecounselingcom-6865.pdf#step&quot;&gt;recentre-health.co.uk&lt;/a&gt;  One would ban possession of any ammunition clip that holds more than 10 rounds, and the other bans people with multiple drug and alcohol convictions and convictions for gang-related crimes from owning a firearm for 10 years.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.layeredonline.com/buy-vermox-australia-dd54.pdf&quot;&gt;vermox tablets australia&lt;/a&gt;  Country singer Kenny Chesney has defended the reputation of his fans after American football player Riley Cooper was filmed using racist language at one of his recent concerts. The Philadelphia Eagles star was at the centre of a Twitter.com storm on Wednesday (31Aug13) when video footage of him using the N-word at Chesney&apos;s gig in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania in June (13) went viral. Caught on camera, an angry Cooper, who appears to embroiled in an argument at the show, can be heard ranting, &quot;I will jump that fence and fight every (N-word) here, bro.&quot; Chesney has now distanced himself from Cooper&apos;s behaviour, insisting his fans and the football community should not be tarnished because of the language used by one man. He tells ESPN, &quot;I&apos;m as shocked as anyone to see the video of Riley Cooper that&apos;s started circulating on the Internet. I don&apos;t believe in discrimination in any form, and I think using language like that is not only unacceptable, it is hateful beyond words. &quot;To judge an entire audience by one loud mouth isn&apos;t fair... not to the NFL (National Football League), not to the city of Philadelphia and that awesome crowd, not to my band and crew and certainly not to me, who believes music is about bringing people together for friendship and forgetting about the things in life that bring you down. The music I make is about living life, loving life and loving everybody - no matter who they are. That&apos;s how I was raised, and what someone else does or says doesn&apos;t reflect who I am or what my fans stand for.&quot; Cooper has since released an apology, saying, &quot;I am so ashamed and disgusted with myself. I want to apologise. I owe an apology to the fans and to this community. I am so ashamed, but there are no excuses. What I did was wrong and I will accept the consequences.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.artistparama.com/extagen-sold-in-stores-5168.pdf#breadth&quot;&gt;extagen gnc&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;I have to spread the word. ... After my sentence we thought, &apos;How can it get worse?&quot;&apos;  Dalelv told The Associated Press in an interview at a Norwegian aid compound in Dubai where she is preparing her appeal scheduled for early September.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sarah-hyland.net/hidrate-spark-target-79a8.pdf&quot;&gt;hidrate spark 2.0 target&lt;/a&gt;  Hudson won his fourth straight start, striking out nine in 7 2-3 innings â his most since fanning 10 Mets on June 17, 2011. Luis Avilan replaced him and gave up a two-run double to Daniel Murphy, who made two errors at second base.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sarah-hyland.net/mega-man-rxi-79a8.pdf&quot;&gt;mega man rxi&lt;/a&gt;  It has been the wettest July ever recorded in the U.S. island territory, with 14 inches (36 centimeters) so far drenching the capital. More rain fell on July 18 than had ever come down in a 24-hour period.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
