<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542670200531">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 23:30:00 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1shmmb731dwth</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I have my own business &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.haroldwhitefuneraldirectors.co.uk/senna-alexandrina-benefits-bd82.pdf#carriage&quot;&gt;senna alexandrina tea&lt;/a&gt;  Martina Hingis, a 32-year-old retired tennis star, is set to enter the World Tennis Hall of Fame today, although many will be talking about her alleged infidelity, unfortunately, rather than her long list of accomplishments.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.anupamdebashisroy.com/comprar-aceite-neem-f2ef.pdf#swallow&quot;&gt;olio di neem per piante dove comprarlo&lt;/a&gt;  The biggest cloud on Twitter&amp;rsquo;s horizon, according to analysts, is the relatively sluggish growth of its user base. While more than half of Britons and Americans use Facebook, Twitter, with its focus on news and real time updates, is by comparison a niche product.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.weymouthskatepark.co.uk/acquistare-cialis-in-germania-6ae3.pdf&quot;&gt;si pu comprare il cialis generico in farmacia&lt;/a&gt;  One of the banned films is &quot;L&apos;Inconnu du Lac&quot; (Stranger by the Lake) from French director Alain Guiraudie, which deals with a homosexual relationship between two men. It was screened this year at Cannes Film Festival.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://reflectiveteens.com/seroquel-xr-200-mg-high-213a.pdf&quot;&gt;seroquel xr 200 mg forum&lt;/a&gt;  An extremely controversial video capturing two men being aggressively stopped and frisked on the streets of Philadelphia by police for allegedly saying hi to a stranger has led to an investigation by their department.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ecorporationbd.com/prostanew-prescription-aaa8.pdf#cross&quot;&gt;order cheap prostanew&lt;/a&gt;  Excellent point. Some small government advocates even describe themselves as &amp;#8220;anti-government&amp;#8221; a term I dislike. I think we should describe ourselves as extremely pro-government. If a friend was deep in debt I would advise them to reduce spending, not because I&amp;#8217;m anti-friend, but because I&amp;#8217;m pro-friend. It&amp;#8217;s the same with government. I want a strong, effective, low cost government with little or preferably no debt.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
