<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542352472526">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">16.11.2018 07:14:32 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1my81ft2taaz3</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I&apos;d like to apply for this job &lt;a href=&quot;http://reflectiveteens.com/stmap_213a0.html?flagyl.levitra.satibo.mexitil&quot;&gt;hra pharma uk ltd&lt;/a&gt;  A small number of posts with so-called &quot;must kill&quot; words such as references to the banned spiritual group Falun Gong are first blocked and then manually deleted. Censors also have to update lists of sensitive words with new references and creative expressions bloggers use to evade scrutiny.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://virtual-operations.com/stmap_92e20.html?neggram.finast.indomethacin.levitra&quot;&gt;gbyuksupplements.co.uk&lt;/a&gt;  * The government won&apos;t back down on allowing large foreigncompanies into Canada&apos;s wireless market, says Prime MinisterStephen Harper, adding that he is more interested in promotingcompetition than in protecting the big domestic telecomcompanies. ()
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.wychwoodcabinetmakers.co.uk/stmap_e0f90.html?viagra.doxycycline.fincar.trecator-sc&quot;&gt;reviews for xytomax&lt;/a&gt;  The decision coincides with heightened ethnic and religious tension in Malaysia after a polarizing May election, in which the long-ruling coalition was deserted by urban voters that included a large section of minority ethnic Chinese.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.weymouthskatepark.co.uk/stmap_6ae30.html?erythromycin.tri-cyclen.viagra&quot;&gt;metoprolol atenolol dose equivalence&lt;/a&gt;  &amp;#8220;I don&amp;#8217;t have a scheduling announcement for you today, but obviously this is not a positive development. And we have a wide range of interests with the Russians, and we are evaluating the utility of a summit,&amp;#8221; Carney said.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://virtual-operations.com/stmap_92e20.html?analgin.cialis.duratia&quot;&gt;delano regional medical center pharmacy&lt;/a&gt;  Your flag will not be visible to anyone but moderators. Please select the reason you are flagging this content: spam, trolling or just inappropriate. Then write us a short note explaining why you flagged it that way.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
