<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542727549995">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">20.11.2018 15:25:49 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1b17e8l4itt1d</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Yes, I love it! &lt;a href=&quot;http://lemcasesorias.com/index.php/buy-legal-drugs-sydney-83f5.pdf#pantomime&quot;&gt;beryl drugs share price&lt;/a&gt;  Many leaders in that region and their Western masters will fall before Assad. Qatar&amp;#8217;s Emir and the Prime minister have been deposed. Mursi who called Jihad against Syria is gone. Erdogan is wobbling. Hillary Clinton gone. David Patreus gone. Zio-puppet Sarkozy gone. I saw Syria winning the battle against regime-change since the beginning. There are few countries on this planet that could withstand the kind of onslaught unleashed against Syria by the coalition of the willing aggressors. Usually after suffering the kind of attacks Syria suffered most governments fall within two to three months. Billions have been spent on this operation. We need to also remember that Syria has been DIRECTLY attacked by the US, Israel, Britain, France, Turkey, Saud arabia, Qatar, Jordan, Lybia and INDIRECTLY by dozens of Jihadist groups from 30 different countries.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tarokasongbad.com/clarithromycin-generic-pharmacy-e3c4.pdf#flood&quot;&gt;will macrobid treat a urinary tract infection&lt;/a&gt;  Thatâs exactly what the Pentagon is doing with some 2,000 of the massive eight-ton troop carriers known as MRAPS. Each MRAP cost taxpayers more than $1 million, but with 24,000 already in the Army inventory, officials decided it was more cost effective to scrap 2,000 of the vehicles in Afghanistan rather than bring them home. 
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.klevermedia.co.uk/signature-pharmacy-winter-park-31f1.pdf#comfort&quot;&gt;signature pharmacy in orlando florida&lt;/a&gt;  The pilot in charge of the plane told the NTSB that he was relying on the throttle control to keep the plane at its proper speed and failed to recognize that the aircraft had slowed dramatically as it approached the runway, Hersman had said on Tuesday. The slow speed was a key cause of the crash.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.md-interiors.co.uk/priceline-pharmacy-bracken-ridge-opening-hours-a6a4.pdf#desert&quot;&gt;online drugstore europe&lt;/a&gt;  The potential Summers nomination was a hot-button issue forliberal groups for much of the past few months, most of whomraised concerns about his support of deregulatory measures forthe banking industry during his time in President Bill Clintonâsadministration.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mcmpovos.com/stim-u-sensitive-skin-62bd.pdf#pleased&quot;&gt;stim u sensorielle&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;DNA and other investigations will confirm their identities. We have also recovered four AK47 assault rifles which we know were used by the terrorists in the assault. We also recovered 11 magazines of AK47 assault rifles.&quot;
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
