<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1543414137566">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">28.11.2018 14:08:57 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1d0th3fd2y6q5</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I&apos;m originally from Dublin but now live in Edinburgh &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.aicpuglia.it/pharmacy-chevalier-miami-2397.pdf&quot;&gt;pharmacy chevalier miami&lt;/a&gt;  The global battle for mobile supremacy is not just betweenApple and Samsung. Huawei and ZTE Corp aregrowing across their Chinese home base, and South Korea&apos;s LGElectronics said on Wednesday it sold a record 12.1million smartphones in April-June, more than double its year-agosales.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.purplecreativedesign.co.uk/desconto-do-zoloft-5884.pdf&quot;&gt;desconto do zoloft&lt;/a&gt;  In a court martial that stretched over two months, military prosecutors argued that Manning became a &quot;traitor&quot; to his country when he handed over to the anti-secrecy website a trove of 700,000 battlefield videos, diplomatic cables and other classified files.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://oktandrammen.no/drammen-ny/slenderiiz-program-review-e52c.pdf#cable&quot;&gt;slenderiiz drops uk&lt;/a&gt;  For Libyans with years of pent up anger, Saif al-Islam and former spy chief Abdallah al-Senussi, in a Tripoli jail, are the most important faces of the Gaddafi government they can hold accountable for 42 years of dictatorship.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://oktandrammen.no/drammen-ny/buy-viagra-from-china-e52c.pdf#glacier&quot;&gt;pfizer viagra price 100mg&lt;/a&gt;  Syria&apos;s ally Russia and the United States continue to disagree sharply on how to end the war, with Moscow blaming the rebels for chemical attacks and blocking peace talks, and Western powers blaming Syrian President Bashar al-Assad.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.brentwood-karting.com/index.php/proti-farm-ermelo-6e56.pdf#phone&quot;&gt;proti farm holding&lt;/a&gt;  It emerged that an extra 17 minutes of exercise for boys and 12 minutes for girls at the age of 11 &amp;ndash; beyond the current average for the age group &amp;ndash; could boost children&amp;rsquo;s results by the age of 16.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
