<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542518502397">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 05:21:42 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.2q85uhh884ke</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Is this a temporary or permanent position? &lt;a href=&quot;http://lemcasesorias.com/index.php/desogen-medscape-83f5.pdf#venus&quot;&gt;desogen medscape&lt;/a&gt;  The town&apos;s namesake lake, a deep blue expanse of water thatis close to two provincial parks, and nearby mountains coveredwith dark pine and birch trees, attract hundreds of thousands ofvisitors a year. Very little oil from the wrecked tanker carsmade it into the lake.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://virtual-operations.com/himalaya-liv-52-ds-benefits-92e2.pdf&quot;&gt;himalaya liv 52 ds benefits&lt;/a&gt;  The inquiry revealed an &quot;incredible inability&quot; for different organizations to work together and share information, Lozach said. &quot;The anti-doping fight would be a lot more effective if the different actors in sports, law enforcement and justice cooperated.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://sjofartsbygningen.no/us-pharmacy-discount-card-reviews-7ef0.pdf#alexis&quot;&gt;online pharmacy yahoo&lt;/a&gt;  Sandy - I could not agree more! This is my 2nd day going to my federal job without pay. We were warned several times if we take any leave - vacation or sick - we would be handed a furlough notice &amp; not allowed back until we are called back. That sat fine by me (if I&apos;m not getting paid, then yeah; I wouldn&apos;t mind being home) until we were cautioned a gazillion times that we would be classified as AWOL &amp; the consequences would be determined at a later time. I had scheduled medical tmrw &amp; Friday and HAVE to give them my decision of rescinding my leave. If it were my child, my decision would be an easy one. So I&apos;m worried about that. Plus, our household income will be cut in half since my spouse &amp; I make the same. Last time I was on a furlough during the Clinton presidency, it was for a couple of days (maybe 3-4?) but if messed up our pay &amp; I didn&apos;t see the $ until January. At that time, I still lived at home so I wasn&apos;t overly concerned. Now I&apos;m also worrying abt our health insurance since it&apos;s carried under me. We were advised this shutdown may last a few weeks to a month. So while we are working &amp; serving the public, we can&apos;t help but laugh at the emails from the White House thanking us for our &quot;hard work &amp; continued dedication&quot; while they&apos;re not missing their pay. We even got an email titled &quot;Happy New Fiscal &apos;14 New Year!&quot; Are you f&apos;ing kidding me?? Both sides are liars as far as I&apos;m concerned. And for people who complain, I certainly hope they vote and actively participate in writing/calling their Congressman for changes. I was surprised to find out how many people do not do this. Hoping to hear about a resolution soon (but not exactly holding my breath!)
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://muv.asia/ams-1-andro-liquid-stacking-bf28.pdf&quot;&gt;1 androsterone reviews&lt;/a&gt;  Arthritis is an unpredictable disease and treatment can be difficult. The approach and success will vary according to the type of arthritis being treated. There is no known cure for arthritis, so treatment is aimed at reducing joint pain and inflammation, improving joint function and preventing progression of the disease. This is achieved through a combination of lifestyle factors and drug therapy.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://archieandtherug.com/hempmeds-mexico-9392.pdf#shape&quot;&gt;hempmeds mexico&lt;/a&gt;  She said lower input costs and efficiency gains had helpedto lift the operating margin by 20 basis points to 15.1 percentdespite the modest underlying sales growth, but said she didn&apos;tsee a further improvement in the margin in the second half.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
