<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542666776663">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 22:32:56 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1ewtp5zcfjn1k</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Get a job &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mikasafloors.com/flagyl-750-mg-tid-bdec.pdf&quot;&gt;buy flagyl metronidazole 500mg&lt;/a&gt;  Contact between nurses and patients in hospitals was often &amp;ldquo;functional&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;perfunctory&amp;rdquo;, with staff admitting they felt they neglected those in their final days because of large workloads and lack of staff.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mcmpovos.com/prescription-drugs-information-australia-62bd.pdf&quot;&gt;purchase profit pharmacy&lt;/a&gt;  At a public event in Cumbria in Northwest England today, it was a young child asking the tough questions. In a video, the child can be heard asking Queen Elizabeth, &amp;#8220;Do you want Kate&amp;#8217;s baby to be a boy or girl?&amp;#8221;
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://accentresurfacing.com/horse-power-armor-location-4110.pdf&quot;&gt;horse power armor location&lt;/a&gt;  The yellow fever mosquito, also known as Aedes aegypti, was found this week at Holy Cross cemetery in a residential area of Menlo Park, according to Robyn Thaw, a spokesperson for the San Mateo County Health System.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://archieandtherug.com/pinkmedicocom-9392.pdf&quot;&gt;healthtips101.com&lt;/a&gt;  The defense team claimed that using the restraint is analogous to hitching an animal to the floor. That got a quick response from Judge Carlos Samour, who said the defense motion, &amp;#8220;while high on rhetoric, is low in substance.&amp;#8221;
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.artistparama.com/side-effects-of-otc-or-prescription-drugs-5168.pdf#bite&quot;&gt;role of generic drugs&lt;/a&gt;  At a conference in 1989, Valentich-Scott and Ó Foighil were chatting about new discoveries when they realized they had each discovered what they then suspected was a new species of clam, at the same time, but more than 1,000 miles apart. Neither scientist could identify the creature.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
