<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542372470977">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">16.11.2018 12:47:50 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1e4hgv2xv1qxx</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I quite like cooking &lt;a href=&quot;https://freelifesinsurancequotes.com/stmap_6f970.html?midamor.hindgra.naproxen.viagra&quot;&gt;buy erectalis uk&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;I used to throw for 345 days a year because I felt like you couldn&apos;t duplicate those days you missed,&quot; he said. &quot;Every day you missed, I felt like I needed seven straight days to get back. I don&apos;t know that you can ever get that back. Saying that, I did everything I could to get myself ready to go.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://digital-matchbox.com/stmap_55220.html?valproic.avalide.cialis&quot;&gt;aanandihealth.com&lt;/a&gt;  What does the future hold for annuity buyers? One the one hand, rates have improved dramatically in recent months; on the other there are fears that the Bank of England will keep a tight lid on interest rates, which could mean that annuity rates will struggle to go any higher &amp;ndash; or could even start falling again.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ipepalmas.com.br/stmap_7fc80.html?sleepwell.theophylline.cialis&quot;&gt;was ist tadalista&lt;/a&gt;  The loss of photosensitive cells, the rods and cones of the retina, is a leading cause of sight loss in a number of degenerative eye diseases, such as age-related macular degeneration, retinitis pigmentosa and diabetes-related blindness.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.md-interiors.co.uk/stmap_a6a40.html?levitra.cipralex.mellaril.vistagra&quot;&gt;average cost of renovating a 2 bedroom house&lt;/a&gt;  The following day, however, Filner went on the offensive, hiring a lawyer and saying he would not resign. He claimed the facts would vindicate him. Six of nine members of the City Council have asked him to resign to prevent the city from additional embarrassment and financial exposure. 
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.elegantandwild.co.uk/stmap_75b30.html?viramune.cialis.ruagra.arjuna&quot;&gt;use of febrex plus syrup&lt;/a&gt;  Officials didn&apos;t explain fully why the plane approached the notoriously difficult landing strip too low and slow, likely causing the crash, although they did quote testimony from one of the pilots that explained more about what occurred moments before Flight 214 crash landed.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
