<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542388718931">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">16.11.2018 17:18:38 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.12sg6jgqvqija</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I&apos;m doing a phd in chemistry &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.anupamdebashisroy.com/stmap_f2ef0.html?raloxifene.levitra.budesonide.avandia&quot;&gt;glucophage 500 mg weight loss&lt;/a&gt;  (The following statement was released by the rating agency)NEW YORK, September 17 (Fitch) Fitch Ratings has affirmed itsratings on WellPoint, Inc. (WLP) including the &apos;BBB &apos; ratings on thecompany&apos;s senior unsecured notes and the &apos;AA-&apos; Insurer Financial Strength (IFS)ratings assigned to various WellPoint insurance company subsidiaries. The RatingOutlook for WLP and its subsidiaries remains Negative. KEY RATING DRIVERS Large Market Position Size/Scale: Under Fitch&apos;s Insurance RatingMethodology, WellPoint Inc.&apos;s (WLP) market position and size/scalecharacteristics are considered &apos;large&apos; reflecting the company&apos;s leading market sharein 14 states and significant scale benefits and operating efficienciesderived from its 36 million membership base and estimated $70 billion in annualrevenues. Fitch believes that WLP&apos;s strong competitive position is directlylinked to the company&apos;s right to use the Blue Cross and/or Blue Shield namesand marks in 14 states. Stable Operating Performance: WLP consistently produces largeamounts of absolute earnings and strong and stable EBITDA-based revenuemargins and net returns on average capital (ROAC) that are consistent withFitch&apos;s guidelines for the company&apos;s current ratings. From 2010 through 2012 thecompany generated average annual EBITDA of $5.2 billion and EBITDA-based marginsand net ROAC of 8.7% and 8.4% respectively. Fitch notes however, that from 2010to 2012, WLP&apos;s EBITDA and net income declined modestly reflecting tepid revenuegrowth and higher medical benefit ratios. The company&apos;s financial results through the first six months of2013 were generally consistent with its longer-term results. WLP reported$3.2 billion of EBITDA and an EBITDA-based revenue margin and net ROAC of 9.1%and 8.8% respectively. Fitch expects WLP and its peers to experience a modest, gradualdecline in operating margins as the Affordable Care Act (ACA) isimplemented and a growing portion of the company&apos;s revenues are derived from lower margingovernment business, particularly Medicaid. From an overall earningsperspective, Fitch expects the impact of these declining margins to be somewhatoffset by ACA related membership growth, particularly in the Medicaid market.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
