<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542639101849">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 14:51:41 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.mji1v0cqcaql</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I stay at home and look after the children &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mikasafloors.com/allencountyhealthcom-bdec.pdf&quot;&gt;bluewavemedicine.com&lt;/a&gt;  Algiers became a battleground between the FLN and the parachutists, with French soldiers ordered to participate in round-ups, interrogations and torture. Saint Marc was Massu&amp;rsquo;s liaison with the press. As questions mounted about the brutality of his methods, Massu pursued the operation remorselessly, pressing through the Casbah until French forces had regained total control. Saint Marc&amp;rsquo;s strategy with journalists was simple: &amp;ldquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t reveal everything, but don&amp;rsquo;t lie.&amp;rdquo;
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cabanadolago.com.br/index.php/natural-max-slimming-capsule-red-amazon-ab8a.pdf&quot;&gt;red natural max slimming capsule side effects&lt;/a&gt;  OAKLAND &amp;mdash; The high-risk sex offender named as a person of interest in the killing of federal defense investigator Sandra Coke had been ordered to stay away from her as a condition of his parole, a judge said Friday.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://theglobalelite.org/rocklandpharmacycom-69bc.pdf&quot;&gt;medby.de&lt;/a&gt;  City Council Speaker Christine Quinn (right) with wife Kim Catullo (left) marching during the 42nd Annual LGBT Pride March in June. The candidate hasn&amp;#39;t gotten a lot of financial help from a lesbian lobbyist group.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://freelifesinsurancequotes.com/cheap-pharmacy-in-dundrum-6f97.pdf#ardour&quot;&gt;arizona pharmacy prescription monitoring&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;There is now a consistent pattern of Speaker Boehner sayingthings that fly in the face of the facts or stand at odds withhis past actions,&quot; Jentleson said. &quot;Americans across the countryare suffering because Speaker Boehner refuses to come to gripswith reality.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lucky-websolutions.com/warfarin-side-effects-drugscom-0a7b.pdf#joyful&quot;&gt;warfarin side effects drugs.com&lt;/a&gt;  Defence Secretary Philip Hammond said hundreds of part-time specialists would be placed across the armed forces in order to protect the UK from online attacks and even launch their own “strikes in cyber space”.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
