<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542546116691">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 13:01:56 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.g0oz73xb93hp</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I don&apos;t like pubs &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tarokasongbad.com/caterpillarcom-production-jobs-e3c4.pdf#frolic&quot;&gt;caterpillar.com production jobs&lt;/a&gt;  Overstretched staff are toiling at a more intense rate than they were a year according to new research from recruiter Randstad, with less than one in three reporting the same level of pressure last year.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://archieandtherug.com/senior-care-pharmacy-topeka-ks-9392.pdf#seventeen&quot;&gt;senior care pharmacy northport al jobs&lt;/a&gt;  Trouble between the two companies began in 2010 when Motorola asked Microsoft to start paying royalties for Motorola technology contributed to the H.264 video compression standard and 802.11 wireless networking standard. The former has become the de facto standard for streaming video while the latter underlies the Wi-Fi technology used in most gadgets today.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.haroldwhitefuneraldirectors.co.uk/walmart-beta-sitosterol-bd82.pdf&quot;&gt;beta sitosterol 40%&lt;/a&gt;  The latest polling is bolstering their concerns. In the latest survey, by the Washington Post and ABC News, 70 percent disapproved of the way Republicans in Congress are handling the conflict versus 61 percent who disapproved of congressional Democrats.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://muv.asia/apricot-power-b17amygdalin-500mg-tablets-bf28.pdf#sharp&quot;&gt;apricot power b17/amygdalin 500mg tablets&lt;/a&gt;  But the real identity of Galbraith was revealed at the weekend after the Sunday Times newspaper received a set of anonymous tweets alleging Rowling was the author and its staff turned detective to match up the use of language and realize that the same literary agent was involved.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.artistparama.com/grupo-orexis-5168.pdf&quot;&gt;what does orexis mean&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;So, someone with type-2 diabetes most likely won&amp;#039;t require frequent tests as their condition will be controlled in other ways such as through diet, whereas those with type-1 will need the strips much more often, therefore these patients&amp;#039; access to strips will most likely not be restricted.&quot;
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
