<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542543222225">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 12:13:42 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1ui15xx0efdz</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Yes, I play the guitar &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.klevermedia.co.uk/cialis-20mg-billiger-31f1.pdf&quot;&gt;achat cialis france 24&lt;/a&gt;  At the end of its conveyor belt, the device spits out pellets made from cellulose fibers, which are found in many discarded items, like baby wipes or fruits and vegetables, said chief executive Refael Aharon.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.proguaru.com.br/amcfollowmyhealthcom-7684.pdf#stitch&quot;&gt;eamedspa.com&lt;/a&gt;  the reason the background check legislation was defeated was, 4 additional pages were added by the anti gun crowd at the end; which even made the moderates vote against it, since it made just about everything a person with a firearm in their home a criminal offense.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.chris-cancercommunity.com/ergoprene-gel-b01a.pdf#fifth&quot;&gt;allsop 30191 ergoprene gel mouse pad with wrist rest black&lt;/a&gt;  Arkansas was also an important stop for Griffin because Sen. Mark Pryor (D-Ark.) is one of three Senate Democrats who have yet to sign on in support of ENDA. Griffin emphasized poll numbers showing 61 percent of Arkansas resident support a transgender-inclusive federal law protecting workers against discrimination.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://paradiseinmexico.com.mx/myhealthysupplementcom-c13c.pdf#matter&quot;&gt;dokimospharmacy.com&lt;/a&gt;  At the same time, think about the financial protection your spouse would need if you died. In particular, if you both worked for a living and are each collecting Social Security, what would happen to those payments if you died? Consider getting a life insurance policy for your older years to help replace the Social Security benefits your spouse would lose when you die.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cabanadolago.com.br/index.php/wwwgib-pharmade-ab8a.pdf&quot;&gt;challans-medical.fr&lt;/a&gt;  Under Prime Minister Tayyip Erdogan, elected in 2002, therole of the Turkish military in politics has been curbed.Political and military relations between Ankara and Washington,while still close, play a less central role, and this could bereflected in procurement policy.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
