<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542548966661">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 13:49:26 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.155xrprjzrfmj</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>How many weeks&apos; holiday a year are there? &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.artistparama.com/wwwpilloleorg-il-manuale-di-clinica-pratica-5168.pdf#premises&quot;&gt;www.pillole.org il manuale di clinica pratica&lt;/a&gt;  He added: &quot;It&amp;#39;s striking that while Lynton Crosby has specifically denied discussing tobacco with the Prime Minister, he has said nothing about alcohol policy, or any of the other policy areas where his reported clients have interests.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mikasafloors.com/costco-pharmacy-vaccines-bdec.pdf&quot;&gt;myths about abusing prescription drugs&lt;/a&gt;  Maxwell, who was in New Orleans for the 19th annual Essence Festival last weekend, was thinking specifically about his native East New York, where the 75th Precinct had the second highest number of stop-and-frisks in the city in 2012.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.layeredonline.com/amoxicillin-ratiopharm-250-mg-5-ml-ts-beipackzettel-dd54.pdf#briefly&quot;&gt;amoxicillin ratiopharm 250 mg 5 ml ts beipackzettel&lt;/a&gt;  Crupi, who worked with Madoff for several decades, claims she knew nothing about his scheme, which stole $19 billion from investors, including Hollywood celebrities like Steven Spielberg, John Malkovich and Kevin Bacon.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://reflectiveteens.com/prednisone-5mg-dosage-for-dogs-213a.pdf#elated&quot;&gt;methylprednisolone vs prednisone&lt;/a&gt;  Berlusconi has kept his party hawks on a tight leash for months, saying the government must continue. Political sources say this stance was influenced by his lawyers, keen to avoid upsetting the supreme court judges. The mercurial magnate&apos;s reaction if he is found guilty is uncertain.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.haroldwhitefuneraldirectors.co.uk/petmartpharmacycom-bd82.pdf&quot;&gt;petmartpharmacy.com&lt;/a&gt;  &amp;#8220;Today in Britain, it seems more acceptable to say you want an abortion because you don&amp;#8217;t want to be pregnant than to say you want an abortion because you don&amp;#8217;t want to be pregnant with a girl. Not wanting a baby because it&amp;#8217;s a girl &amp;#8211; whereas you would like a baby boy &amp;#8211; seems discriminatory, unethical, &amp;#8216;consumerist&amp;#8217; even.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
