<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1543278473799">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">27.11.2018 00:27:53 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1b93ba6cr9nl3</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>What do you like doing in your spare time? &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.aicpuglia.it/stmap_23970.html?vaseretic.potassium.cialis.levlen&quot;&gt;gaia maca root pills reviews&lt;/a&gt;  They are right to recognise that Games-time is not a time when visitors to the World Cup or Olympics will head south of Brazil for a holiday. A few people may take the opportunity to extend their stay while in the region, but as ticket holders for the Olympics and World Cup will largely be Brazilian, this doesn&amp;rsquo;t offer a big opportunity for Argentina. I am also unconvinced that they will receive an influx of visitors before the Games as a result of visitors booking cross-country tours including Brazil. With the exception of London, the pattern of previous Games-time visitor flows shows that visitors tend to avoid the host country in the lead up to the sporting event for fear of construction work, disruption and increased expense. Tourists drawn to the events are unlikely to travel to the region far in advance of their commencement. However, Argentina might benefit from a flow of international travellers who have chosen to avoid Brazil in the lead up to the Games. It might also be able to lure Brazilians who are apathetic about the events. Having never met a Brazilian that isn&amp;rsquo;t passionate about sport, this will be a tough challenge, but it&amp;rsquo;s worth a go.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
