<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542599857723">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 03:57:37 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.13h7vzi5eoash</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Whereabouts are you from? &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mcmpovos.com/pharmpsychcom-62bd.pdf#congratulated&quot;&gt;rjhealthsystems.com&lt;/a&gt;  In addition to the ban on abortions after 20 weeks, the bill would impose strict standards on abortion clinics that critics said could force dozens of facilities in Texas to close. Supporters of the bill say no clinics would be forced to shut down.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://leotoys.cl/nutrex-hibernate-2206.pdf#bladders&quot;&gt;protein jimmybart&lt;/a&gt;  Malcolm Webb, chief executive of Oil and Gas UK, said: &quot;There is much more that needs to be done. Despite impressive investment in new developments, the production efficiency of existing assets has been in worrying decline, with a number of fields failing to produce as expected.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.klevermedia.co.uk/cvs-pharmacy-24-hours-costa-mesa-31f1.pdf&quot;&gt;what is the difference between generic drugs and regular drugs&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;It seems to me that as we&apos;ve tried to restart thisrelationship several times, that maybe now is a moment to pauseand think about how we&apos;re going to move forward with Russia,&quot; Senate Foreign Relations Committee Chairman Robert Menendeztold ABC.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.artistparama.com/wwwmerckcom-coa-5168.pdf#hookup&quot;&gt;www.merck.com/research/fellow/home.html.&lt;/a&gt;  Verizon officials Tuesday unveiled a plan to introduce fiber optic cable to western Fire Island, where landlines were destroyed last fall and public outcry has swelled over a decision to not replace them.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.md-interiors.co.uk/klamath-blue-green-algae-health-benefits-a6a4.pdf#sensible&quot;&gt;klamath blue green algae side effects&lt;/a&gt;  In February, India put on hold a $750 million deal to buy helicopters from Italian aerospace and defense giant Finmeccanica and its British subsidiary, AgustaWestland, following charges of kickbacks and bribes. Three of the 12 helicopters were delivered in December and the rest have been put on hold.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
