<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542675754488">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">20.11.2018 01:02:34 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.nrpz2h3gqobz</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>How many weeks&apos; holiday a year are there? &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.proguaru.com.br/cheap-brand-name-levitra-7684.pdf#as&quot;&gt;cheap generic levitra india&lt;/a&gt;  There&apos;s nothing wrong with getting involved in politics or lobbying; that&apos;s part of our democracy and part of free speech. But lets not call it &quot;social welfare.&quot; They&apos;re not feeding the hungry or teaching orphans to read. They&apos;re making a political point, and generally with the goal of electing or defeating a candidate. Tea party groups (which, as it has been pointed out, might have figured they&apos;d attract some IRS attention after naming themselves after a movement of people who didn&apos;t want to pay any taxes at all) are clearly motivated toward a political end. So are the &quot;occupy&quot; people, and the so-called &quot;progressive&quot; groups which were trying to get Obama re-elected or get Guantanamo closed. Why should they be given tax-exempt status?
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://muktiforum.com/bupropion-sr-generic-price-b18b.pdf&quot;&gt;zyban rash&lt;/a&gt;  “Uttarakhand has been a huge tragedy, but the bigger tragedy has been the inability of politicians to come together at this time of crisis,” said Shankkar Aiyar, columnist and author of “Accidental India: A history of the nation&amp;#8217;s passage through crisis and change”.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dollingstownfc.com/astroglide-x-cvs-6865.pdf&quot;&gt;astroglide bulk&lt;/a&gt;  On Sunday, at age 22, 129 days, Perez became the youngest Rangers pitcher to record a complete game 35 years in a 6-1 win over Houston. He allowed just four hits and struck out a career-high eight. He came within a strike of a shutout before Chris Carter hit a two-out home run.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dollingstownfc.com/holistichealthliorg-6865.pdf&quot;&gt;power-supplements.ch&lt;/a&gt;  Nearly six months later Norton and Ali tangled again at the Forum in Inglewood, Calif. This time, Ali returned the favor, defeating Norton via another split-decision victory. The always svelte Norton was even leaner in their second fight, leading some to observe that perhaps Norton had over-trained.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.anupamdebashisroy.com/wellway-pharmacy-lynemouth-f2ef.pdf&quot;&gt;wellway pharmacy opening times&lt;/a&gt;  Renfe, the Spanish state train company, said Garzon was a30-year company veteran who had been driving for a decade. Hewas highly qualified and had been driving on the line where theaccident took place for about a year. The train was running ontime when the crash occurred.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
