<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542698388357">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">20.11.2018 07:19:48 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1wv91lutarlhk</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Do you play any instruments? &lt;a href=&quot;http://archieandtherug.com/crazy-bulk-dbal-9392.pdf&quot;&gt;crazy bulk coupon 2016&lt;/a&gt;  State attorneys general have fought for years to protect people from the dangers of tobacco products. In 1998, the attorneys general of 52 states and territories signed a landmark agreement with the four largest tobacco companies in the United States to recover billions of dollars in costs associated with smoking-related illnesses and to restrict cigarette advertising to prevent youth smoking.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://digital-matchbox.com/hoteles-barato-en-la-habana-cuba-5522.pdf#roman&quot;&gt;vuelos baratos habana panama&lt;/a&gt;  This is important, the researchers said, in part because there had not been previous research on why napping is important, and as a result, that time was targeted in efforts to find more opportunities for learning because even young children are under pressure for academic achievement.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lucky-websolutions.com/utmbhealthcom-0a7b.pdf&quot;&gt;utmbhealth.com/records&lt;/a&gt;  When prominent British feminist writer Caitlin Moran declared August 4 a day of #TwitterSilence in protest of rape and death threats tweeted to a number of UK women after they campaigned to have Jane Austen featured on a 10-pound note, she probably did not imagine it would incite a feminist civil war.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dollingstownfc.com/precio-de-cytotec-en-mexico-2013-6865.pdf#bates&quot;&gt;cytotec dosage for induced abortion&lt;/a&gt;  Unite, which is Labour&amp;#039;s largest financial backer, had been accused of trying to sign up members without their knowledge in the constituency to ensure its favoured candidate, Karie Murphy, was selected.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://paradiseinmexico.com.mx/rite-aid-ginseng-c13c.pdf&quot;&gt;rite aid ginseng&lt;/a&gt;  The mayor originally said he hoped the program would help the integration of the town&apos;s 250 asylum seekers, but pictures of the refugees, mostly from African nations, in bright red T-shirts and straw hats unleashed an outcry.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
