<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542360059456">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">16.11.2018 09:20:59 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.879qm5q33tgs</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I came here to work &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.chris-cancercommunity.com/stmap_b01a0.html?clozaril.levitra.rogaine&quot;&gt;blog.healthfirst.com&lt;/a&gt;  Goldman reported quarterly profit doubled as the bank mademore money trading bonds before an interest-rate spike hitmarkets in June. On Monday, Citigroup&apos;s strong earnings helped push the S&amp;P 500 to its longest winningstreak since mid-January.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://freelifesinsurancequotes.com/stmap_6f970.html?fucidin.crixivan.viagra.proagra&quot;&gt;accutane depression acne.org&lt;/a&gt;  A source close to the situation said the Yanks will be responsible for roughly $6.8 million of the $24.5 million remaining on Soriano’s contract, and the Cubs will pick up $13 million of the returning slugger’s $18 million salary for next season.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://zoeydeutch.net/stmap_8f080.html?cialis.revia.mentat.cordarone&quot;&gt;antidepressant withdrawal symptoms lexapro&lt;/a&gt;  The technology giant, which was eager to establish its iPad as an e-reading device, handed book publishers the power to set prices, as long as they guaranteed Apple a 30pc cut of the profits and pledged that no other retailer would be able to undercut it.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lucky-websolutions.com/stmap_0a7b0.html?cialis.cytotec.famciclovir.tadadel&quot;&gt;clibido cost&lt;/a&gt;  Speaking about the significance of its latest feature, the company wrote in a blog post: &quot;We&amp;#39;re moving past the days when business owners have to figure out if a &quot;like&quot; or a &quot;click&quot; has any meaning in the real world; now they can tell if someone who saw their ad actually walks into their store.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.weymouthskatepark.co.uk/stmap_6ae30.html?avana.levitra.pepcid&quot;&gt;actavis promethazine syrup online&lt;/a&gt;  A White House official noted that the conversation will takeplace one week before the new exchanges open, which the WhiteHouse says will allow millions of Americans who do not haveinsurance to sign up for plans that fit their budgets.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
