<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542724765474">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">20.11.2018 14:39:25 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.17w5p7i8lk825</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I went to  &lt;a href=&quot;http://archieandtherug.com/gene-lafitte-pharmacy-tishomingo-ok-9392.pdf#heavy&quot;&gt;gene lafitte pharmacy tishomingo&lt;/a&gt;  He said on the average £39,748 pension pot the difference between a &amp;ldquo;better rate and the best&amp;rdquo; was £457 a year &amp;ndash; equal to more than £11,000 over the course of retirement.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.techdesighn.com/centex-pharmacies-b26f.pdf&quot;&gt;centex pharmacies&lt;/a&gt;  Their own documented words totally contradict anyone&amp;#8217;s stated and knowingly fabricated position that multiple Arab nations, in the days leading up to the Six Day War, in 1967, had not threatened the very existence of the State of Israel and organized the immense might of all the Arab armies to not only physically annihilate the State of Israel, but to quote their own words, (see below): &amp;#8220;Wipe Israel off the map&amp;#8221;.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.artistparama.com/greenpoint-pharmacy-brooklyn-5168.pdf#pug&quot;&gt;greenpoint pharmacy southfield mi&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;It&apos;s kinda like people trying to get tickets to the firstPirates home playoff game, right?&quot; said White House spokesmanJay Carney, referring to Pittsburgh&apos;s baseball team, which hasjust reached the post-season playoffs for the first time in 21years.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://accentresurfacing.com/fildena-france-4110.pdf#gaunt&quot;&gt;fildena supractiv side effects&lt;/a&gt;  Following the couple&amp;rsquo;s separation in 2011, Mr F claimed he had been a &amp;ldquo;reluctant participant&amp;rdquo; in the decision and had become &amp;ldquo;increasingly concerned&amp;rdquo; that his daughters were not protected against measles, mumps and rubella, particularly after Dr Wakefield was discredited, and partly because of the recent measles outbreak in Wales.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.anupamdebashisroy.com/goodhealthtalkcom-f2ef.pdf#half&quot;&gt;health-is-in.com&lt;/a&gt;  A source familiar with the matter, who declined to be namedbecause Icahn hasn&apos;t disclosed his holdings in Apple, said theinvestor&apos;s stake was worth around $1 billion, a fraction of thecompany&apos;s market value of more than $400 billion.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
