<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542352628594">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">16.11.2018 07:17:08 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.115b5w0o08301</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I&apos;ve got a very weak signal &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.klevermedia.co.uk/stmap_31f10.html?sumycin.ciplox.viagra&quot;&gt;west tropicana medical center&lt;/a&gt;  Deutsche Telekom had set a July 31 deadline for tentative bids. Second-round bids for the business - which bidders value at roughly 1.5 billion euros ($2 billion) - are due in late September, the sources said.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://freelifesinsurancequotes.com/stmap_6f970.html?viagra.lansoprazole.protonix&quot;&gt;djmedmansentertainment.com&lt;/a&gt;  France has halted sales of Mercedes cars assembled since June 12 because of Daimler&apos;s refusal to stop using the air-conditioning coolant R134a, banned from new vehicles since the start of the year. The blocked models account for most of the brand&apos;s French business and 2 percent of global deliveries.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.chris-cancercommunity.com/stmap_b01a0.html?cyclogyl.dexamethason.viagra.tadadel&quot;&gt;can i take pristiq while pregnant&lt;/a&gt;  People who purchased tickets in advance can also look out over New York Harbor from the statue&apos;s crown, which reopened after a long hiatus one day before Sandy hit and was forced to close again due to the storm. The crown had been off-limits for a year during a $30 million upgrade to fire alarms, sprinkler systems and exit routes.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://archieandtherug.com/stmap_93920.html?tadacip.rythmol.cialis.hydroxyzine&quot;&gt;burn slim lip09 coffee&lt;/a&gt;  The media measurement firm says that for the first time it has proved with statistical rigor what many in the media business have suspected in recent years: that a show&apos;s ratings and the magnitude of its Twitter buzz are correlated.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ascfinancialadvisers.co.uk/stmap_55530.html?levaquin.gemfibrozil.cialis.imuran&quot;&gt;palm medical centers coral gables&lt;/a&gt;  &amp;#8220;That means a home gardener who thought they planted a bee friendly landscape in their backyard may end up planting a bee toxic garden instead,&amp;#8221; said Lex Horan of the Pesticide Action Network.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
