<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542613973970">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 07:52:53 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.da17ne830m66</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>A book of First Class stamps &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.elegantandwild.co.uk/casper-pharma-75b3.pdf#analysis&quot;&gt;casper pharma private limited&lt;/a&gt;  Demand response program participants are compensated forreducing electricity use - and could be penalized for not doingso - by raising air conditioner thermostats and by turning offunnecessary lights and other equipment, including elevators. Putting on-site generators into use also reduces the amount ofpower needed from the grid.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ascfinancialadvisers.co.uk/viaman-viper-5553.pdf#entry&quot;&gt;viaman viper review&lt;/a&gt;  I asked Kessler why he thought humor wasn&apos;t used more often in advancing progressive climate policies, and he wasn&apos;t sure. But it&apos;s not the case, he said, that the activist community is itself humor-deficient:
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://laser-eye-surgery-reviews.org/trenbolone-acetate-used-in-cattle-6a83.pdf&quot;&gt;trenbolone dosage for cattle&lt;/a&gt;  Rivera said it was humbling to hear players speak of him in these ways. He mentioned that fellow New Yorker David Wright made a point of telling him on Tuesday that he admired how the legendary closer has handled himself during his career.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://lemcasesorias.com/index.php/monte-vista-pharmacy-hours-83f5.pdf#armed&quot;&gt;rite aid monte vista pharmacy&lt;/a&gt;  David Horne, managing director of East Midlands Trains, said: &quot;More than 750 buses a day will be running to keep people on the move - we are determined that we will get people to where they want to go.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ecorporationbd.com/can-you-buy-hiv-tests-at-drugstores-aaa8.pdf#novelty&quot;&gt;price of illegal drugs in us&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;The quickest way to end our costly fossil fuel dependency is through energy efficiency and renewable power, not new reactors that will suck up precious investment and take years to complete,&quot; he said.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
