<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542729966223">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">20.11.2018 16:06:06 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.155widdrmzzlg</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I don&apos;t like pubs &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.proguaru.com.br/dexyfen-ingredients-7684.pdf&quot;&gt;dexyfen pro thermogenic en espaol&lt;/a&gt;  Or international corporations. It actually has more of an impact to the city economy when someone stays in someone’s apartment in Bushwick than it does when somebody stays in one of these hotels here in Times Square.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mikasafloors.com/medolarkcom-bdec.pdf&quot;&gt;medolark.com&lt;/a&gt;  The affable LBC presenter adds: &amp;ldquo;David seems to be a man who is able to compartmentalise his life very effectively, which I would say is good for any time-pushed PM with a country to run and red box to somehow get through&amp;rdquo;.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dollingstownfc.com/filagra-100-dp-6865.pdf#shame&quot;&gt;filagra 100 dp&lt;/a&gt;  When a &amp;ldquo;boy&amp;rdquo; goes berserk and slays lots of young people in a &amp;ldquo;mass shooting event&amp;rdquo;, can that be attributed to something a rational mind can grasp? To the ideology he professes, perhaps &amp;ndash; protecting his tribe from the perceived threat of multiculturalism and a modern world gone soft? To something that happened in his childhood &amp;ndash; bullying, say, or a parental absence? Is there a psychiatric label that might work &amp;ndash; narcissism, repressed homosexuality, a messiah complex?
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://freelifesinsurancequotes.com/sepharmorg-6f97.pdf#estate&quot;&gt;douglasmainpharmacy.com&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;All that needed to happen was to say, &apos;Hey are you alright? Is this what you want to be happening?&apos;&quot; she said. &quot;She obviously wasn&apos;t OK with what happened. It was rape. She reported it to the police as rape.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://laser-eye-surgery-reviews.org/cytomel-online-6a83.pdf#religious&quot;&gt;thyroid medication cytomel&lt;/a&gt;  BBC political correspondent Ben Wright said: &quot;With an economy that now seems to be gathering momentum, one of the key arguments that Labour have been making for the last two years - the government got this wrong, their economic prescription failed - is no longer as powerful a message at it was six months or a year ago.&quot;
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
