<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542569013300">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 19:23:33 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.zd26bcdw24ut</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>What sort of music do you listen to? &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.md-interiors.co.uk/dougherty-pharmacy-humble-a6a4.pdf#height&quot;&gt;dougherty pharmacy springtown&lt;/a&gt;  Rupert Murdoch has been recalled to face questioning by MPsafter a tape emerged on which he appeared to express regret overcooperation with police investigating his British newspapers anddescribe corrupt payments to public officials for information as&quot;the culture of Fleet Street&quot;.()
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.casadeadoracao.com.br/index.php/specialtymedicalsupplycom-bac9.pdf&quot;&gt;specialtymedicalsupply.com&lt;/a&gt;  Bernadita Duran, a disabled resident of New York State, got taken in by a &quot;last-dollar&quot; scam. She wound up paying $4,000 to a &quot;debt settlement&quot; company, which pocketed the whole amount in fees without settling any of her debts.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.anupamdebashisroy.com/wwwwaikatodhbhealthnzoralhealth-f2ef.pdf#user&quot;&gt;www.waikatodhb.health.nz/tepunaoranga&lt;/a&gt;  Taylor said that all assistance, however, doesn&apos;t come from the Red Cross. They help families get in contact with other agencies and partners to help provide the services they need. He said they routinely refer people to the United Way and Catholic and LDS churches, but they can also put people in contact with private companies.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://globalelite.tv/super-p-force-next-day-delivery-b1c8.pdf&quot;&gt;super p force next day delivery&lt;/a&gt;  Jordan says the behavior was very unusual for Killian, a black lab and German shepherd mix. &quot;He is a very personable dog,&quot; Jordan told Fox and Friends. &quot;He is an 80-pound lap dog. For him to show aggression towards anyone is a sign.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://leotoys.cl/desyrel-medscape-2206.pdf#convenient&quot;&gt;desyrel medscape&lt;/a&gt;  The family of the seven-year-old girl asked other parents to imagine how they would feel if it were their child who was taken away and added they hoped no-one else would have to go through a similar ordeal.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
