<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542495015667">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">17.11.2018 22:50:15 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.61ke6ccqa9be</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I never went to university &lt;a href=&quot;https://newscvm.com/obidouhealthcloudcom-e9bb.pdf&quot;&gt;boost4health.eu&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;A completely different ecosystem could be built overnight. Google needs to keep Samsung very close. What made Android popular was not the just the operating system itself - it was the money Samsung put into their devices.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.techdesighn.com/apollo-peak-mountain-bike-price-b26f.pdf#mature&quot;&gt;apollo peak beverages&lt;/a&gt;  The deal is the latest in a spate of acquisitions in theglobal telecom sector, which is reshaping the competitivedynamics of an industry struggling in Europe but flourishing inthe United States and Asia where prices and profits are higher.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://contactconsultoria.com/index.php/medicheck-app-a511.pdf#malignant&quot;&gt;medicheck app&lt;/a&gt;  Sun Ho, who led the South Korean delegation, said his team would strive to accomplish &quot;developmental normalisation&quot; of the complex &quot;in accordance with common sense and international rules&quot;.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.casadeadoracao.com.br/index.php/medikalcomec-bac9.pdf#forgive&quot;&gt;shop.sued-med.de&lt;/a&gt;  Boston Scientific, like many medical device makers, has struggled with weak sales for the last several years as people lost their jobs and health insurance and delayed medical procedures. Demand also fell as governments around the world cut spending on healthcare.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dollingstownfc.com/veggie-bullet-recipes-6865.pdf&quot;&gt;veggie bullet accessories australia&lt;/a&gt;  Argentina, still without a Championship victory since making their debut last year, started brightly by restricting New Zealand to just one try in the first half - Julian Savea bursting through to go over in the corner.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
