<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542538537357">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 10:55:37 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.xroedhkyhd1m</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>We&apos;re at university together &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.anupamdebashisroy.com/nf-cure-capsules-price-in-inr-f2ef.pdf&quot;&gt;nf cure capsules price in inr&lt;/a&gt;  Facebook grew revenue 53 percent to $1.813 billion in the second quarter, above the average analyst expectation of $1.618 billion, according to Thomson Reuters I/B/E/S. Facebook had $1.184 billion in revenue in the year ago period.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ecorporationbd.com/levitra-nebenwirkungen-haut-aaa8.pdf#insurance&quot;&gt;levitra reviews patients&lt;/a&gt;  You know the people who run the Jets are fixed on the Giants as much as Rex is fixed on the Patriots; know they have been going up against the Giants at a time when the Giants are bigger than they have been since the ’50s and ’60s, when they were as popular and romantic a sports team as New York has ever known, even if those teams lost five NFL title games out of six and were nearly the Buffalo Bills of their time.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://leotoys.cl/generic-accutane-lawsuit-2206.pdf&quot;&gt;accutane 60 mg 5 months&lt;/a&gt;  I was a milkman&amp;rsquo;s assistant from age 11 or 12 and paid 10s (50p), which was quite a bit in those days. I worked all day Saturday, and that was horrendous when all the money had to be collected. It was pretty dirty work because most people didn&amp;rsquo;t rinse their bottles properly, so I&amp;rsquo;d pick up their manky bottles with sour milk.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mikasafloors.com/diabeteshealthcommx-bdec.pdf#software&quot;&gt;diabeteshealth.com/charts&lt;/a&gt;  Do me a favor: Instead of referring to the bullshit funding nonsense as &quot;farmer welfare,&quot; call it &quot;corporate farmer welfare.&quot; Real farmers don&amp;#039;t get welfare. Big Ag and rich horse breeders do.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ascfinancialadvisers.co.uk/norvelt-pharmacy-pennsylvania-5553.pdf&quot;&gt;norvelt pharmacy pa&lt;/a&gt;  The Prime Minister was more revealing about his role in family life, admitting that being left in charge of his children on his own was &amp;ldquo;very, very hard work.&amp;rdquo; He said his tendency to try and lead them could also lead to conflict with his nine year old daughter Nancy.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
