<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1543384890241">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">28.11.2018 06:01:30 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.s3cd4iwfub5e</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I&apos;ve only just arrived &lt;a href=&quot;http://teerandaz.com/stmap_131c0.html?viagra.butenafine.minocin&quot;&gt;online pharmacy tech reviews&lt;/a&gt;  White House spokesman Jay Carney said Mr Rouhani&amp;#039;s inauguration &quot;presents an opportunity for Iran to act quickly to resolve the international community&amp;#039;s deep concerns over Iran&amp;#039;s nuclear programme&quot;.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.greenlam.com/index.php/stmap_77410.html?silymarin.motrin.budesonide.viagra&quot;&gt;bhv pharmaceutical&lt;/a&gt;  The Pentagon report also reclassified nearly a dozen previous attacks on coalition troops and Afghans patrolling with them as insider violence, which raised the number of attacks from 88 to a total of 102 from 2007 through 2012. A total of 144 NATO troops — 92 of them Americans — died in those attacks. Seventy of the attacks were aimed solely at U.S. troops.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.brentwood-karting.com/index.php/stmap_6e560.html?tamoxifen.ciprofloxacin.levitra&quot;&gt;anabol-steroids.biz australia&lt;/a&gt;  Barclays&apos; rights issue prospectus also said it faced a 50million pound fine from Britain&apos;s Financial Conduct Authorityfor its failure to adequately disclose fees it had paid Qatariinvestors over the last five years.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sensors.co.uk/stmap_98740.html?prozac.levitra.captopril&quot;&gt;supplementsource.ca legit&lt;/a&gt;  Relations between the two countries have grown increasingly tense since a Russian court in the Arctic city of Murmansk ordered 30 people held in pretrial detention earlier this month on charges of piracy stemming from a September protest in which activists attempted to scale an offshore platform in the Arctic to protest oil exploration. The charges carry a prison term of up to 15 years.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://tynerblain.com/blog/stmap_ef2c0.html?leukeran.angeliq.trimox.viagra&quot;&gt;pfizer viagra priser&lt;/a&gt;  The Cardinals managed just 30 yards rushing on 18 attempts, adding to the pass protection woes. “When you get into that type of game and you get behind it’s going to be a struggle,” Arizona coach Bruce Arians said, “but we have to figure out ways to start faster on both sides of the ball. I thought we came out sluggish.”
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
