<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1543412493566">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">28.11.2018 13:41:33 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1dwbb01dh8rim</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>How much does the job pay? &lt;a href=&quot;http://teerandaz.com/fentanyl-patch-transdermal-131c.pdf#reel&quot;&gt;fentanyl patch for pain relief&lt;/a&gt;  Returning from holiday, Tokyo&apos;s Nikkei slipped 0.1percent. One bright spot was stocks in iPhone suppliers,burnished by news Apple Inc had sold 9 million newiPhones during their first three days in stores.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.brentwood-karting.com/index.php/martyspharmacycom-6e56.pdf&quot;&gt;angelushealth.com&lt;/a&gt;  Mahan isn&amp;#8217;t the first expectant father to face such a decision. Last September, Boston Red Sox second baseman Dustin Pedroia found his wife was in labor during the seventh inning of a game. Once Pedroia was notified, he bolted from the field to be with his wife.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://pixelbedlam.co.uk/brothers-pharmacy-brookings-65ef.pdf&quot;&gt;brookshire brothers pharmacy number&lt;/a&gt;  This week&apos;s final ruling ends a lawsuit dating back to 2011, when Facebook was sued over &quot;Sponsored Stories,&quot; which turned users&apos; &quot;likes&quot; into ads on their newsfeed. Plaintiffs accused the social network of improperly using names, photographs, likenesses, and identities of users &quot;to generate substantial profits for Facebook.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://starbizzcon.com/kona-deep-water-reviews-45db.pdf#happyness&quot;&gt;kona deep blue water&lt;/a&gt;  BEIJING/HONG KONG - China reiterated its opposition on Thursday to a European Union plan to limit airline carbon dioxide emissions and called for talks to resolve the issue a day after its major airlines refused to pay any carbon costs under the new law.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://oktandrammen.no/drammen-ny/igunapharmacom-e52c.pdf#degree&quot;&gt;littleblackbagmed.com&lt;/a&gt;  Ajmol Alom, 16, was &quot;one of our brightest prospects&quot;, his headmaster at Langdon Park School in Poplar, east London said. He died after he was wounded in Poplar on 12 August. A man has been charged with his murder.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
