<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542463410346">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">17.11.2018 14:03:30 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.642m2erehmi7</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Where are you calling from? &lt;a href=&quot;https://muv.asia/stmap_bf280.html?amoxapine.cialis.vilitra.starlix&quot;&gt;cialis suppliers australia&lt;/a&gt;  Mr. James A. Bell is Independent Director of JP Morgan Chase &amp; Co. Mr. Bell was an Executive Vice President of The Boeing Company, the world’s aerospace company, from 2003 until his retirement effective April 1, 2012. He had been Corporate President from June 2008 until February 2012 and was Chief Financial Officer from November 2003 until February 2012. While Chief Financial Officer, he oversaw two key Boeing businesses, Boeing Capital Corporation, the company’s customer-financing subsidiary, and Boeing Shared Services, an 8,000-person, multi-billion dollar business unit that provides common internal services across Boeing’s global enterprise. He is a director of Dow Chemical Company (since 2005). Prior to being named Chief Financial Officer in 2003, Mr. Bell held the position of Senior Vice President of Finance and Corporate Controller from 2000 and was Vice President of contracts and pricing for Boeing Space and Communications from 1996 to 2000. Before becoming Vice President at the operating group level in 1996, Mr. Bell served as director of business management of the Space Station Electric Power System at the Boeing Rocketdyne unit. Mr. Bell began his career with Rockwell in 1972. Mr. Bell graduated California State University at Los Angeles with a degree in accounting. He is a member of the board of directors of the Chicago Urban League, World Business Chicago and the Chicago Economic Club.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
