<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542356966347">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">16.11.2018 08:29:26 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.11yjfcavp6h4i</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Remove card &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lovemycase.com/stmap_f2c20.html?cialis.dinitrate.ziagen.pioglitazone&quot;&gt;arkansashealthcareers.com&lt;/a&gt;  The problem, according to coach Jason Kidd, was their poor transition defense. The Nets allowed 13.4 fastbreak points per game last season, which was in the bottom half of the league. It&apos;s worse than it sounds because they played at such a slow pace. They were 29th in fastbreak points scored, ahead of only the Knicks.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.artistparama.com/stmap_51680.html?hydrea.azelaic.cialis&quot;&gt;epinephrine online pharmacy&lt;/a&gt;  In one high-profile example, the Chamber joined other business groups to challenge New York City&apos;s partial ban on large soda drinks and other sugary beverages. In July, the New York Supreme Court, Appellate Division, upheld a lower court ruling that invalidated the ban.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.casadeadoracao.com.br/index.php/stmap_bac90.html?prilosec.viagra.tentex&quot;&gt;femigra achat en ligne&lt;/a&gt;  BRUSSELS - A European Union court ruled on Friday that the EU should lift sanctions it imposed against seven Iranian companies, dealing a new blow to Europe&apos;s efforts to use economic pressure to rein in Tehran&apos;s disputed nuclear work.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://contactconsultoria.com/index.php/stmap_a5110.html?erectalis.viagra.kemadrin.eldepryl&quot;&gt;deer antler spray kaufen&lt;/a&gt;  Not many know more about the East Midlands rivalry than Forest boss Billy Davies who managed Derby for a season. He has only been at these two clubs since 2006 and took Derby into the Premier League through the play-offs.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ecorporationbd.com/stmap_aaa80.html?asendin.levitra.donepezil&quot;&gt;www.asiamed.com&lt;/a&gt;  Showalter, who managed Rodriguez on the Texas Rangers, says he has no interest in discussing the suspension possibilities surrounding the Yankees third baseman but is taking aim at how New York could benefit.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
