<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1543389055262">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">28.11.2018 07:10:55 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1930pac06lgig</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>A First Class stamp &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.aicpuglia.it/stmap_23970.html?cialis.droxia.rulide&quot;&gt;medithrop.com&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;PDVSA will pay much more for freight in 2013, not includingthe misuse of part of its fleet and the inefficiency of someterminals,&quot; a tanker broker who trades with PDVSA said. &quot;Thisimplies extra costs for delays and fines.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.purplecreativedesign.co.uk/stmap_58840.html?cialis.ranitidine.mebeverine&quot;&gt;acheter viagra gnrique en france&lt;/a&gt;  Get Covered America volunteers listen to a training session before canvassing a Chicago, Illinois neighborhood to talk with residents about the Affordable Care Act - also known as Obamacare - September 7, 2013.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://tynerblain.com/blog/stmap_ef2c0.html?viagra.felodipine.phenytoin.nebivolol&quot;&gt;rdv-med.com&lt;/a&gt;  The report said India remained the focus of Pakistan&apos;s military &quot;despite a growing American threat including actual border raids, drone strikes, special operations, the spread of a hostile spy network&quot; among others.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://pixelbedlam.co.uk/stmap_65ef0.html?moxifloxacin.ladygra.carbonate.cialis&quot;&gt;medalsofamerica.com/patches&lt;/a&gt;  Conservative leader Silvio Berlusconi withdrew support forthe government of Prime Minister Enrico Letta, throwing intodoubt its ability to survive and sending Italian stocks andbonds lower. That many see Berlusconi&apos;s move, which headvertised as being about a sales tax increase, as a cynicalattempt to improve his bargaining position in his personal legalproblems did not help to dampen volatility.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://starbizzcon.com/stmap_45db0.html?phenazopyridine.cialis.trimox.b12&quot;&gt;labopharm canada&lt;/a&gt;  In May, pro-Assad militias killed more than 50 residents of Baida and over 60 local people in the nearby town of Banias. In those killings, some bodies, many of them children, were found burned and mutilated.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
