<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542483927469">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">17.11.2018 19:45:27 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1fxflqftkh2oa</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>When do you want me to start? &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.casadeadoracao.com.br/index.php/nutripharmonlinecom-bac9.pdf&quot;&gt;pharmix.ch&lt;/a&gt;  McDonald&apos;s Corp, the world&apos;s largest restaurantchain, reported weaker-than-expected net income and warned thatfull-year results would be &quot;challenged&quot; in the face of fallingsales in Europe, its biggest market. Shares fell 2.9 percent to$97.42 in premarket trade.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lovemycase.com/wegmans-pharmacy-number-hunt-valley-f2c2.pdf#recipe&quot;&gt;wegmans pharmacy christmas eve hours&lt;/a&gt;  Critics say the Canadian design for the medium-haul jet made of light-weight composite materials ignores a trend toward larger aircraft seating 150 people or more as air traffic expands and carriers offer more seats.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.md-interiors.co.uk/goldbely-a6a4.pdf#disposition&quot;&gt;goldbely&lt;/a&gt;  The soldier waived his right to a jury trial and his fate was decided by Col Denise Lind, the military judge who presided over his court martial at Fort Meade, a military base outside Washington.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sarah-hyland.net/snoqualmie-ice-cream-racing-79a8.pdf&quot;&gt;snoqualmie ice cream racing&lt;/a&gt;  But he faces resistance not just from President GiorgioNapolitano, who would have to order parliament to be dissolved,but also from his own increasingly fractious supporters, some ofwhom may switch allegiance and back Letta&apos;s government.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.artistparama.com/midminnesotadrugtestingcom-5168.pdf#lustre&quot;&gt;atmedtreatmentcenter.com&lt;/a&gt;  Jerry Sandusky arrives in handcuffs at the office of Centre County Magisterial District Judge Leslie A. Dutchcot on Nov. 5, 2011, in State College, Pa. Penn State, the school where he coached football, set aside $60 million for settlements in the case that put Sandusky behind bars for 30 to 60 years.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
