<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542494968443">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">17.11.2018 22:49:28 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.16nq2wnvnboqs</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I live in London &lt;a href=&quot;https://muv.asia/where-can-i-get-permethrin-5-cream-bf28.pdf&quot;&gt;how long does it take permethrin to cure scabies&lt;/a&gt;  STOCKHOLM - With 100 million people logging on every day for a fix of its games like Candy Crush Saga, global gamemaker King is showing rivals not just how to hook players, but how to get them to pay.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.haroldwhitefuneraldirectors.co.uk/pillar5-pharma-email-bd82.pdf&quot;&gt;pillar5 pharma email&lt;/a&gt;  Florida lawmakers rejected a similar bill this year after First Amendment concerns surfaced there. Last year, the Missouri Supreme Court cited concerns about free speech in striking down part of a 2008 law enacted after a teenager who was teased online committed suicide.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://digital-matchbox.com/super-1-pharmacy-ellensburg-wa-5522.pdf#permit&quot;&gt;super 1 pharmacy hours carencro la&lt;/a&gt;  A video of what it might look like was a big hit on YouTube and won thousands of &quot;likes&quot; on Facebook. That success led to a Kickstarter campaign that aimed to raise £200,000 to produce a prototype. Sadly, the project was not fully funded.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://lemcasesorias.com/index.php/pro-santedoctipharmafr-83f5.pdf#shocking&quot;&gt;pro-sante.doctipharma.fr&lt;/a&gt;  Athens must put a total of 25,000 workers in a so-called&quot;mobility scheme&quot; by the end of the year, to be eithertransferred to other government jobs or dismissed. It must alsomeet a target of 15,000 mandatory job cuts in 2013-2014.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://sjofartsbygningen.no/mamma-chia-squeeze-nutrition-info-7ef0.pdf#suicide&quot;&gt;mamma chia energy drink review&lt;/a&gt;  Some 800 building owners failed to file mandatory inspection reports on the safety of their balconies and terraces, officials found. It wasn&apos;t clear whether the reports were current at Rosoff&apos;s building.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
