<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542720605683">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">20.11.2018 13:30:05 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1i3qcfkpqnovv</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Canada&gt;Canada &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.chris-cancercommunity.com/cialis-holland-kaufen-b01a.pdf#belong&quot;&gt;prezzo cialis generico&lt;/a&gt;  Cruise ships have traditionally been among the safest bigvessels but the insurance industry has faced a growing challengefrom a new breed of superships like the Costa Concordia and themonstrous new bulk cargo carriers that have emerged with therise in global trade volumes.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.layeredonline.com/how-much-alcohol-can-i-drink-with-cialis-dd54.pdf&quot;&gt;cialis 20 mg comprim pellicul bote de 8&lt;/a&gt;  Annuities are an extremely profitable business for insurance companies, who make as much as 20pc on each sale. Unfortunately, many retirees play into their hands by failing to shop around different firms, which offer wildly varying payout rates.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dollingstownfc.com/flagyl-medication-price-6865.pdf&quot;&gt;can the antibiotic flagyl cause yeast infection&lt;/a&gt;  The guru had been putting his followers through a militant training course to face the coming apocalyptic race war that he predicted and called Helter Skelter. Everyone was armed with a knife and sent out in squads at night, “creepy-crawling,” silently entering houses. Owners would wake up to find their furniture moved around. That nothing was stolen made it just that more menacing and sinister.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dollingstownfc.com/hsmeddk-6865.pdf&quot;&gt;defihealthcare.com&lt;/a&gt;  The quote of the week comes from our old Rosedale friend Philip Talamo, commenting on the U.S. government shutdown. Visitors arrived to find “CLOSED” signs at the Statue of Liberty, the Smithsonian and other parks and historic sites across the country:
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://digital-matchbox.com/safe-website-to-buy-viagra-online-5522.pdf&quot;&gt;r det olagligt att kpa viagra&lt;/a&gt;  At 27, Klee was a house-husband working on the kitchen table, supported by Lily&amp;rsquo;s teaching, while he attempted to make a career as a satirical illustrator. In 1910, he visited Paris and saw Picasso&amp;rsquo;s Cubist paintings; at the same time he loved walking in the mountains in the classic German Romantic spirit. In 1914, he travelled to Tunisia, executing the luminous watercolours that are among his most popular works, claiming &amp;ldquo;colour and I have become one&amp;rdquo;.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
