<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542540475233">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 11:27:55 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1b26wt9e29h8z</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>No, I&apos;m not particularly sporty &lt;a href=&quot;https://virtual-operations.com/housedoctorscomnepa-92e2.pdf#orderly&quot;&gt;housedoctors.com&lt;/a&gt;  David Starkey was typically misinterpreted when he talked about history being &amp;ldquo;feminised&amp;rdquo;, saying that wives and queens were being accorded far too much importance. He was teasing a bit, no doubt, but he was also making a serious point about the difference between stories and history. Almost 60 years ago, AJP Taylor made a comparable observation about Nancy Mitford&amp;rsquo;s 1954 work, Madame de Pompadour. She had, he said, taken the fictionalised Mitford family of her novels and transported them to the court of Louis XV. Versailles was utter blissikins and the king was perfectly heavenly.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.proguaru.com.br/relief-pharmacist-agency-7684.pdf&quot;&gt;relief pharmacist salary canada&lt;/a&gt;  The transformation has been less successful in Ostrava, acity of 300,000 on the country&apos;s northeastern border withPoland, home to an iron industry largely built by the Rothschildfamily almost two centuries ago.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.techdesighn.com/legalsteroidsml-b26f.pdf#transmitted&quot;&gt;vprx-penis-pills.biz&lt;/a&gt;  At this rate, the &amp;#8220;religion of peace&amp;#8221; will have killed each other off in a few years. It&amp;#8217;s a joke religion and the stories coming out of the middle east confirm the assessment. They&amp;#8217;ve killed more of each other than the &amp;#8220;infidels&amp;#8221; have killed throughout the history of the &amp;#8220;religion of peace&amp;#8221;.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://globalelite.tv/olanzapine-api-manufacturer-b1c8.pdf#incidentally&quot;&gt;can i get high off zyprexa&lt;/a&gt;  A total of 71 police officers have now been injured during disturbances in the north and east of the city, and other parts of Northern Ireland, after coming under attack with missiles including petrol bombs and blast bombs in clashes linked to the parading dispute.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mcmpovos.com/azithromycin-hexal-500-mg-preis-62bd.pdf#balanced&quot;&gt;azithromycin 500mg cena&lt;/a&gt;  Forensic specialists have since inspected the stove and found evidence of &quot;painting primer, the remains of canvas and paint,&quot; Ernest Oberlander-Tarnoveanu, director of Romania&apos;s National History Museum, told the Associated Press. Law enforcement officials must now determine whether the ashes came from the missing paintings in question.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
