<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542497417604">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">17.11.2018 23:30:17 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.b508si0fg57o</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I&apos;m retired &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.artistparama.com/pletal-100-mg-prezzo-5168.pdf#apiece&quot;&gt;pletal 100mg preisvergleich&lt;/a&gt;  An Afghan wearing a uniform of the security forces turned his weapon against foreign troops Saturday, killing three in eastern Afghanistan, NATO and Afghan officials said. It was another apparent attack by a member of the Afghan forces against their international allies.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mikasafloors.com/goedkoopste-diclofenac-bdec.pdf&quot;&gt;diclofenac sodico 75 mg precios&lt;/a&gt;  An unsourced report in newspaper Il Messaggero said onWednesday Telecom Italia Chairman Franco Bernabe was mulling acash call to help cope with financial difficulties. (Reporting by Stephen Jewkes; editing by Francesca Landini)
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://reflectiveteens.com/butlerhealthclinicorg-213a.pdf#tap&quot;&gt;cialispharman.com&lt;/a&gt;  The Commission - the EU&amp;#039;s executive and treaty watchdog - says the new authority is needed because the EU&amp;#039;s anti-fraud office Olaf cannot prosecute fraud cases, it can only pass on its findings to national authorities. Conviction rates vary considerably across the 27-nation EU, the Commission adds.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://lemcasesorias.com/index.php/kerave-hair-amazon-83f5.pdf#chaise&quot;&gt;kerave hair&lt;/a&gt;  Police say more than 50 people were wounded in the Wednesday evening attack. They say it happened in a part of the Iraqi capital known as Kasra, a predominantly Shiite enclave in a part of the city that is otherwise largely Sunni.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.elegantandwild.co.uk/pharmamedcomlb-75b3.pdf&quot;&gt;medrc.org&lt;/a&gt;  Adjacent is Machrihanish Dunes, a five-year-old course that looks like it’s been around for centuries. The course received top billing as the most environmentally friendly golf course in the world by the Golf Environmental Organization. “Mach Dunes” uses no pesticides, chemicals or irrigation. The course is incredibly self-sustaining, relying on both Mother Nature and Hebridean black sheep to tidy up its daisy-covered fairways.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
