<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542698870917">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">20.11.2018 07:27:50 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.yycimdfan699</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>The line&apos;s engaged &lt;a href=&quot;https://laser-eye-surgery-reviews.org/buy-proscar-online-uk-6a83.pdf&quot;&gt;finasteride 5mg online uk&lt;/a&gt;  FRANKFURT, Sept 12 (Reuters) - A hacker has stolen thenames, addresses and bank account numbers of about 2 millionVodafone Germany customers who should beware thatcriminals may now try to elicit other information such aspasswords, the company said.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.elegantandwild.co.uk/alphagan-rxlist-75b3.pdf#launch&quot;&gt;alphagan rxlist&lt;/a&gt;  The California lawmakers calling for an overhaul - who comprise nearly half of the Republican delegation to the state legislature - are pushing back against the party&apos;s national leaders for a variety of reasons. The state relies heavily on its agricultural, construction and hospitality businesses, all of which depend on immigrant labor.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://globalelite.tv/buy-tinidazole-uk-b1c8.pdf#swell&quot;&gt;buy tinidazole uk&lt;/a&gt;  The Holocaust Memorial Centre in Budapest had hoped to turn it into a permanent monument to the Jews. Instead, it looks set to be administered by historian Maria Schmidt and her House of Terror museum.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lucky-websolutions.com/winsol-crystal-clear-550-0a7b.pdf&quot;&gt;winsol&lt;/a&gt;  Baseball players are notoriously superstitious, and though no one on the Red Sox associated the team&apos;s record with its hairiness on Tuesday, it&apos;s hardly surprising that more and more of them grew out their whiskers as the club coasted toward the playoffs.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://reflectiveteens.com/pharmaworldcom-213a.pdf#conquered&quot;&gt;pharmaworld.com&lt;/a&gt;  He added: &quot;Far from being a &amp;#039;neo-colonial institution&amp;#039;, the modern Commonwealth operates on a consensus model and its voluntary membership is predicated primarily on a country&amp;#039;s commitment to upholding shared values and principles.&quot;
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
