<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542575449873">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 21:10:49 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.g0vfuwszi3hu</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>What do you like doing in your spare time? &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dollingstownfc.com/parkwood-street-road-pharmacy-inc-6865.pdf#miscellaneous&quot;&gt;parkwood street road pharmacy inc&lt;/a&gt;  Diane Nelson, senior lecturer in linguistics at the University of Leeds, explains that certain words in language, in particular words for ethnic, religious minorities and women, tend to &quot;slide&quot; towards negative connotations.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.layeredonline.com/order-cialis-online-from-canada-dd54.pdf&quot;&gt;cialis over the counter dubai&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;The court found that Apple&apos;s illegal conduct deprived consumers of the benefits of e-book price competition and forced them to pay substantially higher prices,&quot; Bill Baer, Assistant Attorney General in charge of the DOJ&apos;s Antitrust Division, said in a statement. &quot;Under the department&apos;s proposed order, Apple&apos;s illegal conduct will cease and Apple and its senior executives will be prevented from conspiring to thwart competition in the future.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.greenlamindustries.com/blog/prosupps-vexxum-0bae.pdf&quot;&gt;prosupps vexxum stack&lt;/a&gt;  Dalton Philips said Wm Morrison Supermarkets isready to pay an online sales tax on its new internet deliverybusiness if the government is willing to address the &quot;massivedisadvantage&quot; that the high street suffers compared to web-basedretailers. ()
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://laser-eye-surgery-reviews.org/neosize-xl-dubai-6a83.pdf&quot;&gt;neosize xl customer review&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;The downgrade illustrates that we haven&apos;t reached thebottom yet (for ratings) and it shows how worried Spain shouldbe. Spain is more immediately at risk (of forced selling). Thebig thing would be if Spain lost its investment grade status.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://virtual-operations.com/glovestix-review-92e2.pdf#bearing&quot;&gt;glovestix uk&lt;/a&gt;  Apple watchers said early signs pointed to more demand forthe 5S than last year&apos;s new model. But some cautioned that thesize of the crowds this year may not be an accurate gaugebecause consumers were unable to order the more expensive modelonline ahead of time, as with previous launches.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
