<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542582893176">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 23:14:53 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1b0rrsudq2lfz</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Do you play any instruments? &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.haroldwhitefuneraldirectors.co.uk/what-is-diclofenac-used-for-treating-bd82.pdf#plainly&quot;&gt;what is diclofenac used for treating&lt;/a&gt;  Kansas had the highest percentage — 52% — of miles of pavement in poor condition, with Connecticut following closely behind. Then came New Jersey, 45%; Hawaii, 39%; California, 37%; and Oklahoma, 36%.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.greenlamindustries.com/blog/fleatreatmentfordognet-0bae.pdf#goodness&quot;&gt;integrative-medicine.fi&lt;/a&gt;  This is the main reason why bare-foot running is becoming more popular among some long-distance runners. “Lots of people are trying barefoot running. It is massive in America and it’s starting to come over here now,” Dr Wilkinson said.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://stsmihajlopupin.edu.rs/rs/diarrheaemedtvcom-3c56.pdf&quot;&gt;kasugai-med.or.jp&lt;/a&gt;  Chief Financial Officer Ronald T. Hundzinski said on aconference call with analysts that the company&apos;s priority forspending was &quot;strategic&quot; acquisitions, after capitalexpenditures and paying a dividend.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.casadeadoracao.com.br/index.php/how-much-is-viagra-yahoo-answers-bac9.pdf&quot;&gt;can you take 200mg of viagra&lt;/a&gt;  U.S. Senator John McCain talks to reporters as the Senate passes a spending bill to avoid a government shutdown, sending the issue back to the House of Representatives, at the U.S. Capitol in Washington, September 27, 2013.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.chris-cancercommunity.com/p-boost-pills-b01a.pdf&quot;&gt;does ip boost stack with win of the day&lt;/a&gt;  Dina Loor — whose husband, police Officer Eder Loor, survived having a 31/2-inch blade jabbed into his brain while responding to a call that a Harlem schizophrenic was off his medications in April 2012 — was one of 1,247 new police recruits to begin training at the Police Academy this week.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
