<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542637655791">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 14:27:35 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.oigwl1kqi8yu</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I have my own business &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dollingstownfc.com/thequestforhealthnet-6865.pdf&quot;&gt;wildfoodsandmedicines.com&lt;/a&gt;  Already on Thursday, Republican lawmakers in Congress launched a new investigation into the technical glitches, sending letters to U.S. Health and Human Services Secretary Kathleen Sebelius and two of the website&apos;s contractors, asking for details on what is causing the failures and any system changes or testing that had been performed.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://contactconsultoria.com/index.php/lamisil-tabletas-costo-a511.pdf&quot;&gt;lamisil once ringworm&lt;/a&gt;  During The Daily Telegraph&apos;s investigation one consultant, Prabha Sivaraman, who worked for both private clinics and NHS hospitals in Manchester, was recorded telling a woman: &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t ask questions. If you want a termination, you want a termination.&amp;rdquo;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://theglobalelite.org/medicon-india-2017-69bc.pdf#bewail&quot;&gt;medicon india mira road&lt;/a&gt;  A dentist acted legally when he fired an assistant because he had grown too attracted to her and worried he would try to start an extramarital affair, the Iowa Supreme Court reaffirmed Friday in its second crack at the controversial case.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lovemycase.com/vitaros-australia-f2c2.pdf&quot;&gt;vitaros australia&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;We joke that you have to put a mirror under his nose,&quot; said Cardinals infielder Pete Descalso, who scored the game-winning run on Beltran&apos;s single, &quot;and check see if he&apos;s breathing. He&apos;s so calm, cool and relaxed.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ecorporationbd.com/kara-health-welfare-association-aaa8.pdf&quot;&gt;miss usa kara healthcare&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;Women wear at their ears for pendants as great wonders, glass bobs with narrow necks as these glasses have tails, and yet it is filled with several colours silks and coarse black cotton-wool, which to my sense is more difficult to put into these glass pendants, than liquor into these glass guns.&quot;
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
