<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542703495759">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">20.11.2018 08:44:55 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1woyg24vpxavd</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>My battery&apos;s about to run out &lt;a href=&quot;http://stsmihajlopupin.edu.rs/rs/silver-lined-teeth-3c56.pdf&quot;&gt;lined tee&lt;/a&gt;  Nearly every elected official of both parties in San Diego has called on Filner to resign as mayor of California&apos;s second-largest city, and a bipartisan campaign seeking his ouster through a recall election has been launched.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.wychwoodcabinetmakers.co.uk/customer-reviews-on-zenerx-e0f9.pdf&quot;&gt;free zenerx sample&lt;/a&gt;  Wind speeds up to 100 mph and torrential rains centered on the city of Sendai as the typhoon, dubbed Man-yi, hit the city about 160 miles north of Tokyo, causing severe flooding and mudslides throughout the area. A 72-year-old woman was found dead in the debris of her home after it had been demolished by a mudslide in Shiga prefecture. The public news service NHK says at least three people remain missing. Roughly 260,000 were forced to leave their homes in the popular tourist city of Kyoto.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.layeredonline.com/june-jacobs-spa-collection-dd54.pdf#pack&quot;&gt;june jacobs spa collection cranberry body balm review&lt;/a&gt;  Since Dominique Ansel unveiled his Cronut in May, chefs around the world have been coming up with their own Cronut-like concoctions, with some pretty imaginative names, such as âDoissants,â âCrognets,â âDough&apos;Ssantsâ and âCro-Nots.â And why not, when people are prepared to wait hours in long lines for the original. 
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://archieandtherug.com/boost-ultimate-purchase-9392.pdf&quot;&gt;boostultimate&lt;/a&gt;  And in some states, the legal protections only apply to corebenefits, leaving room for adjustments to future earned benefitson features. Many states already have increased employeecontribution rates, tightened age and tenure requirements forbenefits or reduced cost-of-living adjustments.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.weymouthskatepark.co.uk/feminax-shower-gel-6ae3.pdf#presented&quot;&gt;feminax in australia&lt;/a&gt;  The 39-year-old Swiss woman was raped while camping with herhusband in a forest in the central Indian state of MadhyaPradesh in mid-March. Three months earlier, a student wasgang-raped and beaten in a moving bus and thrown bleeding on tothe street in a case that triggered mass protests.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
