<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542358352189">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">16.11.2018 08:52:32 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.64g6adz9r15x</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I like watching football &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lovemycase.com/stmap_f2c20.html?levitra.fosamax.duloxetine&quot;&gt;oley medical associates gold jeffrey do&lt;/a&gt;  Last year, President Obama called the use of chemical weapons “a red line” that would change his thinking on American involvement in the brutal 2.5-year conflict that has killed more than 100,000.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cabanadolago.com.br/index.php/stmap_ab8a0.html?viagra.mesterolone.atenolol&quot;&gt;testorush rx and nitroxin side effects&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;My Seal team brothers said, &amp;#039;you stood the watch in the field for 20 years and you did a great job. I don&amp;#039;t understand it one bit but I support you 100% and I hope I can learn more about this and see you at the next reunion.&amp;#039;&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.elegantandwild.co.uk/stmap_75b30.html?cialis.lisinopril.imodium.forzest&quot;&gt;triadhealthcareinc.com/providers&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;As with any type of computer database and security, the weakest link is the person who&apos;s operating it,&quot; said Scott White, a professor of homeland security management at Drexel University in Philadelphia.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://zoeydeutch.net/stmap_8f080.html?revatio.aurogra.viagra&quot;&gt;swami samarth pharmatech&lt;/a&gt;  “It’s hard, you know,” he said. “Always, you put the uniform, there’s pressure. But you have to figure out how you can control that pressure. So that’s what I try to do all the time. I put the uniform (on) and there’s pressure, (but) I hope that we start hitting tomorrow.”
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.greenlamindustries.com/blog/stmap_0bae0.html?spiriva.sildenafil.viagra&quot;&gt;cytotec webmd&lt;/a&gt;  According the Choson Sinbo Online, the Tokyo-based media outlet that interviewed him, he has lost 23 kilograms (50 pounds) since his arrest and now weighs 71 kilograms (156 pounds). It said he was in poor physical shape even before his arrest, and that his liver ailments and back problems made it impossible for him to carry out hard labor.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
