<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542354552611">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">16.11.2018 07:49:12 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1tb785j5gwnw9</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>What do you like doing in your spare time? &lt;a href=&quot;https://paradiseinmexico.com.mx/stmap_c13c0.html?cialis.doxepin.tulasi.nizagara&quot;&gt;semenax benefits&lt;/a&gt;  Separately, engineers from Britain&apos;s Thomson Airways wereinspecting their own Boeing Dreamliner after it had to turn backduring a flight on Friday from Manchester in England to Sanfordin Florida because of an unspecified technical issue. ThomsonAirways is one of six European airlines owned by TUI Travel, the world&apos;s largest tour operator.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://muktiforum.com/stmap_b18b0.html?ciloxan.levitra.zofran&quot;&gt;famvir 250mg&lt;/a&gt;  In the past five years, products (food, drink and supplements) that want to carry a health claim have had to submit the evidence behind that claim to the EU&apos;s European Food Safety Authority (EFSA). More than 44,000 health claims were originally submitted, and only 248 have so far been approved by the EU. 
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tarokasongbad.com/stmap_e3c40.html?valacyclovir.cilostazol.cialis&quot;&gt;menshealth.com/spud&lt;/a&gt;  In Kenya, military spokesman Maj. Emmanuel Chirchir on Saturday confirmed the names of four fighters implicated in the Westgate Mall attack last month. Chirchir named the attackers as Abu Baara al-Sudani, Omar Nabhan, Khattab al-Kene and Umayr, names that were first broadcast by a local Kenyan television station.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://stsmihajlopupin.edu.rs/rs/stmap_3c560.html?cialis.micardis.indomethacin&quot;&gt;teva generic salmeterol&lt;/a&gt;  Abe is likely to skip visiting the Yasukuni Shrine to war dead, where people convicted as war criminals by an Allied tribunal are also honored. But he may make the offering through a representative of his Liberal Democratic Party (LDP), Japanese media said.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.klevermedia.co.uk/stmap_31f10.html?albendazole.antabuse.cialis&quot;&gt;custom made medicine cabinets&lt;/a&gt;  The move also signals the demise in Japan of a technology inwhich TV makers once invested heavily but has now been overtakenby advances in the liquid crystal display (LCD) business. Plasmadisplay TVs accounted for less than 6 percent of globalshipments in 2012, compared with 87 percent for LCD TVs,according to research firm DisplaySearch.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
