<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542568734342">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 19:18:54 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1sr237ggpt53d</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Would you like a receipt? &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.wychwoodcabinetmakers.co.uk/prescription-drugs-from-israel-e0f9.pdf&quot;&gt;flu rx drugs&lt;/a&gt;  About half of all smartphone users don&apos;t bother to use current screen-locking technology because of the inconvenience of keying in multiple-digit passwords. Apple is betting users may be far more willing to avail themselves of a solution that requires a single finger-swipe.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.proguaru.com.br/customedica-pharmacy-eagle-idaho-7684.pdf#academic&quot;&gt;customedica pharmacy eagle eagle id&lt;/a&gt;  The endangered perch-like fish called the Okaloosa Darter was downgraded in 2011 to threatened after Eglin Air Force base restored its watershed with erosion control projects, according to the U.S. Fish and Wildlife Service.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tarokasongbad.com/kadmedcom-e3c4.pdf#admission&quot;&gt;ramospharma.com.br&lt;/a&gt;  Louisiana&apos;s school voucher program has become a political flashpoint, with congressional Republicans this week joining critics of the Justice Department&apos;s lawsuit, which seeks to block Louisiana from issuing new tuition vouchers in some districts still under desegregation orders. Former Florida Gov. Jeb Bush, a Republican who has championed education reform efforts, joined Jindal in demanding the Justice Department back down.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.layeredonline.com/stendra-avanafil-in-italia-dd54.pdf&quot;&gt;avanafil cas no&lt;/a&gt;  AIG is the fifth-largest property and casualty insurer inthe United States with a market share of 4.52 percent, accordingto the National Association of Insurance Commissioners (NAIC), amulti-state insurance regulatory body.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.klevermedia.co.uk/verapamil-bodybuilding-31f1.pdf&quot;&gt;verapamil bodybuilding&lt;/a&gt;  Including the assumption of debt, the deal would valued atabout $4 billion. Under their agreement, AT&amp;T gets all of Leap&apos;sstock and about 5 million subscribers for $15 per share in cashor about $1.2 billion. As of April 15, Leap had $2.8 billion indebt, the companies said in a statement.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
