<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542657650880">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 20:00:50 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.kejqk880ut4a</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Where are you calling from? &lt;a href=&quot;https://virtual-operations.com/logan-pharmacy-herrin-il-92e2.pdf#masterpiece&quot;&gt;walgreens logan pharmacy hour wichita ks&lt;/a&gt;  The 67-year-old jeweler, Stephan Turk, was confined at home with an electronic bracelet after the shooting last week that left a teenage robber dead in the street outside Turk&apos;s jewelry story in the French Riviera city of Nice. An accomplice escaped on a motorbike as the body lay in the street.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.wychwoodcabinetmakers.co.uk/4-rivers-pharmacy-e0f9.pdf&quot;&gt;3 rivers pharmacy muskogee&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;We’ve got a long way to go before that but you certainly see them being in the postseason. If there is a next time, it may be a little bit easier because it was somewhat of an emotional week. It can be a little bit draining.”
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ecorporationbd.com/arthrosoothe-ingredients-aaa8.pdf#indolent&quot;&gt;arthrosoothe dietary supplement&lt;/a&gt;  The growing attention paid to Japanese fashion overseas, helped by live Internet streaming of many Fashion Week events, allows it to fulfill a key role in providing a showcase for younger designers. Of the 37 brands showing in Tokyo, five were making their Fashion Week debut.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://reflectiveteens.com/pharexhealthcom-213a.pdf&quot;&gt;pharexhealth.com&lt;/a&gt;  Traditionally, vaccines are administered via injection but opening up needle-free, particularly mucosal routes, is valuable because it can enhance patient compliance and facilitate the induction of stronger immune responses at the site of infection.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://paradiseinmexico.com.mx/landis-pharmacy-telford-hours-c13c.pdf&quot;&gt;landis pharmacy telford pa&lt;/a&gt;  Friday&apos;s attacks came in the wake of nationwide celebrations after the Afghan soccer team won the South Asian Football Federation Championship on Wednesday. The win produced a rare moment of national unity in this ethnically divided country, and euphoric Afghans poured into the streets to express their joy over the victory.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
