<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542672756142">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">20.11.2018 00:12:36 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.qrn7xw1sdpcy</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I want to report a  &lt;a href=&quot;https://newscvm.com/lowcostpharmacycom-e9bb.pdf&quot;&gt;lowcostpharmacy.com&lt;/a&gt;  Rehema Katusime knows this contrast as well as anyone. She was breastfeeding her 1-year-old daughter, Amina, in a bed in the university’s study ward. Three days earlier, on a Tuesday, Katusime had brought Amina to the clinic because she was vomiting, feverish, and had an unusual dark yellow color to her urine. Amina tested positive for malaria and qualified for the study, which provided her with the antimalarial drug Coartem. By Friday afternoon, Amina’s temperature had receded and she was keeping down her food. Katusime expressed her happiness at Amina’s recovery.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://muv.asia/pharmacy-innovations-houston-bf28.pdf&quot;&gt;pharmacy innovations folcroft pa&lt;/a&gt;  After landing, the craft will release a radio-controlled rover that will take pictures and dig out samples of the surface. These samples will be tested and the results transmitted back to Earth, but the Chang’e 3 rover will remain on the lunar surface. China is expected to launch another rover in the coming years and an eventual manned mission is expected to bring any rover samples to Earth.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://kssgrp.com/generic-ventolin-canada-5457.pdf#script&quot;&gt;generic ventolin canada&lt;/a&gt;  State representative Martin Walsh and Councilor John Connolly, both Democrats, took the top two spots in the city&apos;s non-partisan first-round vote, and will face off in November in the general election to succeed the city&apos;s longest-serving mayor, Thomas Menino.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.greenlamindustries.com/blog/does-diflucan-kill-all-candida-0bae.pdf#blast&quot;&gt;does diflucan kill all candida&lt;/a&gt;  They that go down to the sea in ships, that do business in great waters; these see the works of the Lord, and his wonders in the deep. Those two verses from Psalm 107 could almost be the pitch for Paul Wright&amp;rsquo;s debut feature, For Those In Peril, in which a young man who has seen those terrors first-hand returns to shore with his soul melted.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://archieandtherug.com/kroger-pharmacy-pages-order-refills-9392.pdf#before&quot;&gt;can you give away prescription drugs&lt;/a&gt;  The oceans are warming because of heat from a build-up of greenhouse gases in the atmosphere. Fertilizers and sewage that wash into the oceans can cause blooms of algae that reduce oxygen levels in the waters. And carbon dioxide in the air can form a weak acid when it reacts with sea water.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
