<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542571702922">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 20:08:22 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1xk2x5vh50d1f</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>We&apos;re at university together &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tarokasongbad.com/ou-acheter-le-clomid-e3c4.pdf#arrangement&quot;&gt;acheter du clomid sans ordonnance&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;I know his name has been surfacing out there,&quot; Woodson said in Las Vegas, where New York has a summer league team competing. &quot;I can coach any player. I coached guys from 18-, 19-, 20-year-old young men, and built a team in Atlanta, and that&apos;s tough for a first-time coach. So I experienced that, and I don&apos;t think there&apos;s a player I can&apos;t coach if he&apos;s willing to be coached. ... If anybody comes to this team, they&apos;ve got to understand it&apos;s all about team, man. It&apos;s not about individuals here, it&apos;s not about me as a coach. It&apos;s about the New York franchise trying to win an NBA title. If you understand that, then we&apos;ve got a chance.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.haroldwhitefuneraldirectors.co.uk/proactivehealthcoin-bd82.pdf#fixed&quot;&gt;herbalforhealth.co.in&lt;/a&gt;  When Seamus returned to his hometown after winning the Nobel Prize, Sean Brown presented him with a painting of Lough Beg, and the celebration, organized by Brown, was noteworthy because everybody, Protestant and Catholic alike, turned out to greet a local boy made good.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.artistparama.com/berkesan-ke-proextender-5168.pdf&quot;&gt;berkesan ke proextender&lt;/a&gt;  The Texas measure would change standards for abortion clinics in ways that opponents say would cause dozens of the facilities to shut down, forcing Texans to turn to illegal, unsafe means. Bill supporters disagree that clinics would have to close.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.anupamdebashisroy.com/brighthealthplancommedicare-f2ef.pdf#heavily&quot;&gt;jobs.leonmedicalcenters.com&lt;/a&gt;  Ali (17-0) eventually took a unanimous decision to extend his unblemished record inside the Cushman &amp; Wakefield Theater, but was flattened at the first round bell by challenger Jay Krupp (17-6), who jogged excitedly to the neutral corner in celebration.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.greenlamindustries.com/blog/buy-rogaine-foam-in-stores-0bae.pdf&quot;&gt;where to buy women&apos;s rogaine in canada&lt;/a&gt;  Zeman&amp;#8217;s appointment of his own economic advisor to head a cabinet of technocrats drew accusations from the outgoing finance minister that he was becoming &amp;#8220;Putinesque&amp;#8221; in wanting to develop a semi-presidential system.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
