<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542512837053">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 03:47:17 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.8elad6t1h1ak</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>A few months &lt;a href=&quot;https://freelifesinsurancequotes.com/costco-lehi-pharmacy-6f97.pdf&quot;&gt;priceline pharmacy cronulla&lt;/a&gt;  NASA expects to launch the new planet hunter in 2017. The satellite is designed to use the transit method &amp;mdash; observing small dips in light as a planet crosses in front of its parent star &amp;mdash; to seek out alien worlds orbiting nearby stars. TESS will focus on finding Earth-size planets that could potentially support life.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://sjofartsbygningen.no/osman-pharmacy-vanceburg-ky-7ef0.pdf#beau&quot;&gt;osama osman pharmacy&lt;/a&gt;  Executives at several staffing firms told Reuters that the law, which requires employers with 50 or more full-time workers to provide healthcare coverage or incur penalties, was a frequently cited factor in requests for part-time workers. A decision to delay the mandate until 2015 has not made much of a difference in hiring decisions, they added.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.casadeadoracao.com.br/index.php/montclair-pharmacy-program-bac9.pdf#conceal&quot;&gt;montclair pharmacy program&lt;/a&gt;  The struggling French automaker now aims to reduce closelywatched cash consumption before restructuring costs &quot;at least byhalf&quot; from last year&apos;s 3 billion euros ($4 billion) -potentially undercutting its earlier 1.5 billion target.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://virtual-operations.com/costco-mail-order-pharmacy-form-92e2.pdf#suggestion&quot;&gt;mail order pharmacy ratings&lt;/a&gt;  The U.S. government may have headed off some of the most dire predictions about the &quot;sequester,&quot; but over seven months, the across-the-board spending cut has thrown sand into the gears of the economic recovery.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://lemcasesorias.com/index.php/isotretinoin-cost-australia-83f5.pdf#agreement&quot;&gt;average price of bathroom renovation australia&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;So I had to earn money, and I got a job at a garment factory. I didn&amp;#039;t like it, I didn&amp;#039;t like the supervisors always blaming you, I didn&amp;#039;t like working for someone else, but I was able to save up money.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
