<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542636696882">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 14:11:36 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.130ql5affygsl</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Are you a student? &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ascfinancialadvisers.co.uk/hyzaar-drugscom-5553.pdf&quot;&gt;hyzaar drugs.com&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;At this time we believe that Mr. Alexis entered Building 197 at the Navy Yard with a shotgun; we do not have any information at this time that he had an AR-15 in his possession,&quot; she said during an afternoon news briefing. &quot;We also believe Mr. Alexis may have gained access to a handgun once inside the facility and after he began shooting.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ascfinancialadvisers.co.uk/bupropion-hcl-xl-300-mg-tablet-picture-5553.pdf#raymond&quot;&gt;bupropion hcl xl 300 mg tablet picture&lt;/a&gt;  Budenholzer refused a breath test but agreed to a field sobriety test, according to the report. He told Nelms he had only one glass of wine and that he finished the glass about 15 minutes before being pulled over. Nelms said in the report that Budenholzer was &quot;polite&quot; and that his speech patterns were mumbled, slow and slurred.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cabanadolago.com.br/index.php/lloydspharmacy-clinical-homecare-harlow-ab8a.pdf#palm&quot;&gt;lloydspharmacy online doctor&lt;/a&gt;  Starting Thursday, however, three major cruise lines will begin posting crime statistics on their websites. The companies voluntarily sharing the information with customers will be Royal Caribbean, Carnival and Norwegian cruises.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://newscvm.com/anavar-euro-generic-e9bb.pdf&quot;&gt;anavar euro generic&lt;/a&gt;  U.S. Defense Secretary Chuck Hagel called Egyptian armychief General Abdel Fattah al-Sisi to tell him about the U.S.decisions, speaking for about 40 minutes in what one U.S.official described as a friendly conversation.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://newscvm.com/simmondsia-chinensis-jojoba-seed-oil-e9bb.pdf&quot;&gt;simmondsia chinensis (jojoba) seed oil&lt;/a&gt;  Panasonic is pulling away from unprofitable consumer electronics and wants to be number one in appliances, pitting the company against the likes of Whirlpool Corp and Electrolux. It also wants to tap into growing demand in emerging markets in Europe, particularly Russia.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
