<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542532251749">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 09:10:51 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.vb7txyu7jrky</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Sorry, I&apos;m busy at the moment &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mcmpovos.com/wwwnorthcoastmedcom-62bd.pdf#flannel&quot;&gt;health.jeancoutu.com&lt;/a&gt;  Joe Biden, the vice president, is second at 8%, followed by Massachusetts Gov. Deval Patrick (5%), Newark Mayor and New Jersey senatorial candidate Cory Booker (2%), and New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo (1%). Nineteen percent are undecided.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.klevermedia.co.uk/m-stak-amazon-31f1.pdf&quot;&gt;animal m stak and stak combo&lt;/a&gt;  Hedge fund TCI has asked EADS to transfer its 4 billion eurostake in Dassault Aviation directly to shareholders aspart of its campaign to force the group to sell the asset,Financial Times reported, citing a letter sent by TCI to EADSChief Executive Tom Enders.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cabanadolago.com.br/index.php/el-viagra-es-de-venta-libre-en-chile-ab8a.pdf&quot;&gt;how do you know if viagra is fake&lt;/a&gt;  A revamped design process helped give Delta what it wanted. Alur&apos;s designs are in Marlin&apos;s computer system. He can email them to Delta, share them with the four other design engineers at Marlin, or tweak a design and instantly see how the changes work. \&quot;They&apos;ve reordered a couple of times,\&quot; he says.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://lemcasesorias.com/index.php/axiom-pharma-products-83f5.pdf&quot;&gt;om pharma lisbonne&lt;/a&gt;  Smaller companies are both more levered to growth and less able to withstand temporary slowdowns than their larger peers. There is also the possibility that smaller companies are more likely to be the beneficiaries of government support for research, be they defense technology companies or biotech firms.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.elegantandwild.co.uk/harga-obat-digest-lansoprazole-75b3.pdf#chase&quot;&gt;achat lansoprazole&lt;/a&gt;  Bolivia, which offers free healthcare to its older citizens despite being one of the poorest surveyed countries, and Sri Lanka, with its long-term investments in health and education, were among those singled out for praise.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
