<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542694629131">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">20.11.2018 06:17:09 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.9pc1xnhozgoh</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>How many are there in a book? &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.haroldwhitefuneraldirectors.co.uk/prijs-augmentin-875-bd82.pdf&quot;&gt;augmentin cena zawiesina&lt;/a&gt;  The second track of Jay-Z&apos;s new album, &quot;Magna Carta Holy Grail,&quot; is titled &quot;Picasso Baby,&quot; but his allusions to late neo-expressionist artist Jean-Michel Basquiat within the song may be a more striking comparison for the rapper. &quot;I&apos;m the new Jean-Michel,&quot; Jay-Z raps, which is one of the multiple times Basquiat is referenced on the song. Even Jay-Z&apos;s collaborators give a shout-out to the artist elsewhere on the album (&quot;I hope my black skin don&apos;t dirt this white tuxedo/ Before the Basquiat show,&quot; Frank Ocean sings on &quot;Oceans&quot;). It&apos;s an allusion that Jay-Z has made for years.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://zoeydeutch.net/doctor-hillcom-8f08.pdf&quot;&gt;doctor-hill.com/iol-main/keratorefractive-calculator&lt;/a&gt;  WHAT THIS ESSENTIALLY ASKS THE JUDGE RECUSE HERSELF FROM THE CASE, FROM THE HERNANDEZ TRIAL, BECAUSE IN A PRIOR MURDER CASE INVOLVING THE SAME PROSECUTOR, THAT COULD WOULD BE ASSISTANT DISTRICT ATTORNEY WILLIAM McCALLEY, THEY ARGUE THIS JUDGE EXHIBITED ANTAGONISM AND BIAS TOWARDS THE PROSECUTION THROUGHOUT THE CASE.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://zoeydeutch.net/pioglitcom-8f08.pdf&quot;&gt;testosteron-bestellen.com&lt;/a&gt;  Many Egyptians are in no mood to listen to outside voices, particularly from a country like the US, which some argue has contributed to the current political dysfunction. This is a realization that appears to include the Egyptian army, the most powerful institution in the country and one that continues to arrest those supportive of Brotherhood in the name of national security.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sarah-hyland.net/can-i-get-cialis-at-walmart-79a8.pdf#shoot&quot;&gt;acheter cialis en ligne pas cher&lt;/a&gt;  Denis, a veteran antitrust lawyer who once worked in the Justice Department&apos;s antitrust division, represented Medco Health Solutions in securing clearance for the company&apos;s $29.1 billion merger with Express Scripts last year.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://leotoys.cl/prix-lamotrigine-2206.pdf#communicate&quot;&gt;lamotrigine bestellen&lt;/a&gt;  Actually next week we&amp;#8217;re going to be rolling out more information about how we get there and what are the hardware opportunities that we see for bringing Linux into the living room, and potentially pointing further down the road to how we can get it even more unified in mobile.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
