<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542662805315">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 21:26:45 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1njqh6tdod26q</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>perfect design thanks &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.proguaru.com.br/hotdealmartcom-7684.pdf&quot;&gt;eu-tablets.net&lt;/a&gt;  Her final destination was Bab al-Aziza, Gaddafi&apos;s fortress in Tripoli. She was lead to the basement and was shown a small, mirrored room that was hers. Summoned upstairs in the middle of the night, Soraya found another woman, Amal, gyrating to a Bedouin song for Gaddafi&apos;s pleasure..
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.greenlamindustries.com/blog/medinetcommy-0bae.pdf#reservoir&quot;&gt;dnahealthcorp.com&lt;/a&gt;  For the first time in the nine years the spacecraft had been in orbit, Earth’s inhabitants knew that their photos would be taken and came out to take part in “The Day that the Earth Smiled.” Scientists knew this and a social media campaign had been waged in the weeks prior, urging Earthlings to participate in the worldwide event.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://virtual-operations.com/wwwbuyallmedsnowbiz-erfahrungen-92e2.pdf#little&quot;&gt;www.buy.allmedsnow.biz erfahrungen&lt;/a&gt;  Powerful computer models, first developed by the three scientists in the 1970s, offer a new window onto such reactions and have become a mainstay for researchers in thousands of academic and industrial laboratories around the world.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.anupamdebashisroy.com/phytopharmaceuticals-for-brain-health-f2ef.pdf&quot;&gt;use of phytopharmaceutical products&lt;/a&gt;  Assistant District Attorney William McCauley announced in court that he planned to file a motion asking Judge Susan Garsh to set aside due to her history with McCauley from a previous case. In a memorandum to support of the motion, prosecutors wrote, “Unfortunately the lead prosecutor and the trial judge currently assigned to this case have a well-known and publicly documented history of antagonism – a history that has, in the past, generated broad public comment and concern.”
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://virtual-operations.com/healthlanecommy-92e2.pdf&quot;&gt;healthlane.com.my&lt;/a&gt;  The Beaufort Regional Chamber of Commerce, in South Carolina, has paid the Rhoads Group $190,000 since 2006 to help ensure “East Coast basing of F-35 mission.” In December 2010, the Pentagon announced its decision to base five F-35 squadrons at Marine Corps Air Station Beaufort. Senator Lindsey Graham, a beneficiary of Lockheed campaign contributions, issued a statement that said, “Christmas came early this year.”
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
