<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542671001262">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 23:43:21 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.b85vvsfw1h1l</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>How many weeks&apos; holiday a year are there? &lt;a href=&quot;http://stsmihajlopupin.edu.rs/rs/cardizem-cd-drugscom-3c56.pdf#lease&quot;&gt;cardizem cd drugs.com&lt;/a&gt;  &amp;ldquo;Referendums like this are a once in a generation event, which means the vote on September 18th next year will be the opportunity of a lifetime for many people in Scotland, as we get the chance to choose our country&amp;rsquo;s future.&amp;rdquo;
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cabanadolago.com.br/index.php/ky-jelly-uk-ab8a.pdf&quot;&gt;ky jelly uk&lt;/a&gt;  The defending Emmy champ in that category, Showtime&apos;s domestic terrorism thriller &quot;Homeland,&quot; also has a chance, although critics say its second season did not hit the surprising high notes of its first year, while HBO&apos;s slick medieval fantasy &quot;Game of Thrones&quot; has its share of buzz and 16 nominations overall.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://newscvm.com/medical-one-sunshine-e9bb.pdf#eventful&quot;&gt;medical one liners&lt;/a&gt;  The jealous former husband who attacked his ex-wife and her new boyfriend with a machete and pocket knife Sunday morning allegedly cut the tip of his former wife&apos;s nose off before slitting his own wrists, prosecutors said.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lovemycase.com/best-place-to-buy-viagra-online-in-uk-f2c2.pdf&quot;&gt;buy viagra pills uk&lt;/a&gt;  Equities have been tethered to Fed policy for much of theyear with the S&amp;P currently less than 1 percent away from itsall-time high. Many traders are awaiting clarity on when theFed&apos;s $85 billion a month asset purchasing program could beginto slow before adjusting positions.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.greenlamindustries.com/blog/cipro-500-mg-recommended-dosage-0bae.pdf#attribute&quot;&gt;cipro dosage kidney infection&lt;/a&gt;  “We were talking about the difference between a policy — a policy — that protects constitutional rights while keeping us safe, versus a policy that doesn’t protect constitutional rights. The American ideal is based on really doing something tougher than is done all around the world. Of really protecting people’s individual liberties while keeping law and order, and so that’s what he (Baldwin) was talking about,” he said. “I think there’s a very insightful, or a historical analysis he was offering.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
