<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542561573264">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 17:19:33 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.9kc3ns66eb82</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Can I call you back? &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.techdesighn.com/vigour-300-gold-side-effects-b26f.pdf&quot;&gt;vigour 300 for sale&lt;/a&gt;  Oct 17 (Reuters) - IBM Corp has reassigned the headof its growth markets unit, a source with knowledge of the movesaid, after a surprisingly steep drop in quarterly hardwaresales in China prompted a 7 percent share slide on Thursday.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://leotoys.cl/nworld-products-set-2206.pdf#structure&quot;&gt;nworld products description&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;We represent one of Gennady Timchenko&apos;s companies, Airfix Aviation,&quot; Patton Boggs partner Laurence Harris wrote in a May email, seen by Reuters, in which he requested a meeting with the U.S. government official. &quot;We know you have concerns about Gennady. We&apos;d like to talk to you about this.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://stsmihajlopupin.edu.rs/rs/bestgenericmedsnet-review-3c56.pdf&quot;&gt;bestgenericmeds.net betrouwbaar&lt;/a&gt;  Back in 2007, when Nintendo&apos;s Wii was the current object of techno-lust, US radio station KDND promised listeners a free console for whoever could drink the most water on-air. The contest, entitled &quot;Hold Your Wee for a Wii,&quot; resulted in the death of the winner from water intoxication.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.proguaru.com.br/medishieldlifesgcalculator-7684.pdf#five&quot;&gt;medishieldlife.sg/calculator&lt;/a&gt;  The U.S. International Trade Commission in June banned the import or sale of the iPhone 4, iPhone 3GS, iPad 3G and iPad 2 3G distributed by AT&amp;T Inc, saying the devices infringed a patent owned by the South Korean electronics giant.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://archieandtherug.com/skelaxin-drug-interactions-ibuprofen-9392.pdf#unfair&quot;&gt;skelaxin medication pain&lt;/a&gt;  Culinary tome The Modernist Cuisine features &quot;Romaine lettuce infused sous vide with liquid hickory smoke&quot; in a burger recipe. David Chang, founder of Momofuku, makes &quot;smoked eggs&quot; by soaking hardboiled and peeled eggs overnight in a water bath containing a dash of liquid smoke. And Byron Parsons, from South African liquid smoke company Smoked Potjie, shares some creative uses for liquid smoke he&apos;s come across: &quot;A blogger used some in an onion marmalade, a caterer made a smoky cardamom ice cream, and a fellow exhibitor at a show used it to make cocktails.&quot;
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
