<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542547422055">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 13:23:42 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.xe4xnrh8f145</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>What&apos;s the last date I can post this to  to arrive in time for Christmas? &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lovemycase.com/bugs-away-spray-f2c2.pdf&quot;&gt;bugs away spray 8 oz&lt;/a&gt;  He has yet to live down accusations that he purposefully slowed the police response to the 2002 Gujarat riots to allow Hindus to vent their anger on the state&amp;#39;s Muslims, even though he was cleared of wrongdoing by a court-appointed special investigation team.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://lemcasesorias.com/index.php/adding-abilify-to-effexor-xr-83f5.pdf#bathroom&quot;&gt;buy cheap abilify&lt;/a&gt;  Nearly 150,000 devotees gathered to celebrate the holy festival of Dussehra at the Ratangarh temple, in a forest outside the town of Datia, 390 km (240 miles) north of the Madhya Pradesh state capital, Bhopal.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://stsmihajlopupin.edu.rs/rs/lamictal-overdose-400mg-3c56.pdf#capable&quot;&gt;lamictal for depression user reviews&lt;/a&gt;  Southeast Asian allies involved in the dispute had hopedthat Obama&apos;s participation could provide &quot;geopolitical ballast&quot;to convince China to abide by the new code, Ernest Bower, chairfor Southeast Asia Studies at the Center for Strategic andInternational Studies, told reporters earlier this week.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://lemcasesorias.com/index.php/tqpharmacom-83f5.pdf&quot;&gt;localhealth.io&lt;/a&gt;  U.S. crude oil futures for December delivery fell 51cents to $97.79. The November futures, the previous front-monthcontract, expired on Tuesday after hitting a low of $97.50, itsweakest since July 1.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://virtual-operations.com/medicactivcom-92e2.pdf&quot;&gt;exerciseprescription.com.au&lt;/a&gt;  Although equities showed resilience on Tuesday on hopes thefirst partial shutdown of the U.S. government in 17 years wouldbe short-lived, just one day later concerns about the economicimpact grew as no signs emerged of an end to the budget standoffin Washington.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
