<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542571113943">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 19:58:33 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.jh5qge66s7fw</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Have you read any good books lately? &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.haroldwhitefuneraldirectors.co.uk/cefuroxime-goodrx-bd82.pdf&quot;&gt;cefuroxime goodrx&lt;/a&gt;  In November of last year, the UN General Assembly passed a motion to upgrade Palestine to &amp;#8220;non-member observer state&amp;#8221;. Israel, the United States and a number of other countries voted against this new status.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.chris-cancercommunity.com/dolce-vita-synthesia-b01a.pdf&quot;&gt;dolce vita synonym&lt;/a&gt;  Ok great. I was willing to give the GOP the benefit of the doubt, and thought it was only a few hard-liners who would have our country default on our debt. Now I understand that it is the entire Republican party&amp;#8217;s plan.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://accentresurfacing.com/zydena-al-4110.pdf&quot;&gt;zydena&lt;/a&gt;  France&amp;#039;s finance minister Pierre Moscovici has been speaking to the BBC&amp;#039;s Andrew Walker. He says he won&amp;#039;t stand for &quot;France-bashing&quot;. The economy is getting better, he says, and reforms to pensions and the labour market will make France &quot;more competitive, more creative&quot;.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cabanadolago.com.br/index.php/zinzino-ab8a.pdf#officer&quot;&gt;zinzino&lt;/a&gt;  A more significant date may be 2016, when the opposition hasa chance to demand a referendum to try and recall Maduro. Thatmeasure is allowed under the constitution halfway through apresidential term, if some 3.8 million signatures are gathered.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.casadeadoracao.com.br/index.php/buy-online-drugs-australia-bac9.pdf#tail&quot;&gt;is it legal to mail order prescription drugs from canada&lt;/a&gt;  In 1940, Charlie Chaplin&apos;s The Great Dictator condemned a growing threat in the world. Parts of Chaplin&apos;s stirring speech are especially relevant today - the era of technology&apos;s ability to sift through big data for personal identifiers: &quot;Machinery that gives abundance has left us in want,&quot; Chaplin said. &quot;More than machinery we need humanity.&quot;
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
