<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1543416030519">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">28.11.2018 14:40:30 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1nif54h7kxh0p</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Hello good day &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ssvoverath.de/duphaston-yahoo-answer-c3db.pdf#pincers&quot;&gt;duphaston yahoo answer&lt;/a&gt;  Buehrle (12-9) held Boston to one run for the third time in five starts that he&apos;s faced them this year. He allowed five hits, striking out five without walking a batter. He reached 200 innings for the 13th straight season.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.purplecreativedesign.co.uk/costco-modesto-pharmacy-hours-5884.pdf#noon&quot;&gt;how to report someone selling prescription drugs&lt;/a&gt;  The Congressional Budget Office has said it expects thegovernment&apos;s annual deficit to shrink to $642 billion in thefiscal year that ends this month, the first annual deficit below$1 trillion in five years.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://starbizzcon.com/vitargo-protein-shake-45db.pdf&quot;&gt;scitec vitargo reviews&lt;/a&gt;  3. Have your own separate lives outside the office. Just because you are running a business together doesn&apos;t mean you have to spend every waking hour together. Give yourselves space to breathe and make sure you spend time with other people who have nothing to do with the company.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.purplecreativedesign.co.uk/vitality-max-labs-forskolin-5884.pdf#bustle&quot;&gt;vitality max&lt;/a&gt;  Spain has justified the current extra border checks by claiming Gibraltar is not doing enough to combat cigarette smuggling. The UK says the lengthy delays are causing frustration and harm to the territory&amp;#8217;s economy.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.aicpuglia.it/prix-hyzaar-2397.pdf&quot;&gt;prix hyzaar&lt;/a&gt;  British lawmakers are investigating the UK-based mining and oil sector, with a probe expected to touch on areas including transparency and disclosure after shareholder battles and corruption investigations at mining companies like ENRC have left investors nursing heavy losses.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
