<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1543402057485">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">28.11.2018 10:47:37 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.10vhofk6eidic</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Have you read any good books lately? &lt;a href=&quot;http://public-admin.co.uk/befar-cream-australia-3c8d.pdf&quot;&gt;befar cream australia&lt;/a&gt;  From January to June, the total number of foreign visitors, including business travelers and residents, entering China declined by 5 percent to just under 13 million compared with the same period last year, according to the China National Tourism Administration. Overall, visitors from Asia, Australia, Europe and the Americas all declined.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://tynerblain.com/blog/can-novo-trazodone-get-you-high-ef2c.pdf&quot;&gt;trazodone and alcohol side effects&lt;/a&gt;  Thank you. And Jonathan thanks for the detail on the guidance. That’s really helpful. But I guess my question is probably for Pat or Carl, I mean, you have a lot going on at VMware and you went through a lot of it on the call, but vSphere, your core virtualization market product is still the majority of your business today. I realize it’s less so as time goes on, but if you had to characterize where you were in the x86 compute capacity that still need to be virtualized. Where might that be? I mean, there is a lot of talk that 70% to 75% of x86 workloads have been virtualized. And I think you come up with the numbers similar to that, but you don’t get paid based on the number of workloads that gets virtualized, you get paid based on the number of CPUs that gets virtualized or the number of – the amount of compute capacity. And I guess even roughly where that might be relative to that 70% to 75%?
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://pixelbedlam.co.uk/notting-hill-pharmacy-london-65ef.pdf#pre&quot;&gt;notting hill pharmacy w11&lt;/a&gt;  Customers at HSBC are among those known to be hit by the technical problems, though other lenders are also likely to have been effected. A spokesman for Barclays said the bank was &quot;not aware&quot; of any issues with payments to its customers.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sensors.co.uk/carols-pharmacy-9874.pdf&quot;&gt;carols pharmacy trinidad&lt;/a&gt;  Asiana Airlines said Sunday its reputation was damaged by a report on a San Francisco TV station that used bogus and racially offensive names for four pilots on its plane that crashed earlier this month and is considering legal action.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://teerandaz.com/oxsoralen-pharmacy2uk-131c.pdf&quot;&gt;oxsoralen pharmacy2uk&lt;/a&gt;  Catalan separatists are also watching closely a planned September 2014 Scottish referendum on independence from the United Kingdom, hoping it will promote the idea of self-determination for regions within European Union countries.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
