<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542586185729">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 00:09:45 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1tr4re4aac3ll</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Will I have to work on Saturdays? &lt;a href=&quot;https://muv.asia/big-jim-and-the-twins-joke-bf28.pdf#carpet&quot;&gt;big jim and the twins ingredients&lt;/a&gt;  Her words echoed the anguish vented across the country after the July 13 verdict sparked an emotional debate on race and Florida’s “Stand Your Ground” self-defense law that saw President Barack Obama chime in.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://reflectiveteens.com/pharmadrugorg-213a.pdf&quot;&gt;hicarepharma.com&lt;/a&gt;  Foreign Minister Elias Jaua suggested via Twitter that the probe was related to the financing of Capriles two presidential campaigns. In October, Capriles lost to long-time President Hugo Chavez, who died in March of cancer.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://reflectiveteens.com/storechurchhealthorg-213a.pdf#turpentine&quot;&gt;medproveins.com&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;Clearly capex on an individual operator basis is flat inEurope. It is not growing on an annualised basis. But thedirection of that spending is obviously moving more towards LTEthan 2G and 3G networks,&quot; Juggins said.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.proguaru.com.br/wwwmedfarmuuse-7684.pdf#insect&quot;&gt;www.media.medfarm.uu.se&lt;/a&gt;  The CDC could not be reached for additional informationabout the recurrences of infection because of the U.S. federalgovernment shutdown. Calls to CDC phones were answered byrecordings about furloughed workers.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.layeredonline.com/beaute-basics-brushes-dd54.pdf#excepting&quot;&gt;beaute basics brushes&lt;/a&gt;  Is there any celebrity left in Hollywood who hasn&apos;t flipped his or her lid (or a table) at one time or another? From the painfully public outbursts (yes, you, Mel Gibson), to the breakdowns you never saw coming, take a look at the biggest celebrity meltdowns in Tinseltown&apos;s tainted history ... Don&apos;t get on his bad side! NBA star Lamar Odom completely lost his cool with the paparazzi on July 10, 2013. After photographers tried taking his picture, Khloe Kardashian&amp;#146;s hubby trashed one cameraman&apos;s car by smashing it with a piece of metal, but not before he threw the contents of another photographer&apos;s vehicle into a busy street. Before things got heated, the the 33-year-old reportedly tried to reason with the paparazzi, saying, &quot;put your cameras down and let me talk to you man to man.&quot; Check out more of Odom&apos;s outburst ...
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
