<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1543408451401">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">28.11.2018 12:34:11 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.zk6p0ovqxay2</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I&apos;m sorry, I&apos;m not interested &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bombeirodf.com.br/does-vaso-ultra-give-permanent-results-50f8.pdf&quot;&gt;purchase vaso ultra&lt;/a&gt;  He said Caesar&apos;s had refinanced $4.5 billion in debt and hadraised $200 million worth of equity, some of which would be usedto service the remaining debt. &quot;As we&apos;ve done over the lastseveral years, we&apos;ll continue to work on that as the conditionsare appropriate.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.aicpuglia.it/musclemaxx-bars-2397.pdf#forepaws&quot;&gt;allmax musclemaxx bars&lt;/a&gt;  Rousseff, a pragmatic leftist, will not be easy to unseat.While she has not officially announced her candidacy forre-election in 2014, she currently leads polls by a healthymargin and has seen her popularity bounce back recently aftertaking a huge hit during the protests.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.purplecreativedesign.co.uk/prescriptionshoppecvphorg-5884.pdf&quot;&gt;rx-australia-hq.net&lt;/a&gt;  The company&apos;s cheese business grew 5 percent in the quarterto $945 million because of strong sales of Velveeta dinners andnatural cheese, while Kraft&apos;s beverage revenues fell 3.2 percentto $753 million, mostly because of lower coffee prices.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ssvoverath.de/buystratteraonlinenoprescriptionncom-c3db.pdf#champion&quot;&gt;miparafarmaciaonline.com&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;Angola&apos;s efforts to increase transparency and disclosurecould help ... but international investors are saying that thebusiness environment is getting tougher even for establishedcompanies,&quot; he added.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bombeirodf.com.br/ralphs-pharmacy-coupons-for-new-prescriptions-2013-50f8.pdf&quot;&gt;king soopers pharmacy drug prices&lt;/a&gt;  But in the end it was Rufus Norris, the insiders&amp;rsquo; front runner from the very start - and a man who is both an obvious choice for the most important job in British theatre and a bit of a gamble.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
