<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542514528037">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 04:15:28 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.3jdp4my7jxsb</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Have you got a telephone directory? &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mcmpovos.com/pentasa-czopki-cena-62bd.pdf&quot;&gt;pentasa custo&lt;/a&gt;  More moderate Senate Republicans disapproved of usingObamacare as a bargaining chip from the start, arguing that itbecause it is non-negotiable for Democrats, it would inevitablylead to a shutdown and sour voters on the Republican Party.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://virtual-operations.com/testosterone-max-xxl-gnc-92e2.pdf#jessie&quot;&gt;testosterone max xxl for sale&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;In short, beef is beef, whether the cattle were born in Montana, Manitoba, or Mazatlán,&quot; the lawsuit filed in federal court in Washington, D.C., said. &quot;The same goes for hogs, chickens, and other livestock.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cabanadolago.com.br/index.php/newerahealthbiz-ab8a.pdf#bin&quot;&gt;imedrix.com&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;You don&apos;t need decree powers to fight corruption. That&apos;s part of the &apos;show&apos; by Maduro to cover up his disaster of a government,&quot; opposition leader Henrique Capriles said on Twitter. &quot;It&apos;s certain he doesn&apos;t have the votes to approve it.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://theglobalelite.org/24tabscom-review-69bc.pdf#buffer&quot;&gt;24tabs.com review&lt;/a&gt;  Sometimes termed &quot;the invisible poor&quot; by demographers, lower-income whites are generally dispersed in suburbs as well as small rural towns, where more than 60 percent of the poor are white. Concentrated in Appalachia in the East, they are also numerous in the industrial Midwest and spread across America&apos;s heartland, from Missouri, Arkansas and Oklahoma up through the Great Plains.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.layeredonline.com/pristiq-wind-up-doll-dd54.pdf#tiring&quot;&gt;pristiq duration of action&lt;/a&gt;  Nothing in Washington is certain, but yes, a shutdown is almost assured if both sides continue on their current path. Most lawmakers across the Capitol &amp;#8212; including those who said only a few days ago they didn&amp;#8217;t think it was likely &amp;#8212; now believe a short-term shutdown is nearly certain. The bigger question is not whether the government will have a partial shutdown, but for how long? A short-term shutdown is the most likely outcome, perhaps a matter of hours or days.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
