<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542638976166">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 14:49:36 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1m33u0te0a9ot</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Are you a student? &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.haroldwhitefuneraldirectors.co.uk/deboralabscom-bd82.pdf&quot;&gt;deboralabs.com&lt;/a&gt;  In this sequence of photos released in April, a jet of gas spews from a massive black hole in the center of the M87 galaxy. The gas fades and brightens, with a peak that even outshines the galaxy&apos;s core. The outburst is coming from a blob of matter, dubbed HST-1, and scientists are so far at a loss to explain its weird behavior.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://contactconsultoria.com/index.php/pharmevo-private-limited-shahrah-e-faisal-road-karachi-a511.pdf#father&quot;&gt;pharmevo private limited pakistan&lt;/a&gt;  Morrisons reported a 10 percent drop in first-half profits,hit by its late entry into the online and convenience storemarkets and also cut its capital expenditure plans, as itsshifts spend to the new channels.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.infocalcbba.edu.bo/ashwagandha-cvs-9e88.pdf&quot;&gt;ashwagandha cvs&lt;/a&gt;  Donatella Versace told Italian newspaper Il Sole 24 Ore the firm was vetting offers from investors interested in buying a minority stake. A source said earlier this month the fashion house is looking to sell a stake of up to 20 percent, valuing the group at more than 1.2 billion euros ($1.6 billion).
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://virtual-operations.com/inlovewithhealthcom-92e2.pdf#sober&quot;&gt;nchealthplansguru.com&lt;/a&gt;  Since 1946, when Britain built its last full-length runway at what is now Heathrow, successive governments have been stuck in a holding pattern on where to put the next one. So, maybe it is helpful for the body charged with finally making a decision that several submissions eschew any need for new landing strips.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.casadeadoracao.com.br/index.php/247overnightpharmacycom-reviews-bac9.pdf#bradley&quot;&gt;247overnightpharmacy.com reviews&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;One thing we know about this president, he is as stubborn as hell,&quot; said Gehad El-Haddad, a Brotherhood member whose father Essam El-Haddad, a British-trained doctor, was Mursi&apos;s politically moderate top foreign policy adviser and is now in detention with him.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
