<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1543410406813">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">28.11.2018 13:06:46 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.6urirkwl8reb</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Recorded Delivery &lt;a href=&quot;http://starbizzcon.com/restaid-reviews-45db.pdf#area&quot;&gt;restaid&lt;/a&gt;  A spokesman for Aberdeen Coastguard. said the Aberdeen, Peterhead and Fraserburgh lifeboats had been launched to take part in the search and RAF Sea King helicopter had also been scrambled from RAF Lossiemouth.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://oktandrammen.no/drammen-ny/a-plus-waterproofing-e52c.pdf&quot;&gt;a plus waterproofing louisville ky&lt;/a&gt;  A severe thunderstorm with a 71-mph wind gust measured at Nellis Air Force Base swept across the Las Vegas Valley on Friday evening, causing heavy damage in places, stranding drivers in flash floods, snapping power poles and tearing trees from the ground.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.purplecreativedesign.co.uk/floronetcom-5884.pdf#ill&quot;&gt;sandaoil.com&lt;/a&gt;  She decided to volunteer as a bomber pilot after her home was taken over by the invading Germans and her brother, Leonid, was killed at the front: &amp;ldquo;He was 20 and had never even kissed a girl,&amp;rdquo; she recalled. &amp;ldquo;My mother sobbed, &apos;That damn Hitler.&amp;rsquo; I saw the German aircraft flying along our roads filled with people who were leaving their homes, firing at them with their machine guns... they blasted our school.&amp;rdquo;
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://worldnewsnetwork.co.in/xtend-life-vitamins-walmart-08d2.pdf#newspaper&quot;&gt;xtend life total balance multivitamin&lt;/a&gt;  Anti-Google graffiti has turned up here, and activists recently held a small anti-gentrification rally at which they smashed a Google bus piñata. Last year, a Google bus driver was caught on video threatening a bystander for photographing a shuttle blocking city buses and bicyclists.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://teerandaz.com/xenia-custom-pharmacy-aurora-co-131c.pdf#champagne&quot;&gt;xenia custom pharmacy llc aurora co&lt;/a&gt;  Apple reached out two to three years ago to Microlatch, an Australian company, to license and test its peripheral fingerprint sensors. Apple asked it to build a Bluetooth connection to the phone and accompanying software, Microlatch managing director and founder Chris Burke said, so Apple could gauge user reactions and habits, particularly in e-commerce strongholds like China.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
