<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542564748726">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 18:12:28 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1n55havwcoin0</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>How many weeks&apos; holiday a year are there? &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.casadeadoracao.com.br/index.php/walgreens-lafayette-square-pharmacy-hours-bac9.pdf#see&quot;&gt;barclay square pharmacy sunnyside&lt;/a&gt;  Sen. Jeff Sessions, R-Ala., top Republican on the Senate Budget Committee, and Rep. Paul Ryan, R-Wis., chairman of the House Budget Committee, had earlier revealed they&apos;d been told about the department&apos;s decision on XpressWest. The two lawmakers had been among the toughest critics of the project and loan, calling it &quot;costly, wasteful and risky.&quot; 
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://paradiseinmexico.com.mx/skinny-confidential-jaw-surgery-c13c.pdf&quot;&gt;skinny confidential gomi&lt;/a&gt;  People tend to promote in their own image, and with men still holding the majority of managerial positions, women are often being unfairly viewed as a more &amp;lsquo;risky&amp;rsquo; choice because they don&amp;rsquo;t necessarily display the same leadership traits at work as men, or they may display them in a different way. It is an uncomfortable truth that we are influenced by deep-held stereotypes and are therefore not as fair as we think we are. We are missing out on some key talent because of this.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.greenlamindustries.com/blog/prolatis-substitute-0bae.pdf#catching&quot;&gt;still get the original prolatis&lt;/a&gt;  âThe National Mall rally was unprecedented in its size but we will double and triple those numbers until Democrats and Republicans get together,â added Sarsour. âWe will continue doing this because we are tired of the lies, the deportations, the young people without opportunity to further their studies. We need something to happen this year and Republicans know it. And you know what? I think we will get it.â
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.elegantandwild.co.uk/1-physique-enhancing-science-erase-pro-30-caps-75b3.pdf&quot;&gt;physique enhancing science erase pro 30 caps&lt;/a&gt;  While the question about whether the governor should considering resigning from moderator Judy Woodruff of the Public Broadcasting Service stirred the audience, the candidates spent most of their 90-minute debate attacking each other.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.wychwoodcabinetmakers.co.uk/prescriptionassistanceservicesinfo-e0f9.pdf&quot;&gt;is prescriptionassistanceservices.info legit&lt;/a&gt;  Remember when Manning&apos;s gutsiest plays would rescue the Giants, when you held your breath waiting for miracle TDs? This football bounced off a helmet and floated into the waiting hands of Eagles linebacker Mychal Kendricks, who returned it to the 25. One play later, Eagles backup quarterback Nick Foles, subbing for an injured Michael Vick, rolled left, then threw back to the right to tight end Brent Celek, giving Philly a 29-21 advantage.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
