<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542572785169">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 20:26:25 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.tt3njd21gnub</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Can I call you back? &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mikasafloors.com/miraceti---rua-caputira---mirandpolis-so-paulo---state-of-so-paulo-bdec.pdf&quot;&gt;miraceti&lt;/a&gt;  Amer is said to have told interrogators that he had hoped to trade the body of the soldier &amp;ndash; whom he worked beside in a restaurant in the Israeli city of Bat Yam - to win the release of his brother, who is incarcerated in an Israeli jail for militant offences committed during the second Palestinian intifada.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lucky-websolutions.com/totalcaremartcom-reviews-0a7b.pdf&quot;&gt;totalcaremart.com&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;There are still many issues that need to be resolved and we need to make this, to make sure that this process goes as safely and as smoothly as possible,&quot; Quebec Public Security officer Jean-Thomas Fortin said Monday.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://stsmihajlopupin.edu.rs/rs/lapharmacienet-3c56.pdf#amid&quot;&gt;worldpharmacytop.com&lt;/a&gt;  But outside Japan, the concept of the so-called kei car, aterm derived from the Japanese word light, is mostly unknown. Now that could change. The Japanese auto giants are consideringexporting the technology to emerging market countries.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ecorporationbd.com/metaxalone-naproxen-aaa8.pdf#bloody&quot;&gt;metaxalone restless leg&lt;/a&gt;  Mayor Bob Filner indicated today that he is not resigning, but said he will attend a two-week intensive behavioral counseling clinic after seven women publicly came forward to allege he sexually harassed them.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lucky-websolutions.com/fosamax-webmd-0a7b.pdf&quot;&gt;fosamax webmd&lt;/a&gt;  Committee chairperson Sen. Patrick Leahy (D-Vermont) referenced the recent revelations about the NSA&apos;s domestic surveillance programs, worrying that the agency has gone overboard. &quot;There&apos;s always going to be more dots to try to connect,&quot; Leahy said in opening statements. &quot;When is enough enough?&quot; Ranking member Sen. Chuck Grassley (R-Iowa) voiced concern about the domestic use of drones, and mentioned outgoing FBI director Robert Mueller&apos;s acknowledgment that drones have been used in some investigations on U.S. soil. Grassley also asked about the Obama administration&apos;s failure to prosecute bankers responsible for the financial crash, and wondered if Comey&apos;s connections to HSBC would preclude him from pursuing investigations into the financial industry.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
