<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542533324788">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 09:28:44 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.rwigsne9eyr4</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>How much is a Second Class stamp? &lt;a href=&quot;https://newscvm.com/drpharmahr-e9bb.pdf&quot;&gt;gsmedicalusa.com&lt;/a&gt;  By tradition, the Queen will be the first person to be informed when the baby is born, with a handwritten note taken from the hospital to Buckingham Palace. A note will then be pinned outside the gates of the palace.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lucky-websolutions.com/probenecid-drugscom-0a7b.pdf#fiery&quot;&gt;probenecid drugs.com&lt;/a&gt;  The United Nations adopted a resolution last week demanding that Syria eliminate its chemical weapons. The vote came amid outrage over a sarin gas attack in a Damascus suburb that killed hundreds. Facing the threat of U.S. military action and coaxing from Moscow, Syria agreed to surrender the arms.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://zoeydeutch.net/intouch-pharmacy-valparaiso-8f08.pdf#employ&quot;&gt;intouch pharmacy dawsonville ga&lt;/a&gt;  Huff was making his first start because the Yankees have lost faith in Phil Hughes, but after a perfect first inning, Huff allowed eight runs without escaping the fourth. He was relieved by Jim Miller, a veteran minor league reliever called up hours earlier to help the depleted bullpen, and he let Huff&apos;s last base runner score, then gave up three runs of his own.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://contactconsultoria.com/index.php/dream-mask-a511.pdf#relaxing&quot;&gt;dream mask&lt;/a&gt;  No injuries have been reported, but falling trees and gas lines severed by tornado-like winds forced the evacuation of 200 condominium units on the city&apos;s east side, Las Vegas fire spokesman Tim Szymanski said. Fifteen units were damaged by falling trees, and about 50 residents of the complex were expected to take shelter at a nearby high school.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dollingstownfc.com/john-gilbride-pharmacy-glasgow-6865.pdf#pedestrian&quot;&gt;john gilbride pharmacy glasgow&lt;/a&gt;  But, Collins said, that was unrealistic and he’s right. Everyone, from the 27,581 in the stands who were chanting “Let’s Go, Harvey” in the ninth inning, to the men in the dugout to the one standing on the mound wanted Harvey to finish. First shutout is a milestone of sorts, even if, as Collins put it, it’s the “first of many shutouts he’s going to pitch.”
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
