<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1543413942968">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">28.11.2018 14:05:42 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.q0x6bgqbob6g</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Can I call you back? &lt;a href=&quot;http://public-admin.co.uk/epic-specialty-pharmacy-3c8d.pdf&quot;&gt;epic specialty pharmacy software&lt;/a&gt;  Per Pale means that the Shield is divided vertically with one half blue (azure) and the other half red (gules). A Chevron Or means the gold chevron across the centre of the shield. There are smaller white chevrons, or cotises, above and below the gold chevron, symbolising snow-capped mountains from the Middletons&apos; skiiing holidays. Slipped means &amp;lsquo;with a stalk,&amp;rsquo; so the final part of the blazon &amp;ndash; and distinguishing feature of the Shield &amp;ndash; means three acorns with gold stalks and leaves.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://public-admin.co.uk/audiomedicalcl-3c8d.pdf#distracted&quot;&gt;mchealthgrid.com&lt;/a&gt;  Under the law, Planned Parenthood would have to upgrade itsclinic in Lafayette, Indiana, to surgical standards or stopadministering RU-486, commonly called the abortion pill, it saidin a lawsuit filed in Indianapolis federal court.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.purplecreativedesign.co.uk/astelin-yahoo-sports-5884.pdf&quot;&gt;astelin yahoo sports&lt;/a&gt;  If the debt ceiling is not raised in time, Fitch said aformal review of the AAA rating &quot;with potentially negativeimplications&quot; would be triggered, even though it believes U.S.Treasury securities will be honored in full and on time.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bombeirodf.com.br/how-many-ibuprofen-and-paracetamol-can-i-take-in-a-day-50f8.pdf#raised&quot;&gt;acetaminophen vs ibuprofen liver&lt;/a&gt;  As is common on Law &amp; Order, Fontana shares a number of other characteristics with the actor who plays him: they hail from the same Chicago neighborhood, attended the same parochial school, and have the same tastes in both clothes and music.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bombeirodf.com.br/buy-zyprexa-uk-50f8.pdf&quot;&gt;olanzapine therapeutic class&lt;/a&gt;  Democrats say bills to fund the government and raise thedebt ceiling could be resolved quickly if House ofRepresentatives Speaker John Boehner permitted votes on simple,no-strings-attached measures.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
