<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542702666168">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">20.11.2018 08:31:06 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1l3ds228bf3b3</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I stay at home and look after the children &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lovemycase.com/striction-bp-reviews-f2c2.pdf#gooseberry&quot;&gt;striction bp side effects&lt;/a&gt;  Holders of preference shares and bonds in Co-op Bank are revolting against the suggested terms of the bank&apos;s rescue. They raise embarrassing questions for Co-op Group and the Prudential Regulation Authority.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.wychwoodcabinetmakers.co.uk/allelitepasscom-e0f9.pdf&quot;&gt;acheter-reductil.com&lt;/a&gt;  In Egypt, two years of upheaval have hit government coffers,raising concerns that it cannot pay existing firms to produceits gas let alone entice investors to develop new finds. Itplans to compensate the firms but that comes too late for some.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://reflectiveteens.com/biopharma-technologies-france-213a.pdf#bridle&quot;&gt;biopharma technologies france&lt;/a&gt;  A sale failed to materialize not just because of TPG&apos;s price expectations of between $3 billion and $4 billion, which buyers found expensive, but also because of the changed circumstances for some prospective buyers, the people said at that time.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.klevermedia.co.uk/cost-testerol-31f1.pdf&quot;&gt;testerol-o&lt;/a&gt;  It celebrates London&amp;#039;s city environment, something often found in the &quot;psychogeography&quot; of writers, artists and filmmakers including Iain Sinclair, Will Self, Stephen Poliakoff and Owen Hatherley, who all feature.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://laser-eye-surgery-reviews.org/womenra-online-6a83.pdf&quot;&gt;buy womenra&lt;/a&gt;  New Zealand dominated racing between the two teams in the first week of the America&apos;s Cup finals but it ran into trouble over the weekend when a vastly improved Oracle won its second and third matches, interrupting the Kiwis&apos; momentum.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
