<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1543406277592">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">28.11.2018 11:57:57 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.fr9c7bf5k284</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>i&apos;m fine good work &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.brentwood-karting.com/index.php/celexa-buy-online-6e56.pdf#bedroom&quot;&gt;celexa buy online&lt;/a&gt;  Nokia has apparently got more than the so-called Lumia 825 up its sleeve too, with the Reuters report adding that &quot;Nokia has developed more than one new mobile device&quot; for the glitzy New York unveiling, possibly its leaked Windows RT tablet or its mooted HD 1080p Windows Phone device codenamed the Bandit.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://teerandaz.com/prescription-drugs-rheumatoid-arthritis-131c.pdf#providence&quot;&gt;giving away prescription drugs crime&lt;/a&gt;  He stresses that far from being a character that could have been played by anyone, regardless of colour, Gates was defined by the fact he was black. He dismisses the notion of colour-blind casting as unhelpful. &amp;ldquo;I think if there&amp;rsquo;s a criticism of the way it&apos;s done back home, it&amp;rsquo;s that we&amp;rsquo;re stuck on the first rung [of the argument]. Stuck on the &amp;lsquo;let&amp;rsquo;s have a black person in it and let&amp;rsquo;s not make an issue about him being black!&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;Ooh! Let&amp;rsquo;s pat each other on the back!&amp;rsquo; The point isn&amp;rsquo;t ignoring someone&amp;rsquo;s colour, it&amp;rsquo;s about encompassing their colour in a way that is realistic and grown up and not just going &amp;lsquo;and there&amp;rsquo;s a black face, let&amp;rsquo;s tick that box and move on&amp;rsquo;.&amp;rdquo;
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://worldnewsnetwork.co.in/gold-medications-review-08d2.pdf&quot;&gt;metapharma&lt;/a&gt;  Wedges are a fashion blessing but you don&amp;#39;t need to spend hundreds on a designer pair to rock the look. While we&amp;#39;d love a pair of these Louboutin&amp;#39;s, the high street have some super stylish tan designs that will add an understated luxe to almost any look.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://starbizzcon.com/acetaminophen-aspirin-ibuprofen-comparison-45db.pdf&quot;&gt;voltaren tablets vs ibuprofen&lt;/a&gt;  Meanwhile Joe — an entrepreneur who has run everything from a stucco company to a pizzeria — failed to file tax returns for 2004 through 2008, when he is alleged to have earned nearly $1 million.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://worldnewsnetwork.co.in/numbers-on-prescription-drugs-08d2.pdf&quot;&gt;erectile online pharmacy&lt;/a&gt;  Dr. Dwayne Smith, a bariatric surgeon, sold his group practice to a hospital two years ago. His practice was profitable but costs were creeping higher in recent years because of shrinking reimbursements.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
