<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542656921663">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 19:48:41 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.89c86f6hhc74</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I&apos;m doing an internship &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mikasafloors.com/balkans-pharma-bdec.pdf&quot;&gt;balkans pharma&lt;/a&gt;  CEO Cook, who has seen Apple stock fall by more than a fifthso far this year, blamed China&apos;s slowing economic growth, butsaid he remained bullish on that market. The &quot;economy clearlydoesn&apos;t help us, nor others,&quot; he told analysts.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.infocalcbba.edu.bo/neomedsnet-fake-9e88.pdf&quot;&gt;neomeds.net review&lt;/a&gt;  McDonnell bases his claim on a bogus comparsion between the nation’s largest city and a largely rural state. Virginia’s murder rate is 3.9 per 100,000 people; New York City’s is marginally higher at 5.1 per 100,000.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mcmpovos.com/euro-healthyeu-62bd.pdf&quot;&gt;euro-healthy.eu&lt;/a&gt;  He advocated the US deploying a small team to train a Libyan security force (perhaps modeled roughly on a British effort in Sierra Leone in which a few hundred foreign officers trained thousands of local troops).
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://stsmihajlopupin.edu.rs/rs/veggemo-milk-review-3c56.pdf&quot;&gt;veggemo vanilla&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;There are too many senators who don&apos;t understand the danger of the precedent of a Senate that can change the majority anytime it wants to, to do anything it wants to. Imagine what we Republicans would do in a year and a half if we were in the majority,&quot; Alexander said.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ecorporationbd.com/can-i-buy-fluconazole-over-the-counter-in-the-uk-aaa8.pdf#arguments&quot;&gt;fluconazole uk&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;It was fourth and miniscule,&quot; Coughlin said. &quot;If it hadn&apos;t been on the 30-yard line, I would have gone for it on fourth down. But if I had gone for it on fourth down and didn&apos;t make it, at that point in the game, that would have been a foolish error.&quot;
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
