<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1543376626271">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">28.11.2018 03:43:46 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.xh7r0kqv9guh</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Can I use your phone? &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.yoriko-ballet-studio.com/stmap_f0470.html?arjuna.valparin.cialis&quot;&gt;anxietyremedies.org&lt;/a&gt;  Jackie Barry, a National Grid spokeswoman, said the companyis pleased to settle. &quot;We have made significant progress inresolving the payroll issues that have been affecting ouremployees, and regret the inconvenience and frustration thatthese issues have caused.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://teerandaz.com/stmap_131c0.html?viagra.irbesartan.tadalafil.synthroid&quot;&gt;www.calvetsupply.com/&lt;/a&gt;  UNITED NATIONS, Oct 1 (Reuters) - Israeli Prime MinisterBenjamin Netanyahu on Tuesday dismissed a charm offensive byIran&apos;s new president as a ruse concocted by a &quot;wolf in sheep&apos;sclothing,&quot; and declared that Israel was ready to stand alone todeny Tehran an atomic weapon.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.greenlam.com/index.php/stmap_77410.html?champix.danazol.virecta.levitra&quot;&gt;bhv pharmaceutical&lt;/a&gt;  The move is a setback for foreign leaders trying to bolster more secular rebel groups and to reassure voters skeptical of deeper involvement in Syria&apos;s civil war. Some may think again about help for the fighters, which ranges from weaponry from the Gulf to non-lethal aid from Europe and the United States.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.yoriko-ballet-studio.com/stmap_f0470.html?levitra.desmopressin.fluvoxamine&quot;&gt;medikamente-per-klick.de seris&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;They may still receive a couple of downloads every day - maybe even up to 100 or so - but that is not going to be enough for a developer to capitalise on or draw motivation from to support the app.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://pixelbedlam.co.uk/stmap_65ef0.html?levitra.trileptal.celexa&quot;&gt;buy azolol uk&lt;/a&gt;  A bomb has killed 31 people in the Pakistani city of Peshawar, with at least seventy wounded. The blast comes in the wake of another attack a week ago when an Anglican church was targetted, killing over 80 people, the highest death toll on Christians in predominantly Muslim Pakistan.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
