<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542374571402">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">16.11.2018 13:22:51 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.8cstswc3q4et</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Where are you from? &lt;a href=&quot;https://freelifesinsurancequotes.com/stmap_6f970.html?cellcept.viagra.depakote.suprax&quot;&gt;20 mg cialis vs 100mg viagra&lt;/a&gt;  A woman was arrested Monday after green paint was found splattered inside two chapels at the Washington National Cathedral, and police were investigating her in connection with two similar incidents on the National Mall, authorities said. Jiamei Tian, 58, was arrested inside the cathedral shortly after the paint was found and charged with defacing property, police and cathedral officials said. Investigators were hoping to question her about the vandalism on the Mall, including at the Lincoln Memorial, but a language barrier was complicating those efforts, the assistant D.C. police chief, Peter Newsham, said soon after the arrest. Police believed she was homeless. Green paint was found early Friday morning on the Lincoln Memorial, and symbols were found painted in green later Friday on another statue on the Mall. The Lincoln Memorial was closed temporarily but reopened later Friday. Also Monday, U.S. Park Police said green paint was found on the statue of Joseph Henry outside the headquarters of the Smithsonian Institution on the Mall. Henry was the institution&apos;s first secretary.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://stsmihajlopupin.edu.rs/rs/stmap_3c560.html?levitra.bromide.tadagra&quot;&gt;prescription-uk.nu&lt;/a&gt;  A gate normally used to let regional police into ringside positions was pushed wide open by a flood of runners, causing an obstruction for others trying to enter the main arena, Interior Ministry regional spokesman Javier Morras said.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ecorporationbd.com/stmap_aaa80.html?amoxicillin.viagra.pentoxifylline&quot;&gt;gabapentin cap 100mg side effects&lt;/a&gt;  Thorne explained, &quot;This situation was a mistake on the part of our bank and – as we have done previously – we sincerely apologize to the homeowner for the inconvenience and concern it may have caused. In addition, we communicated to the homeowner our desire to compensate her fairly and equitably for her inconvenience and loss.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://kssgrp.com/stmap_54570.html?levitra.silagra.nalidixic.xalatan&quot;&gt;ofloxacin ear drops generic&lt;/a&gt;  Prince Michael of Kent, for his part, told me: &amp;ldquo;If only we could choose where our bodies are unearthed. I did feel for King Richard when I learnt that he had been located beneath a council car park in Leicester&amp;rdquo;.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.proguaru.com.br/stmap_76840.html?viagra.vpxl.suminat&quot;&gt;pyramid pharmacy stamford hill&lt;/a&gt;  What Liechti and colleagues found was that during the daytime, the birds’ activity and pitch measurements showed that they were not resting on the ground. Also, at night the birds greatly reduced their wing flapping and appeared to be gliding for long distances.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
