<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542534161817">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 09:42:41 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.16jimgbb8e7jy</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I&apos;m in a band &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.casadeadoracao.com.br/index.php/clay-medical-supplies-petersburg-bac9.pdf#disgust&quot;&gt;clay medical supplies petersburg&lt;/a&gt;  The shutdown began on Tuesday when the Republican-led House of Representatives refused to approve a bill funding the government unless it included measures designed to delay or defund key provisions of Obama&apos;s signature legislation, the 2010 Affordable Care Act, which are now being implemented.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.md-interiors.co.uk/healthplansonlinecom-a6a4.pdf#ram&quot;&gt;pacs.aimmedicalimaging.com&lt;/a&gt;  House Speaker John Boehner and the Tea Party band took all of that hostage, offering deals that were no deals at all: Bow to us on this, that or the other Obamacare provision and we will keep Uncle Sam in business. This wasn’t the art of compromise. It was political criminality.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://zoeydeutch.net/samrxcom-review-8f08.pdf&quot;&gt;samrx.com&lt;/a&gt;  The roadside bomb that struck the cart was aimed at stopping a joint patrol of Afghan soldiers and police that was pursuing a group of Taliban militants in the western province of Herat, local police Lt. Sher Agha said. But the bomb exploded next to the cart carrying the villagers, killing 12 women, four children and a man, Agha said.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.wychwoodcabinetmakers.co.uk/crestor-20-mg-cena-e0f9.pdf#sculpture&quot;&gt;precio del medicamento crestor&lt;/a&gt;  The Indian media and the ruling Congress party regularly claim that Modi has employed foreign help - in particular APCO Worldwide, one of the largest PR agencies in the United States - to help him rehabilitate his image and make him more acceptable to voters at home and governments abroad.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://contactconsultoria.com/index.php/best-place-to-buy-amoxicillin-online-a511.pdf#poking&quot;&gt;best place to buy amoxicillin online&lt;/a&gt;  Pressed on BBC Radio Four&amp;rsquo;s Today programme on whether the parties should give the money back, he said: &amp;ldquo;Absolutely &amp;ndash; as quickly as possible and to put it to some good purpose that everyone will endorse.&amp;rdquo;
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
