<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542659476620">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 20:31:16 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.13wz9diax8681</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>We&apos;ve got a joint account &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dollingstownfc.com/buy-cheap-stromectol-6865.pdf#hoped&quot;&gt;stromectol 3 mg price&lt;/a&gt;  “Such bigots, for bigots is what they are, have no qualms about using such power as they have to bully anyone who holds views rooted in tradition or religion,” the editorial stated. “Such discrimination is proposed under the cloak of a ‘non-discrimination’ ordinance. George Orwell is alive and hiding in Texas.”
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cabanadolago.com.br/index.php/buy-pfizer-viagra-online-india-ab8a.pdf#boots&quot;&gt;viagra for sale in auckland&lt;/a&gt;  There have been some signs of softness at the top end of thesmartphone market, marked by weaker than expected sales ofSamsung&apos;s flagship Galaxy S4 smartphone. Apple, however, comfortably beat forecasts for iPhone saleson Tuesday.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://lemcasesorias.com/index.php/med-pharmacy-argus-83f5.pdf&quot;&gt;med pharmacy argus&lt;/a&gt;  Police forced a pathway through hundreds of Bulgarians who have been protesting for 40 days against a controversial government decision to name a media magnate as security chief, corruption and a system deemed by many as “oligarchic.”
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.layeredonline.com/qian-lie-shu-wan-ingredients-dd54.pdf&quot;&gt;qian lie shu wan pian&lt;/a&gt;  While reviews for &quot;The Canyons&quot; have been generally negative, critics have praised Lohan&apos;s performance as the jaded actress Tara, who finds herself in the crosshairs of her jealous boyfriend&apos;s psychological manipulation. Variety&apos;s Scott Foundas praised Lohan&apos;s &quot;raw conviction&quot; and her &quot;uncanny conflagration of drama and autobiography.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://newscvm.com/garcinia-q-es-e9bb.pdf#tragic&quot;&gt;garcinia q es&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;People are just starting to tune in,&quot; Sebelius said. &quot;As weramp up our communications and connect it with real facts, forthe first time, a lot of Americans will be learning what the lawmeans for them.&quot;
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
