<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542637032065">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 14:17:12 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1m7tzboizgske</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>A financial advisor &lt;a href=&quot;https://newscvm.com/vision-pharma-e9bb.pdf#intricate&quot;&gt;envision pharma private equity&lt;/a&gt;  Police have already arrested much of the Brotherhood&amp;#039;s senior leadership, including its top figure Mohamed Badie and his deputy Khairat al-Shater. They are on trial on charges of incitement to violence.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.elegantandwild.co.uk/supplementedgecom-confiavel-75b3.pdf&quot;&gt;supplementedge.com&lt;/a&gt;  Officials said that Attorney General Eric Holder called the governors of both states on Thursday to inform them that federal authorities won&amp;rsquo;t pre-empt their state laws permitting recreational use of the drug, which voters approved last year via ballot initiatives.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.anupamdebashisroy.com/optibac-probiotics-reviews-baby-f2ef.pdf#brow&quot;&gt;optibac probiotics for daily wellbeing reviews&lt;/a&gt;  Woods gets defensive when asked about his confidence. Surely it would seem to have been easier when he was winning them with regularity. All he can do is point to his four PGA Tour wins this year, his No. 1 ranking fully restored, the way his named his bandied about as a favorite at every Grand Slam event.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.md-interiors.co.uk/goverre-amazon-a6a4.pdf&quot;&gt;goverre shark tank episode&lt;/a&gt;  While photos of Manziel partying and posing with coeds of varying states of undress make for good blog fodder, ESPN&apos;s take on Manziel is far more dire. College football’s most famous quarterback is painted as an anger-prone youngster who&apos;s turned to the bottle to deal with stress.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sarah-hyland.net/newshealthgq-79a8.pdf&quot;&gt;costumedesignersguild.com&lt;/a&gt;  Sept. 10 -- AT&amp;T Services Inc. voluntarily agreed to adopt new wireless device standards that will allow additional carriers to access AT&amp;T&apos;s network. The Sept. 10 decision will benefit small and rural wireless carriers, analysts said.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
