<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542535864483">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 10:11:04 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1nbeqaxfw1el3</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>How much were you paid in your last job? &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.wychwoodcabinetmakers.co.uk/herb-pharm-albizia-e0f9.pdf#violence&quot;&gt;epilady brizard&lt;/a&gt;  July 22 (Reuters) - Activist hedge fund Third Point LLCreached an agreement to sell two-thirds of its stake in YahooInc back to the company for $29.11 per share on Monday,sending shares of the Internet company down nearly 5 percent.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://lemcasesorias.com/index.php/cost-of-actos-30-mg-83f5.pdf#encourage&quot;&gt;buy cheap pioglitazone&lt;/a&gt;  The premier has stopped short of saying he will stake his government&apos;s future on a confidence vote. If he chooses to do so, and loses, early elections could be the result, further distracting the country from efforts to shake off a recession. Letta could also ask for confidence votes not pegged to the government per se but to specific policies.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dollingstownfc.com/why-are-prescription-drugs-so-expensive-in-the-usa-6865.pdf&quot;&gt;why are prescription drugs so expensive in the usa&lt;/a&gt;  Fire authorities said it was too early to assess the impact fully. There were reports of superficial damage to buildings from the quake, which shattered windows and sent items tumbling from supermarket shelves.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://reflectiveteens.com/es-fiable-comprar-cialis-por-internet-213a.pdf&quot;&gt;forum acheter du cialis sur internet&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;A lot of them want to go back to the mainland, but they&apos;re feeling trapped in the islands,&quot; she said. &quot;They can get reunited with their families, and it takes away the burden of Hawaii having to support them.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.layeredonline.com/diamedicain-dd54.pdf&quot;&gt;savondrugshealth.com&lt;/a&gt;  Up to now, anyone with the H7N9 virus was believed to have come into contact with an infected bird. Now researchers report that before a woman and her father both died from the illness, he had visited poultry markets &amp;mdash; but she had only visited him in his sick bed. Despite the clearest indication yet that the virus is mutating, doctors say it&amp;#39;s not yet time to panic: the disease still isn&amp;#39;t very good at human-to-human transmission, they assure. Don&amp;#39;t mind us if we decide to invest in industrial quantities of face masks before it gets any better.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
