<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542709887921">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">20.11.2018 10:31:27 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1hw58ayyrfax9</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Do you play any instruments? &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tarokasongbad.com/foundation-rx-e3c4.pdf#jewellery&quot;&gt;foundation rx&lt;/a&gt;  Burying Ms Hussey in a shallow grave dug in the dirt floor of a basement, Weeks recalled, he put her body on top of an earlier victim. &quot;We were kind of running out of room down there,&quot; he deadpanned.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://paradiseinmexico.com.mx/med-rx-advisors-c13c.pdf#jail&quot;&gt;psrx advisors&lt;/a&gt;  A technical support number listed on the UK website remained on hold for 30 minutes when contacted by the BBC. A separate sales number gave an estimate of a &quot;47-minute&quot; wait to speak to an advisor.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://globalelite.tv/caremedicationcom-b1c8.pdf#measure&quot;&gt;lose-weight-overnight.com&lt;/a&gt;  ** Indian snack maker Balaji Wafers is in separate talkswith private equity funds, including Blackstone Group andActis, to raise between $100 million and $125 million, twosources with direct knowledge of the matter told Reuters.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.klevermedia.co.uk/mouthhealthykidsorg-31f1.pdf#repel&quot;&gt;primecareinternalmed.com&lt;/a&gt;  “We won two out of three here last time. They beat us in our ballpark. We didn’t pitch very well in those games nor did we hit well in those games. Talk is cheap. You just have to go out there and play.”
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://digital-matchbox.com/dr-david-williams-5522.pdf&quot;&gt;dr david williams st vincent&amp;#39s&lt;/a&gt;  Each bidder has sought congressional support. Blue Origin&apos;splan has the backing of Frank Wolf, a Virginia Republican whochairs the House subcommittee overseeing NASA funding. Wolf andother legislators including Senator Patty Murray, a Democratfrom Blue Origin&apos;s home state of Washington, and RepresentativeRobert Aderholt, an Alabama Republican, warned NASA aboutgranting an exclusive use agreement for the launchpad.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
