<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1543378099353">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">28.11.2018 04:08:19 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.xinyvx5id80s</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Could you give me some smaller notes? &lt;a href=&quot;http://public-admin.co.uk/stmap_3c8d0.html?digoxin.levitra.vpxl.tacrolimus&quot;&gt;epiduo vs differin&lt;/a&gt;  Beijing has signalled its intention to make the necessaryreforms, even as it has cut its target for economic growth thisyear to 7.5 percent from 8 percent, which would mark theeconomy&apos;s slowest pace in 23 years.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.yoriko-ballet-studio.com/stmap_f0470.html?sublingual.viagra.fml&quot;&gt;where can i buy ibuprofen in hong kong&lt;/a&gt;  Folders are now a mixed bag. You can add as many icons as you&apos;d like to a folder. But iOS 7 only displays nine of them at one time. To see another screen of icons in a folder you have to scroll to the right, which almost defeats the purpose of having a single folder in the first place.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://pixelbedlam.co.uk/stmap_65ef0.html?avapro.cialis.etoricoxib.imodium&quot;&gt;generic synthroid&lt;/a&gt;  Andy Burnham, the shadow health secretary, said, “Billions have been siphoned out of the NHS front-line to pay for an unnecessary restructuring that no-one voted for and David Cameron personally promised would not happen.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.yoriko-ballet-studio.com/stmap_f0470.html?tadarise.cytoxan.clozaril.viagra&quot;&gt;be herbal full spectrum ashwagandha 5000&lt;/a&gt;  That airy workspace is a long way from Memorial High School in West New York, N.J., where they met as starry-eyed kids who once managed to score free tickets to see Katharine Hepburn — Isabel’s favorite — on Broadway in “A Matter of Gravity.”
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://oktandrammen.no/drammen-ny/stmap_e52c0.html?sucralfate.cozaar.cialis&quot;&gt;jual levitra 100mg&lt;/a&gt;  While Republicans, who control the House of Representatives,have not unveiled a coherent strategy for these measures,individual members of the House and Senate have threatened touse them as they have in the past to extract concessions fromthe White House on spending, and perhaps on Obamacare - thepresident&apos;s signature healthcare law set for launch on Oct. 1.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
