<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542361281292">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">16.11.2018 09:41:21 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1xhvmn62c77uu</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Go travelling &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sarah-hyland.net/stmap_79a80.html?drospirenone.levitra.tamoxifen.cefixime&quot;&gt;xango aeris instant eye gel&lt;/a&gt;  Even President Traian Basescu, the project’s former champion, now believes the law would unfairly benefit the Canadian-Romanian consortium. &quot;You can’t create a law addressing a company,” he told reporters. “It will be rejected by the Constitutional Court.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.weymouthskatepark.co.uk/stmap_6ae30.html?xeloda.cialis.glucotrol.sildigra&quot;&gt;is it illegal to throw away prescription drugs&lt;/a&gt;  Pretty quiet on the stock exchange announcements this morning. Thomas Cook, which brought us exciting news of its new logo last week, has just sold its businesses in Egypt and Lebanon to Yusuf Bin Ahmed Kanoo of Bahrain for £6.5m.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mikasafloors.com/stmap_bdec0.html?neoral.lozol.viagra.enalapril&quot;&gt;ordine commercialisti verona tirocinio&lt;/a&gt;  An 87-year-old Ontario man was allegedly beaten up by police in his London, Ontario home after his wife who suffers from Alzheimer&amp;#39;s disease told a passerby that &quot;a bad man&quot; was in the home.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.weymouthskatepark.co.uk/stmap_6ae30.html?viagra.starlix.arimidex.varenicline&quot;&gt;bactroban webmd&lt;/a&gt;  Demonstrators, some chanting racist slogans, vandalized shops and other sites known for employing migrant workers in the southern Biryulyovo area after the killing of a young ethnic Russian widely blamed on a man from the Caucasus.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://leotoys.cl/stmap_22060.html?mesterolone.tulasi.viagra&quot;&gt;sulbutiamine long term benefits&lt;/a&gt;  Phelps won six golds at the 2004 Athens Olympics, seven at the 2007 worlds and, of course, a record eight at the Beijing Olympics, eclipsing Spitz&apos;s mark of seven at the 1972 Munich Games. Otto won six golds at the 1988 Seoul Olympics — an accomplishment since clouded by revelations of rampant doping in East Germany — and Thorpe claimed a half-dozen victories at the 2001 worlds.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
