<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542372126874">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">16.11.2018 12:42:06 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1r4f11pkis7j4</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Enter your PIN &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.md-interiors.co.uk/stmap_a6a40.html?ethambutol.cialis.trecator-sc&quot;&gt;lamisil tablets directions&lt;/a&gt;  Commuter frustration with the second strike in four months boiled over Monday, as traffic leading to the San Francisco-Oakland Bay Bridge was already backed up for miles by dawn. The evening commute repeated the nightmare.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.elegantandwild.co.uk/stmap_75b30.html?chloromycetin.cardura.cialis.zyrtec&quot;&gt;retin a gel tretinoin&lt;/a&gt;  The Drummond stoppage has had little impact on coal priceshowever, with the global market well-supplied, a factor that hasweighed on prices for most of this year. Coal for delivery toEurope (ARA) traded at $78 a tonne on Friday.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.md-interiors.co.uk/stmap_a6a40.html?ascorbic.ciplox.levitra&quot;&gt;ihealth.net.au&lt;/a&gt;  (Phys.org) —By folding a paper-based Li-ion battery in a Miura-ori pattern (similar to how some maps are folded), scientists have shown that the battery exhibits a 14x increase in areal energy density and ...
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://laser-eye-surgery-reviews.org/stmap_6a830.html?levitra.cyclosporine.eregra&quot;&gt;dial vision spectacles&lt;/a&gt;  Secured lenders at Texas Competitive Electric Holdings, which represents Energy Future&apos;s unregulated subsidiary, and EFIH&apos;s unsecured bondholders had previously been in direct negotiations. The TCEH creditors have agreed to remain in negotiations, according to the filing, as has a &quot;significant creditor&quot; who owns debt in various parts of the company&apos;s capital structure.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.greenlamindustries.com/blog/stmap_0bae0.html?astelin.prednisone.dipivoxil.cialis&quot;&gt;healthwellegypt.com&lt;/a&gt;  The information broadcast by AIS is public - but when the system was first put in use, in the early 1990s, the technology required to receive the information was prohibitively expensive for those not directly involved in the industry.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
