<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1543404149742">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">28.11.2018 11:22:29 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.lh29r2p4qo</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>A company car &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sensors.co.uk/webinarscovermymedscom-9874.pdf#drag&quot;&gt;natur-pharm.ge&lt;/a&gt;  Apple quickly sent out iOS 7.0.2 to fix the bugs and now it appears that some users are experiencing issues with battery life, Wi-Fi connections, Bluetooth accessories and more.  Apple promised that iOS 7 was going to be the biggest software update since the first iPhone hit the market and for some, it has been a very good experience, but for others, the update has only caused problems.  Because Apple does not offer a chance to revert back to the older software, many users are stuck with what they have until the company gets another update ready.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.aicpuglia.it/bolttalk-2397.pdf&quot;&gt;boltt beat hr fitness band&lt;/a&gt;  More than 200 homes have been destroyed in New South Wales(NSW) state since last Thursday, when bushfires tore throughSydney&apos;s outskirts, razing entire streets. One man died from aheart attack while trying to save his home.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://worldnewsnetwork.co.in/x3s-bench-for-sale-08d2.pdf&quot;&gt;x3s bench review&lt;/a&gt;  Beijing has provided much-needed capital to a continentstarved of investment. The China Import-Export Bank is thecontinent&apos;s largest creditor and Beijing has promised $20billion more in loans over the next three years.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.purplecreativedesign.co.uk/vimax-quem-ja-tomou-5884.pdf&quot;&gt;vimax vimax&lt;/a&gt;  MALAYSIA-BASED private equity firm Navis Capital said it hassold industrial valve specialist Callidus Process Solutions toPon Holding Australia. Navis sold Callidus for around A$75million to A$100 million, making a return of over two times onits initial 2010 investment, according to a source withknowledge of the matter.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://pixelbedlam.co.uk/orthogenrx-website-65ef.pdf&quot;&gt;orthogenrx&lt;/a&gt;  Trading volumes remained light while Italian and Spanish government bonds, perceived to be more risky than German debt, were little changed. The 10-year Italian government bond yield was 0.02 percentage points higher at 4.33% while the corresponding Spanish bond yield was 0.01 percentage point lower at 4.46%.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
