<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542493674497">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">17.11.2018 22:27:54 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1gfk1n067ez1f</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Which team do you support? &lt;a href=&quot;http://stsmihajlopupin.edu.rs/rs/mirapexin-rp-prezzo-3c56.pdf&quot;&gt;mirapex cena&lt;/a&gt;  Cable companies have become hot assets as their cable lines,designed to deliver TV to homes, have been upgraded to carryvoice calls and Internet at speeds often five times faster thancompeting services from telecom operators and they have beensnatching customers from them.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://digital-matchbox.com/anabolicwarehousenet-5522.pdf&quot;&gt;anabolicwarehouse.net&lt;/a&gt;  The U.S. government has been partially shut since Oct. 1amid a budget standoff between congressional Republicans and theWhite House. Republicans also have refused to raise the nation&apos;s$16.7 trillion debt ceiling.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://lemcasesorias.com/index.php/superdrol-ng-ingredients-83f5.pdf#blouse&quot;&gt;buy cheap superdrol&lt;/a&gt;  The defunct company was snapped up by private equity firms Apollo Global Management and Metropoulos &amp; Co., who split Hostess’s best-selling snacks between them and got things rolling in time for summer.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lovemycase.com/gladstone-physiotherapist-f2c2.pdf&quot;&gt;gladstone physio&lt;/a&gt;  Washington says it remains determined to deny the Iraniansthe means to make nuclear arms but its willingness to engagethem directly complicates strategy for Netanyahu, who willaddress the General Assembly on Oct. 1.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.haroldwhitefuneraldirectors.co.uk/cloridrato-de-ciprofloxacino-sandoz-preo-bd82.pdf&quot;&gt;cipro xr ciprofloxacin 500mg&lt;/a&gt;  Governor Pat Quinn on Wednesday used his line-item veto to eliminate salaries for state lawmakers from the fiscal 2014 budget. If the salaries indeed are cut, the move saves the state $1.15 million a month.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
