<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542358868312">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">16.11.2018 09:01:08 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.lz1ns5yz368h</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Very funny pictures &lt;a href=&quot;http://reflectiveteens.com/stmap_213a0.html?cialis.apcalis.p-force&quot;&gt;phantom pain hackers&lt;/a&gt;  A police force has apologised and paid compensation to an enslaved maid after officers failed to believe her story and sent her back to her wealthy middle-class abusers. Hertfordshire police admitted that they had failed to protect the 40-year-old woman despite her pleas for help and returned her to the family.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://newscvm.com/stmap_e9bb0.html?viagra.azelaic.stavudine&quot;&gt;testosterone shots&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;There are whole groups of people who are going to claimthis would be a hardship and will not sit,&quot; said Andrew Lawler,a white-collar defense attorney and former assistant prosecutorin the office that is bringing the case against Madoff&apos;semployees. &quot;I think the judge will be sympathetic to anyone whosays they can&apos;t sit for five months for some legitimate reason,&quot;he said.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://virtual-operations.com/stmap_92e20.html?fildena.levitra.himcocid.ciplox&quot;&gt;rx green technologies denver&lt;/a&gt;  Today Microsoft reported the number of data requests it received from various law enforcement agencies around the world in the first half of (calendar) 2013: 37,196. Those requests dealt with, at most, 66,539 accounts.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://stsmihajlopupin.edu.rs/rs/stmap_3c560.html?droxia.levitra.zebeta&quot;&gt;nifedipine cena&lt;/a&gt;  Militants have previously carried out deadly bombings inMoscow and other parts of Russia outside the mostly Muslim NorthCaucasus, but specific allegations of plots to attack sitesholding weapons of mass destruction in nuclear-armed Russia arealmost unheard of.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://laser-eye-surgery-reviews.org/stmap_6a830.html?antivert.cialis.ocuflox.prothiaden&quot;&gt;viamax power coffee review&lt;/a&gt;  He added: &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m not frankly entirely sure what rolling back green levies [means]. If removing all green levies which help two million people on very low incomes, which help support thousands of jobs in our renewable energy sector, if that is what is meant, I think that would be an own goal.&amp;rdquo;
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
