<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1543387516937">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">28.11.2018 06:45:16 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1jtwg1usgjt8x</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I&apos;ve got a very weak signal &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sensors.co.uk/stmap_98740.html?viagra.proscar.vepesid&quot;&gt;what is aciphex&lt;/a&gt;  Chinese clients also often request boys, a consequence of a cultural preference for boy children. While sex-selective abortion is illegal - though still common - in China, gender selection is technically straightforward through IVF in the United States, where it is used in surrogacy cases.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://oktandrammen.no/drammen-ny/stmap_e52c0.html?clarithromycin.cialis.chlorambucil&quot;&gt;ultramedic.com.pl&lt;/a&gt;  The Petzval lens was the most popular choice for photos in the 19th century, and produces a unique bokeh (background blur) effect with a very narrow depth of field. They&amp;#8217;re pretty recognizable once you see some samples taken with them, and the effect is very impressive when paired with the sensors and imaging capabilities of modern DSLRs.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sensors.co.uk/stmap_98740.html?forzest.oxytetracycline.viagra&quot;&gt;yxhshop.com&lt;/a&gt;  Tributes have been paid to the victims, named as Duncan Munro, 46, from Bishop Auckland, County Durham; George Allison, 57, from Winchester, Hampshire; Sarah Darnley, 45, from Elgin in the Highlands; and 59-year-old Gary McCrossan, from Inverness.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ssvoverath.de/stmap_c3db0.html?cialis.verapamil.citrate.silvitra&quot;&gt;kamagra oral jelly erfahrungsberichte&lt;/a&gt;  Crosby is a veteran of this type of schedule, having served as an alternate captain at the 2010 Vancouver Games when Canada captured the gold medal. Crosby scored the &quot;Golden Goal&quot; in overtime against the United States to win the championship.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://oktandrammen.no/drammen-ny/stmap_e52c0.html?dexone.carbonate.levitra.zyban&quot;&gt;propecia vs generic finasteride&lt;/a&gt;  Wright spent the last few weeks working out and playing in simulated games. With the minor league seasons over, he had nowhere to play in rehab games. Bones, who last appeared in a major league game in 2001, did his best to get Wright ready.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
