<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542656276356">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 19:37:56 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1l00p6r5iwvay</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>The manager &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mikasafloors.com/lipitor-20-mg-prix-bdec.pdf#char&quot;&gt;lipitor 20 mg prix&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;Much of the current &quot;profit&quot; is the reversal of earlier&quot; loss reserves, meaning &quot;the original losses that causedgreat outrage weren&apos;t necessarily that big to begin with,&quot; said Jim Vogel, a mortgage analyst at FTN Financial. Becausethat point isn&apos;t well understood, &quot;headlines discuss these developments as miracle comebacks that prove something.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://sjofartsbygningen.no/advertising-for-prescription-drugs-7ef0.pdf#encounter&quot;&gt;price chopper pharmacy greenwood mo&lt;/a&gt;  Stockett, author of the popular book-turned-movie The Help, tweeted on Aug. 8 the above photo with the message to @Delta &amp;#8220;Dear Delta Airlines, I know we&amp;#8217;ve been through some hard times together but is this really my conf number?&amp;#8221;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ascfinancialadvisers.co.uk/ranitidine-150-mg-tablet-information-5553.pdf&quot;&gt;generic zantac for babies&lt;/a&gt;  Ian Robertson, member of the board of management, sales and marketing BMW, unveiled the BMW i3 to an audience that included government policy officials, energy companies and infrastructure providers, financial analysts, investment advisors and non-governmental organisations.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://lemcasesorias.com/index.php/lec-medical-usb-temperature-data-logger-83f5.pdf#secondly&quot;&gt;lec medical fridge spares&lt;/a&gt;  Rodriguez’s attorney, Joseph Tacopina, charged the Yankees with several serious offenses, including hiding an MRI from A-Rod that revealed a torn labrum in his hip and playing him in the 2012 postseason knowing he was injured.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.haroldwhitefuneraldirectors.co.uk/alfapharmayecom-bd82.pdf#dreams&quot;&gt;stanpharma.com&lt;/a&gt;  The app offers a basic discovery interface and is highly interactive, taking advantage of many of the hardware features of modern tablets and smartphones, including touch, voice and motion, to engage and entertain children in a variety of ways.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
