<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542693696091">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">20.11.2018 06:01:36 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.ruklstw8x533</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I&apos;d like a phonecard, please &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.techdesighn.com/healthcgigroupcomami-b26f.pdf#embrace&quot;&gt;health.cgigroup.com/ami&lt;/a&gt;  “I think he’s playing well enough,” said Jets defensive coordinator Dennis Thurman. “I mean when you’re going against a team’s top receiver most every game, the other guy’s going to be good, too. He gets paid just as well. I think he’s performing pretty well, but we can always do better.”
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ascfinancialadvisers.co.uk/how-to-apply-permethrin-for-head-lice-5553.pdf&quot;&gt;permethrin cream for lice how to use&lt;/a&gt;  And in return for Strub&amp;rsquo;s help on Pearl Harbor, the producers changed an entire character. Initially, Lt Col Doolittle was described as &amp;ldquo;a boorish, oafish type of fellow&amp;rdquo;. By the time Alec Baldwin played him on screen, he had transformed into somebody who was far more sympathetic.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://leotoys.cl/oxanabol-tablets-what-do-they-do-2206.pdf#comely&quot;&gt;oxanabolic&lt;/a&gt;  And the Seattle-based company is getting an assist from social media users in China, who have begun to pick apart critical reports of Starbucks carried by China Central Television and the China Daily newspaper.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sarah-hyland.net/ciamedscom-79a8.pdf#corners&quot;&gt;ciameds.com&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;I think even if Wendy Davis runs, it&apos;s still an 8, 10, 12-point race,&quot; said Republican consultant Matt Mackowiak. &quot;Keep in mind Romney won Texas by double digits. He was a pretty weak candidate in retrospect. Perry beat Bill White by a significant margin. Cruz won by a significant margin. So recent history &amp;mdash; you don&apos;t have to go back too far &amp;mdash; recent history shows double-digit wins for Republicans statewide in Texas.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://lemcasesorias.com/index.php/propranolol-bestellen-83f5.pdf#throw&quot;&gt;propranolol receptores&lt;/a&gt;  — Finance Minister Ahmed Galal: An economist, Galal is a U.S.-educated World Bank veteran who was also director of the Egyptian Center for Economic Studies, an independent think tank. He has written extensively on fiscal, trade and monetary policy.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
