<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542630582353">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 12:29:42 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.3fk11ntzenel</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>What&apos;s the exchange rate for euros? &lt;a href=&quot;https://digital-matchbox.com/wwwehealthgotz-5522.pdf#bow&quot;&gt;www.ehealth.go.tz/admin&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;I feel this is the right time for me to make this decision and it&apos;s not a choice I&amp;rsquo;ve made lightly. I greatly appreciate all of the support I have received over the past years, particularly from the British public and my team and sponsors. It has been an extremely happy and successful time.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.proguaru.com.br/man1-man-oil-ebay-india-7684.pdf&quot;&gt;man1 man oil reviews&lt;/a&gt;  It fined U.S.-based Mead Johnson 203.8 million yuan ($33.29 million); French food group Danone 172 million yuan; Biostime 162.9 million yuan; Abbott 77 million yuan; FrieslandCampina 48 million yuan and Fonterra 4 million yuan.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://newscvm.com/what-is-apo-amoxicillin-500mg-used-for-e9bb.pdf&quot;&gt;amoxicillin 200 mg 5 ml&lt;/a&gt;  The S&amp;P 500 hit a record high early in the session, boostedby gains in Apple after a bullish research note, butlackluster results from McDonald&apos;s Corp. weighed on theDow and S&amp;P, which reversed gains to trade slightly lower.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.md-interiors.co.uk/ehealthorgtz-a6a4.pdf&quot;&gt;www.admedsol.com&lt;/a&gt;  Reliance took over BSES Rajdhani Power Ltd (BRPL) in 2002 inpartnership with the Delhi state government. It was a rare forayby a private company into the power distribution business, whichis mostly controlled by India&apos;s 28 states.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://newscvm.com/land-institute-prairie-festival-e9bb.pdf#shout&quot;&gt;land institute prairie festival 2017&lt;/a&gt;  The foundation that runs the zoos, known as Fundazoo, has asked an administrative tribunal to block the closure, foundation spokesman Eduardo Bolanos said Saturday. It argues that its contract to run the zoos has been renewed through 2024.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
