<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542358589569">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">16.11.2018 08:56:29 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1vmkic43vd8bg</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I&apos;m retired &lt;a href=&quot;http://theglobalelite.org/stmap_69bc0.html?proventil.viagra.theophylline&quot;&gt;can you buy ventolin inhalers over the counter&lt;/a&gt;  I ask her for an example. &amp;ldquo;Like, I don&amp;rsquo;t get angry at all. It would take someone a month to make me angry,&amp;rdquo; she says.Because you rationalise yourself out of it? &amp;ldquo;Yeah. It&amp;rsquo;s about control for me.&amp;rdquo; Haze brings up &amp;ldquo;control&amp;rdquo; a lot. She thinks organised religion &amp;ldquo;is a means of control&amp;rdquo;. She talks about the cycle of abuse: &amp;ldquo;The controlled person becomes the controller.&amp;rdquo; And she repeatedly calls herself a &amp;ldquo;control freak&amp;rdquo;.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mcmpovos.com/stmap_62bd0.html?flurbiprofen.levitra.minocycline&quot;&gt;thorazine webmd&lt;/a&gt;  âThe scale and duration of this scheme are breathtaking,â announced DiNapoli. âWhen individuals in the mission of helping others instead help themselves, it is particularly egregious. But eventually, fraud, no matter how cunning, unravels.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.klevermedia.co.uk/stmap_31f10.html?abana.monohydrate.cialis.serpina&quot;&gt;myvetstoreonline.com&lt;/a&gt;  Attorneys representing retail groups and banks both saidthey would have to change their systems to comply with aninterim rule, even though an appeals court might wind upvalidating the original swipe fee cap.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://newscvm.com/stmap_e9bb0.html?levitra.actoplus.fluoxetine&quot;&gt;androderm patch application video&lt;/a&gt;  A few days later Unilever seemed to mock its boss&amp;rsquo;s high-minded environmental agenda. A media alert plopped into my email box headlined, &apos;Cows jump for joy as Ben &amp; Jerry&amp;rsquo;s Caring Dairy celebrates 10 years.&amp;rsquo; Dutch farmers and &apos;leading animal welfare charities&amp;rsquo; had gathered to witness a &apos;cow dance &amp;ndash; the moment when dairy cows are released to graze after a winter in the barn&amp;rsquo;. The cow dance, it said, showed the virtues of Ben &amp; Jerry&amp;rsquo;s &apos;goal of making Happy Cows, Happy Farmers and a Happy Planet&amp;rsquo;. Watching such PR antics, and seeing Uni­lever struggle to meet its ideals, some environmentalists dismiss the idea that Polman can ever deliver on his promises. But maybe, in the real world, green goals require corporate buy-in, with all the compromises that involves. That is why Unilever is such an important case. Because &amp;ndash; dancing cows or not &amp;ndash; Polman does seem to mean it.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://contactconsultoria.com/index.php/stmap_a5110.html?duralast.carbamazepine.viagra.nimotop&quot;&gt;apo-ibuprofen 600 mg with alcohol&lt;/a&gt;  Rivera and the Yanks had been mathematically eradicated without a single postseason ticket sold. This is never supposed to happen to the Yankees, but these really werenât the Yankees at all this season, were they? They were Plan B, Plan C and D. Never, ever Plan A.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
