<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542503528745">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 01:12:08 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1a13wofkcg8vv</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>What line of work are you in? &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dollingstownfc.com/what-happens-if-you-take-clomid-late-in-your-cycle-6865.pdf&quot;&gt;100mg clomid chances of multiples&lt;/a&gt;  Oaktree looked at selling the company in 2011, pursuing apossible deal with the world&apos;s biggest spirits group Diageo and then later considering a listing on the Warsawbourse before eventually deciding to keep hold of it.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.md-interiors.co.uk/jubilee-pharmacy-vernal-ut-a6a4.pdf&quot;&gt;royal jubilee pharmacy hours&lt;/a&gt;  They also testified he had insisted that most of his children be born at home so they wouldn&apos;t have birth certificates or social security numbers. The women also testified he kept the children from seeing doctors, home-schooled them, made them follow an extreme vegetarian diet and enforced his will with regular beatings.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.md-interiors.co.uk/enanthate-dosage-for-bodybuilding-a6a4.pdf#supporter&quot;&gt;trenbolone enanthate powder weight&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;We are a united city and the EDL are not welcome in Bradford,&quot; said Ratna Lachman, part of a group called Bradford Women for Peace, which held a vigil in the city&apos;s Centenary Square on Friday along with the Muslim Women&apos;s Council, Bradford Council for Mosques, anti -fascist campaign group Hope Not Hate and local trade union groups. The 200-strong group sang a specially written peace song and tied 7.5km of green ribbon around the city as they made their opposition to the EDL clear.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.haroldwhitefuneraldirectors.co.uk/pelvic-joint-flexibility-exercises-bd82.pdf&quot;&gt;joint flex glucosamine gel&lt;/a&gt;  Yoga Raves bring the yoga studio to the club -- so don&apos;t forget your glow sticks (and glitter). Combining music, movement and meditation in a single space, Yoga Raves also promote drug-free fun. Many of these raves begin with a guided meditation as a warm up, to lead into a more free movement.According to the not-for-profit movement&apos;s website &lt;a href=&quot;http://Yoga Rave&quot; target=&quot;_hplink&quot;&gt;Yogarave.org&lt;/a&gt;, &quot;The Yoga Rave Project will bring the spiritual element back to celebration and the way we have fun, offering a drug free alternative for our youth to gather and release their energy and tension.&quot;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.artofliving.org/us-en&quot; target=&quot;_hplink&quot;&gt;The Art Of Living Foundation&lt;/a&gt;, which funds and organizes &lt;a href=&quot;http://Yogaraves.org&quot; target=&quot;_hplink&quot;&gt;Yogaraves.org&lt;/a&gt;, is not the only initiative propelling the yoga dance party. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.jivamuktiyoga.com/&quot; target=&quot;_hplink&quot;&gt;Jivamukti&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.laughinglotus.com/&quot; target=&quot;_hplink&quot;&gt;Laughing &lt;/a&gt;Lotus are among the yoga schools supporting the combination of yoga and &quot;getting down.&quot;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.yogadork.com/news/grab-your-glow-ga-sticks-yoga-raves-all-the-rage/&quot; target=&quot;_hplink&quot;&gt;Yogadork.com might have said it best:&lt;/a&gt; &quot;The Yoga Rave: a place where you can totally trip out drug free, get friendly with your fellow man/woman and wake up in your own bed the next morning (if you so choose).&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.weymouthskatepark.co.uk/action-medical-equipment-elmhurst-il-6ae3.pdf&quot;&gt;action medical equipment&lt;/a&gt;  Camuto, who founded Nine West in the â70s and now makes shoes under his own name as well as for Jessica Simpson, BCBG and others, has put the sprawling 22,000-square-foot home is back on the market at a reduced price â at  a time when Hamptons mansions are selling faster than Camuto-crafted Tory Burch flats.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
