<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542469328566">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">17.11.2018 15:42:08 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.yykmkivff7m4</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Have you got any ? &lt;a href=&quot;https://muv.asia/stmap_bf280.html?viagra.cytotec.intagra&quot;&gt;1285 muscle and xm recovery side effects&lt;/a&gt;  This notion of power &amp;ndash; that all it requires is &quot;the will to do what the other guy wouldn&apos;t&quot; &amp;ndash; is at the core of the fringe right&apos;s last-ditch push to stop the Affordable Care Act, popularly known as Obamacare, from taking effect. These conservatives&apos; big idea, pushed by Sens. Mike Lee of Utah, Ted Cruz of Texas and Marco Rubio of Florida, as well as outside groups like the Heritage Foundation&apos;s political activist arm, is that Republicans should refuse to fund the government beyond the end of September (when currently authorized funding runs out) unless the president agrees to defund Obamacare. A popular variation would involve refusing to raise the debt ceiling unless Obama agrees to the right&apos;s terms. With the law&apos;s health insurance exchanges opening up on Oct. 1, conservatives see this as their last chance to scrap the law. These men of will then figure that they&apos;ll prevail because they&apos;re willing to do what Obama won&apos;t: shut down the government or default on U.S. debts and thus imperil the country&apos;s credit rating.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
