<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542534155605">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 09:42:35 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.4374b0wn3wfa</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>An estate agents &lt;a href=&quot;http://archieandtherug.com/how-to-cancel-vydox-9392.pdf#rely&quot;&gt;vydox plus work&lt;/a&gt;  Saif al-Islam Gaddafi, who was seen as the most likely successor to his father, was captured by militias in the desert town of Ubari in November 2011 - allegedly trying to flee the country - and has been held in the western town of Zintan ever since.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ecorporationbd.com/talbotstmedicalcentreie-aaa8.pdf&quot;&gt;lacienegapharmacy.com&lt;/a&gt;  The most likely deal may be for Nokia to buy Alcatel&apos;s wireless division, which includes a big presence in the lucrative U.S. market where NSN has traditionally been weak, one of the sources said. That would leave Alcatel-Lucent to focus its fast-growing IP routing and optical business, the person said.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.klevermedia.co.uk/tpharma1com-31f1.pdf&quot;&gt;mediscountpharmacy.com&lt;/a&gt;  While the possibility of a reduction in bond buying wouldtypically push Treasury yields higher, yields fell to theirlowest level in a week on Thursday, driven by technical tradingin what is typically a time of lower volume in the market.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.elegantandwild.co.uk/brain-forza-75b3.pdf&quot;&gt;brain forza lion 39s mane&lt;/a&gt;  FRANKFURT, Oct 23 (Reuters) - Primacom, Germany&apos;sfourth-largest cable operator, wants an active role in themarket&apos;s consolidation, its managing director said, and hasalready made bids for certain assets of Tele Columbus and for Deutsche Telekabel.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.chris-cancercommunity.com/wenn-bekommt-man-viagra-auf-rezept-b01a.pdf&quot;&gt;precio viagra generico en espaa&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;Google started out saying they were going to do a broad set of things. They hired Larry Brilliant, and they got fantastic publicity. And then they shut it all down. Now they&apos;re just doing their core thing. Fine. But the actors who just do their core thing are not going to uplift the poor,&quot; he said.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
