<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542624351725">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 10:45:51 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1ep6izfr3jqhb</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>A packet of envelopes &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mikasafloors.com/fematril-ingredients-bdec.pdf#effort&quot;&gt;buy fematril&lt;/a&gt;  Doctors at Akron Children’s Hospital said that they had to intervene when the Hershberger family ended chemotherapy for their daughter Sarah in June because it was making her extremely sick. The hospital said Sarah Hershberger’s leukemia was very treatable but warned she would die within a year without chemotherapy.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tarokasongbad.com/keys4healthykidscom-e3c4.pdf&quot;&gt;keys4healthykids.com&lt;/a&gt;  Lord Owen, who was on the advisory board of a private equity firm - Terra Firma - said private equity had its uses but added: &quot;What they basically do is fatten it up over a few years, invest in order to sell at very high substantial prices.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://sjofartsbygningen.no/neurontin-for-back-leg-pain-7ef0.pdf&quot;&gt;neurontin 300 mg for sleep&lt;/a&gt;  Actually, the Dixiecrats were the conservative Dems at the time. THEY filibustered the Civil Rights Act and eventually went to the Republican Party once they knew that the Dems would support civil rights. The Civil Rights Act turned the entire South from the Democratic Party to supporting the Republicans.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://reflectiveteens.com/zofran-4-mg-im-213a.pdf&quot;&gt;ondansetron 4mg/2ml&lt;/a&gt;  In January of this year, Gallup found that 64 percent of Americans support outlawing abortion in the second trimester, and a whopping 80 percent in the third. A National Journal poll last month reported that more women (50 percent) than men (46 percent) support banning abortions after 20 weeks, except in cases of rape and incest. Nearly two-thirds want Roe v. Wade to stand. Most think abortion should be legal, but safe.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://sjofartsbygningen.no/meds-4uscom-7ef0.pdf#glove&quot;&gt;drug-storerx.com&lt;/a&gt;  The Stoxx Europe 600 Index slipped 0.3 percent to 308.23 at9:20 a.m. in London. The equity benchmark dropped 0.2 percentyesterday, to its lowest level since Sept. 9, after U.S. HouseSpeaker John Boehner said he will attach conditions beforepassing a bill to increase the federal borrowing limit. S&amp;P 500Index futures were unchanged today, while the MSCI Asia PacificIndex gained 0.3 percent.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
