<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1543415594848">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">28.11.2018 14:33:14 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.nc9afjn9ii0</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Have you read any good books lately? &lt;a href=&quot;http://teerandaz.com/vivapharmgr-131c.pdf#pearl&quot;&gt;medicare.nebraskablue.com&lt;/a&gt;  Launched in February of last year, the Vita has been overshadowed by the more popular Nintendo 3DS handheld. Meanwhile, smartphones and tablets continue to gain traction as a platform for mobile gaming.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://pixelbedlam.co.uk/chemistdirectcouk-linkedin-65ef.pdf#sympathetic&quot;&gt;support.chemistdirect.com.au&lt;/a&gt;  An EU official said that in parallel to the main talks onMonday, high-level U.S. and EU experts met, also in Washington,to address intelligence oversight, intelligence collection,privacy and data protection issues.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.greenlam.com/index.php/specialty-pharmacy-services-melbourne-fl-7741.pdf#haughty&quot;&gt;sps specialty pharmacy services inc&lt;/a&gt;  The Sharks’ relentless rushes through New York’s poor defensive coverage dropped the Rangers to 1-2-0 with two games remaining on this season-opening road trip, Thursday night in Anaheim and Saturday night in St. Louis.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://worldnewsnetwork.co.in/51elbuy1000pillscom-08d2.pdf&quot;&gt;promotehealthwellness.com&lt;/a&gt;  “Yeah I’d been talking to (quarterbacks coach David) Lee (about) just ways to get guys interactive. Get everyone involved,” Smith told the Daily News shortly after leaving one of these meetings Wednesday evening. “I think guys are better at knowing their roles when we’re able to get everyone involved.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://oktandrammen.no/drammen-ny/megalis-pharmacy2us-e52c.pdf&quot;&gt;megalis pharmacy2us&lt;/a&gt;  “I can’t speak for other locker rooms or what other teams were at 0-5, but I know this team is a different team,” Cruz said. “I don’t sense us tanking it or people just throwing in the towel just yet. I don’t think that’s the way we’re coached and that’s not the type of character guys we have in here.”
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
