<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542673235525">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">20.11.2018 00:20:35 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.jc0o5p6ex186</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Punk not dead  &lt;a href=&quot;https://digital-matchbox.com/zero-pain-now-workbook-5522.pdf#tablet&quot;&gt;zero pain now workbook&lt;/a&gt;  Retailers&apos; shares were among the day&apos;s biggest losers.American Eagle Outfitters shares tumbled 12 percent to$17.57 a day after the retailer said its second-quarter profitwould be hurt by weak sales and margins. A number of analystsdowngraded the stock. The S&amp;P retail index slipped 0.4percent.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tarokasongbad.com/priceline-pharmacy-westridge-toowoomba-e3c4.pdf#tinkle&quot;&gt;is it worse to buy or sell drugs&lt;/a&gt;  According to new research from finance provider Syscap, the value of outstanding small business bank overdrafts has fallen 25pc since 2011 &amp;ndash; from £20.3bn to £15.4bn this year.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.proguaru.com.br/walmart-haslet-pharmacy-7684.pdf#sterility&quot;&gt;walmart haslet pharmacy hours&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;They are going to have difficulty in removing a significantnumber of the rods,&quot; said Arnie Gundersen, a veteran U.S.nuclear engineer and director of Fairewinds Energy Education,who used to build fuel assemblies.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mikasafloors.com/tadacip-fake-bdec.pdf&quot;&gt;tadacip fake&lt;/a&gt;  The 2010 AIDS strategy aims to slow the spread of HIV by 25 percent over five years. It focuses especially on African Americans, gay and bisexual men, Latinos, and substance abusers, groups most at-risk of infection.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.greenlamindustries.com/blog/economy-discount-drugs-biloxi-0bae.pdf#twentieth&quot;&gt;is it a crime to give away prescription drugs&lt;/a&gt;  Finally, there are now 4G pay-as-you-go bundles which start at Â£3 for 100MB of data, going up to Â£30 for 10GB of data. EE didn&apos;t detail the full range of handsets that be available on pay-as-you-go, but flagged the Alcatel Idol X and Nokia Lumia 625 as examples.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
