<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542555049151">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 15:30:49 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1hu5issdue9f8</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Can you hear me OK? &lt;a href=&quot;http://sjofartsbygningen.no/ductus-arteriosus-prostaglandin-7ef0.pdf#ruin&quot;&gt;prostaglandin kidney arteriole&lt;/a&gt;  The Senate, as expected, passed a straight-forward emergency-funding measure on Friday to keep the government running through November 15. But first, it stripped out Republican language to end funding for the healthcare law known as Obamacare.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lovemycase.com/buying-nolvadex-in-canada-f2c2.pdf&quot;&gt;buy nolvadex&lt;/a&gt;  “They really know what is necessary to win and what it takes. Everyone wants to win but not everyone knows how. They&apos;re creative, they&apos;re intuitive and they want to get an edge in every way they can,” Lamoriello said of his new bosses. “I&apos;m comfortable with that and I&apos;m honored to be here and stay here in New Jersey with the New Jersey Devils.”
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://newscvm.com/metformin-tablet-dosage-e9bb.pdf&quot;&gt;is glucophage 500mg safe during pregnancy&lt;/a&gt;  When reached for comment about the claims of racism in the song, Wilson told &amp;#8220;Nightline&amp;#8221; Wednesday night, &amp;#8220;I just really love Chinese food and that is why I wrote a song about it.&amp;#8221;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.chris-cancercommunity.com/coversyl-rxlist-b01a.pdf&quot;&gt;coversyl rxlist&lt;/a&gt;  On the ninth anniversary of his major-league debut, David Wright homered in the first and had a single and scored a run on Juan Lagares&apos; first home run at Citi Field, a three-run shot in the fourth. Marlon Byrd slammed his team-leading 17th homer into the second-deck in left-field in the first right after Wright, the first back-to-back homers for the Mets this season.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dollingstownfc.com/renagel-rxlist-6865.pdf&quot;&gt;renagel rxlist&lt;/a&gt;  The newest inversions are attempts to game the rules by buying large enough companies to make the argument that they have &quot;substantial business&quot; abroad. As the FT points out, some of these acquisitions come to tens of billions of dollars, so you can see the method in their madness.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
