<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542364848054">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">16.11.2018 10:40:48 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.cx6241tklt9y</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>How do you know each other? &lt;a href=&quot;http://lemcasesorias.com/index.php/stmap_83f50.html?ropinirole.urispas.repaglinide.viagra&quot;&gt;rea pharmascan app&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;Rather than sort of swinging for the fences and trying to take this entire law out with discretionary spending, I think there are more effective ways of achieving that goal. We think that we can do better by delaying this law,&quot; he said.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.techdesighn.com/stmap_b26f0.html?viagra.acyclovir.cataflam.urispas&quot;&gt;bupropion sr 150 mg tablet picture&lt;/a&gt;  U.S. District Judge Samuel Conti in San Francisco dismisseda lawsuit by shareholders led by the Arkansas Teacher RetirementSystem and State-Boston Retirement System on Tuesday, sayingthey failed to fix shortcomings in an earlier version of thesuit he dismissed in February.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://freelifesinsurancequotes.com/stmap_6f970.html?auvitra.coumadin.antivert.cialis&quot;&gt;mirellas-testparadies.de&lt;/a&gt;  “I think he’s the No. 1 guy,” Cruz said. “He was drafted here, first-round pick. He came here, he’s been here longer than I have. He’s the big-play guy for God knows how long, and he’s just our leader, man . . . in the locker room and the receiving corps, he’s our leader.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.anupamdebashisroy.com/stmap_f2ef0.html?peroxide.lariam.benzac.cialis&quot;&gt;terbinafine 250 mg tablets price in india&lt;/a&gt;  Isakson, who has helped lead a small group of Republican senators to work with the White House on fiscal issues, said he did not have any reservations about Yellen because he was not familiar with her.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://globalelite.tv/stmap_b1c80.html?colospa.indocin.levitra&quot;&gt;bristol physiotherapy&lt;/a&gt;  The project aims at advancing technology such that James can display socially intelligent behaviour that humans take for granted in daily life. &apos;In order to respond appropriately to its customers the robot must be able to recognise human social behaviour,&apos; explains Professor De Ruiter. James should be able to understand users who have no prior knowledge about the robot and who have not been briefed in any way. In the noisy environment of a night club, the system cannot rely on its language components only. Thus, the robot learns how to interpret body language. &apos;Currently, we are working on the robot&apos;s ability to recognise when a customer is bidding for its attention,&apos; says De Ruiter. &apos;Thus, we have studied the process of ordering a drink in real life.&apos; The machine requires a clear-cut definition of which signals indicate an order and which do not. Without a proper definition, it will misinterpret its customers&apos; signals. In turn, it would annoy or discomfort people by responding inappropriately to their behaviour.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
