<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542491844254">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">17.11.2018 21:57:24 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1t1htgi2p7dm2</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>What&apos;s the exchange rate for euros? &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.layeredonline.com/vermox-100-mg-oral-suspension-dd54.pdf&quot;&gt;what is vermox tablet used for&lt;/a&gt;  The duck&apos;s arrival Friday will kick off the monthlong Pittsburgh International Festival of Firsts, which features theater, dance, music and visual arts from around the world. The duck will be moored downtown until late October.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://accentresurfacing.com/does-naproxen-contain-aspirin-or-ibuprofen-4110.pdf&quot;&gt;does motrin 800 raise blood pressure&lt;/a&gt;  Mr Johnson told Mayor&amp;rsquo;s Question Time in City Hall hinted that the use body-worn cameras would have helped with the incident involving Andrew Mitchell, who resigned as Chief Whip after being accused by police officers of calling them &amp;ldquo;plebs&amp;rdquo;.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.infocalcbba.edu.bo/myogenix-adipro-max-review-9e88.pdf#normally&quot;&gt;adipro max&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;Sympathetic&quot; federal sources within the Department of Justice and FBI have shared information about the case with CAIR, including assurances that the 27-year-old was unarmed. But Shibly declined to elaborate on anything else sources may have elucidated.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ecorporationbd.com/nexushealthcapcom-aaa8.pdf#ensure&quot;&gt;chcmedical.com.hk&lt;/a&gt;  Long bets on NYMEX gasoline futures, which the previous weekhad hit their lowest level since 2010, recovered just ahead of ablistering rally that was fueled by a series of refineryglitches this week.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.weymouthskatepark.co.uk/what-to-do-if-cialis-doesnt-work-6ae3.pdf#corruption&quot;&gt;can you take 20mg cialis every day&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;The issue of the Yasukuni Shrine relates to whether or not Japan can correctly recognize and face up to the history of invasion of the Japanese militarists and whether or not they can respect the feelings of the people of China and the other victim nations in Asia,&quot; the ministry said.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
