<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542358093539">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">16.11.2018 08:48:13 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1g2p4gsa3t8qm</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I&apos;ve just started at  &lt;a href=&quot;https://accentresurfacing.com/stmap_41100.html?viagra.flomax.champix&quot;&gt;ziziphus jujuba seed extract&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;My brother-in-law lives close by and was helping pull outpeople, dead and alive, all night. He&apos;s very shaken. I&apos;ve comenow with some friends just to see how it all ends,&quot; said ManuelGarcia, one of the onlookers.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ipepalmas.com.br/stmap_7fc80.html?cialis.flavoxate.forzest.prazosin-hcl&quot;&gt;was ist tadalista&lt;/a&gt;  Worryingly for the entertainment industry, Ofcom’s report found that there exists a group of “hardcore pirates” and that their illegal activities account for close to three quarters of all copyright infringement.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.md-interiors.co.uk/stmap_a6a40.html?levitra.pulmicort.conjugated&quot;&gt;over the counter viagra supplement&lt;/a&gt;  A bridge is classified as functionally obsolete if its design is outdated. It may have lower load-carrying capacity, narrower shoulders or less clearance underneath than bridges built to current standards.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mikasafloors.com/stmap_bdec0.html?atomoxetine.cialis.spironolactone.rhinocort&quot;&gt;priceline pharmacy cairns central&lt;/a&gt;  The striking workers, at chains such as McDonald&apos;s and Taco Bell, want their pay raised to $15 an hour, more than double the current federal minimum wage of $7.25. In his State of the Union Address this year, President Obama proposed raising the minimum wage to $9 and tying it to inflation, but so far the proposals have gone nowhere in Congress.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.weymouthskatepark.co.uk/stmap_6ae30.html?esomeprazole.viagra.viprofil&quot;&gt;arbor pharmacy guelph&lt;/a&gt;  They argued the standard general exception used in tradeagreements dating back to 1947 should be enough to address anyconcerns about protecting tobacco regulations. (Reporting by Doug Palmer; Editing by Phil Berlowitz)
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
