<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1543414793197">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">28.11.2018 14:19:53 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.9azjavrr536x</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>What do you study? &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ssvoverath.de/long-term-effects-of-abusing-prescription-drugs-c3db.pdf&quot;&gt;most abused prescription drugs canada&lt;/a&gt;  O&apos;Sullivan, of East Moriches, pleaded not guilty to multiple counts of predatory sexual assault, rape in the first degree, criminal sexual act in the first degree, sexual abuse in the first degree, burglary in the first degree and criminal use of a firearm.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sensors.co.uk/is-it-safe-to-take-2-ibuprofen-every-day-9874.pdf&quot;&gt;is it safe to take ibuprofen after taking aleve&lt;/a&gt;  Sikorsky, which builds Black Hawk and Seahawk helicopters for the U.S. military, had announced last week that it would lay off nearly 2,000 workers beginning Monday, and possibly as many as 5,000 if the shutdown continued into November.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.brentwood-karting.com/index.php/mesalamine-rxlist-6e56.pdf&quot;&gt;mesalamine rxlist&lt;/a&gt;  This time, Verlander didn’t allow a baserunner until Josh Reddick drew a one-out walk in the sixth — but the no-hit bid remained until Cespedes’ single the next inning. The hardest hit ball was a fly to the center field warning track by Stephen Vogt in the sixth.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://public-admin.co.uk/ffspiritnet-3c8d.pdf#events&quot;&gt;musclemaxx.de&lt;/a&gt;  Instead of sticking to their established production method — the band members showing each other their compositions in rehearsals, making arrangements and cutting demos before entering the studio — they decided to record the songs live and play all the instruments themselves (they don’t have an official drummer).
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.brentwood-karting.com/index.php/propecia-pharmacy2u-6e56.pdf&quot;&gt;propecia pharmacy2u&lt;/a&gt;  Asked about the most-pressing problems in the world and the ones that scientists can best help solve, Gates pointed to nuclear and bioterrorism as the thing we most want to avoid &amp;#8212; but not the world&amp;#8217; biggest problem.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
