<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542502644319">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 00:57:24 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.kxqe8sfltx37</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Whereabouts are you from? &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.proguaru.com.br/roids-shopnet-review-7684.pdf&quot;&gt;www.fruthpharmacy.com&lt;/a&gt;  Greater Manchester Police Chief Constable Sir Peter Fahy said: &quot;It&amp;#039;s always on anniversaries like this that you recall what an awful day it was - a huge tragedy for the families, the colleagues and the loved ones of Fiona and Nicola.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.proguaru.com.br/marionmedcom-7684.pdf#email&quot;&gt;medecinetravail.canalblog.com&lt;/a&gt;  I can&apos;t help but wonder at the type of people who think abuse/rudeness is something which they can get away with because they cannot be seen when they do it. Perhaps it is ok to make a point forcefully or even to rile against stupidity, but offensive comments are just wrong. Part of me thinks Twitter accounts should be traceable so that the abusers can be outed, but this could open up witch hunts?
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tarokasongbad.com/libbera-gotas-dosis-e3c4.pdf&quot;&gt;libbera d gotas dosis&lt;/a&gt;  A key issue in the city&apos;s pending Chapter 9 bankruptcy is whether Detroit&apos;s state-appointed emergency manager, Kevyn Orr, may treat certain general obligation bonds as unsecured debt on a par with its pension obligations, and repay them at just pennies on the dollar.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.proguaru.com.br/viagra-tablet-prices-7684.pdf&quot;&gt;free viagra 100mg&lt;/a&gt;  The increasingly fragmented and brutal nature of the war was illustrated by an incident in Homs province, where gunmen loyal to Assad shot dead at least six mediators sent to try to reconcile warring sectarian groups in an area where opposing sides had until now been able to coexist.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://lemcasesorias.com/index.php/biosuperfood-formula-f20-83f5.pdf&quot;&gt;biosuperfood formula f20&lt;/a&gt;  If a deal looks &quot;too good to be true, it probably is,&quot; says Biggs. He points caution to fast moving-products, such as everyday household items like toothpaste, shampoos and cosmetics that are marked half off when they normally would be full price at reputable stores. He also suggests consumers should &quot;be cautious if you&apos;re buying goods that you would be consuming or would give to a child,&quot; and buy those products from a reputable venue if possible.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
