<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542366894929">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">16.11.2018 11:14:54 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1l0wubesplptq</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I want to make a withdrawal &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dollingstownfc.com/stmap_68650.html?beconase.levitra.thyroxine&quot;&gt;pristinewater-treatment.com&lt;/a&gt;  Weiner says the so-called &quot;Jenkins Rule&quot; entitles players to refuse to answer the league&apos;s questions, though the league may see things differently and seek to apply stricter punishment to the players that haven&apos;t cooperated.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://freelifesinsurancequotes.com/stmap_6f970.html?viagra.lipothin.keppra&quot;&gt;stlmedclinic.com&lt;/a&gt;  The Rogue brewery lives up to its name by daring to brew interesting, non-traditional beers using off-the-wall ingredients like peanut butter, banana and bacon. They even went so far as to brew a beer with a wild yeast cultivated from microbes growing in the brewmaster&apos;s beard. So, one with juniper berries aged in spruce gin barrels almost seems tame in comparison. The pair of Johns in the name refers to the collaboration of Rogue Brewmaster John Maier and Rogue Master Distiller John Couchot, who distills Rogue Spruce Gin and then supplies the barrels in which this juniper pale ale is aged. A bit of a homegrown beer, &quot;John John Ale&quot; features Rogue Micro Hopyard Revolution hops and the Dare and Risk strains of barley from Rogue&apos;s micro farms. Upon sipping, you discover an effervescent, bright piney freshness, with flavors of spruce and juniper dominating but not overpowering. The myriad ingredients used to make the spruce gin include spruce, juniper berries, ginger, fresh cucumber, orris root, orange peel, lemon peel, tangerine, grains of paradise, angelica root, coriander and grain neutral spirit, which contribute to the ale&apos;s dry, complex, spicy finish.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.proguaru.com.br/stmap_76840.html?cyclosporine.cyklokapron.fluvoxamine.viagra&quot;&gt;can i take ibuprofen before a flu shot&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;Our conservation efforts are first and foremost focused on protecting readiness and eliminating the need for restrictions on training,&quot; said John Conger, acting deputy undersecretary of defense for installations and environment.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jalapaoecolodge.com.br/index.php/stmap_7abb0.html?levitra.aventyl.trental&quot;&gt;write prescription amoxicillin oral suspension&lt;/a&gt;  The new sense of optimism sent U.S. stocks higher on Friday,extending gains from a major rally in the previous session.. But U.S. Treasury bills maturing in lateNovember and throughout December spiked as banks and major moneymarket funds shy away from holding debt with any risk of delayedinterest or principal payments.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://muv.asia/stmap_bf280.html?serophene.levitra.kamagra&quot;&gt;buy cheap ofloxacin&lt;/a&gt;  &amp;ldquo;An explosive device that went off inside a passenger bus at [2:05 p.m.] today in Volgograd caused human casualties,&amp;rdquo; Dmitry Parvlov, a spokesman for the National Anti-terrorist Committee, told Rossiya-24. He said authorities were working to prevent other possible explosions in the city.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
