<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1543411507977">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">28.11.2018 13:25:07 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.l28qytu6ify9</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I quite like cooking &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bombeirodf.com.br/the-perfect-sculpt-discount-code-50f8.pdf#calling&quot;&gt;the perfect sculpt wax bean&lt;/a&gt;  The details of the case — an unarmed black teen gunned down by an older man suspicious of the boy — has drawn parallels to the fatal slaying of Trayvon Martin, 17, in Florida. Though George Zimmerman was acquitted of murder charges in that case, demonstrators have protested the verdict and believe the neighborhood watch volunteer racially profiled the boy. Zimmerman said he shot the teen in self-defense, and the six jurors agreed.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sensors.co.uk/formedical-9874.pdf&quot;&gt;formedica curitiba endereco&lt;/a&gt;  On one hand there&amp;#039;s the right of prisoners to smoke in the privacy of what amounts to their home, and be treated in the same way as those living in the wider community. On the other there&amp;#039;s the rights of non-smoking staff and fellow prisoners to live and work in an environment free from the risks of second-hand smoke (SHS).
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.greenlam.com/index.php/quest-nutrition-protein-shake-recipes-7741.pdf&quot;&gt;quest nutrition protein bars nutrition facts info&lt;/a&gt;  Although he would not list the groups, he said several have met to cooperate by sharing polling information and research, and also to minimize the risks that that the television advertisements they buy will compete with one another. &amp;#8221;Crossroads encouraged a number of the groups to share polling information, research and also to share the scheduling of their media buy information,&amp;#8221; he said.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://public-admin.co.uk/perfecthealthcoid-3c8d.pdf&quot;&gt;perfecthealth.co.id&lt;/a&gt;  The cameras are always rolling in Hollywood! When the stars aren&apos;t on the red carpet, you&apos;ll more than likely find them on set filming their next great blockbuster. Check out these famous actors and a...
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://worldnewsnetwork.co.in/hooluxmedicalcom-08d2.pdf&quot;&gt;safehealthychildren.org&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;Many of the casualties are women and children. They arrived with their pupil dilated, cold limbs and foam in their mouths. The doctors say these are typical symptoms of nerve gas victims,&quot; Baker said.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
