<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1543365867942">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">28.11.2018 00:44:27 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.bu7ukzl5iqpo</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Do you know what extension he&apos;s on? &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bombeirodf.com.br/stmap_50f80.html?levitra.arjuna.danocrine.zhevitra&quot;&gt;koshland pharmacy jobs&lt;/a&gt;  Yes. I think we ended the second quarter around the 65,000 level or so. We also have, obviously -- there&apos;s 11,000 subscribers that started as digital only that we fortunately were able to also participate in a home delivery as well. So they are no longer digital-only subscribers. I think there&apos;s -- as I alluded to in my remarks, there&apos;s a number of things, frankly, that we&apos;re working on in terms of enhancements, additional digital platforms and potentially a fairly exciting add to the consumer experience by blending some assets that Gannett is uniquely positioned to do. I can&apos;t say more about that, but that&apos;s something, as I alluded to in my remarks, that we&apos;re going to be looking at very, very carefully over the next few months and expect to have some news on probably in the late fall. So while we are obviously continue to be very focused on new digital subscribers, really pleased with the beginnings of some of the new college programs that we&apos;re bringing on and expect to see more of that. We&apos;re total -- we&apos;re focused more on the totality of the effort. The other thing I&apos;d say, Bill, because I think sometimes folks compare apple to oranges vis-à-vis our numbers, I think the New York Times has done just a fabulous job on their strategy and what they&apos;ve done and they talk about 700,000 paying digital subscribers. And we&apos;ve got a couple of metrics, and the one I think that is the most comparable to that several hundred thousand is the one that Victoria shared, which is that we have 1,300,000 all-access subscribers that have activated their digital part of their subscription that they&apos;re obviously paying. So the apples-to-apples number with the New York Times several hundred thousand, which is a phenomenal -- which is phenomenal, is 1.3 million for us. We then added that additional metric of simply brand new digital-only subs, an important additional metric, but we focus on the totality of it. We focus on that 1.3 million that have activated. And frankly, that&apos;s right on track with what we had planned, and we expect that number to continue to grow over the next few quarters.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
