<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542626346817">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 11:19:06 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.742uknuxazt7</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Nice to meet you &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.md-interiors.co.uk/bf-medic-aps-a6a4.pdf&quot;&gt;purepharm ltd&lt;/a&gt;  She has seen a sharp uptick in evictions under the Ellis Act, the state law that allows a landlord to evict all tenants of a building if it is being taken off the rental market. And now she and the other tenants in her building &amp;mdash; some elderly and disabled &amp;mdash; have also received eviction notices. She is facing the prospect of leaving the neighborhood where she has lived for three decades.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.elegantandwild.co.uk/ikiapharm-korres-75b3.pdf#haunt&quot;&gt;ikiapharm frezyderm&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;Preppies are people who like the classics,&quot; said first-time author Nunn, executive chef of Grange restaurant in Westwood, New Jersey. &quot;Like that Brooks Brothers navy blazer you can wear for 20 years.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.elegantandwild.co.uk/microlactin-powder-for-dogs-75b3.pdf&quot;&gt;microlactin powder for dogs&lt;/a&gt;  &amp;ldquo;She started with how wonderful it was to be here, obviously, and then she told me she wouldn&amp;rsquo;t like to be a judge herself as it is so difficult to choose between the authors.&amp;rdquo;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://reflectiveteens.com/elearning-healthcare-213a.pdf#harp&quot;&gt;elearning.healthscotland.com&lt;/a&gt;  With any product, even iconic ones like the iPhone, sooner or later, the time comes when it begins to lose it&amp;#8217;s claim to superiority and must again establish it&amp;#8217;s unique identity. Apple has always been about this, the ability to reinvent itself. I think the continuing challenge for Apple and the iPhone brand is the ability to do this. If the past is any indication, I don&amp;#8217;t think investors or customers have much to worry about.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lucky-websolutions.com/bigsportsmedcom-0a7b.pdf#tumbled&quot;&gt;healthtech.net&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;Criminals who are successful in their usual endeavors are often undone by a foray into art theft,&quot; said Robert Korzinek, a fine art underwriter at insurer Hiscox. &quot;They steal these works of art ... and then they have the problem that they can&apos;t dispose of them.&quot;
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
