<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542567453453">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 18:57:33 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.j3899c6n7qhj</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>What&apos;s the exchange rate for euros? &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dollingstownfc.com/foodmarble-aire-6865.pdf&quot;&gt;foodmarble aire&lt;/a&gt;  At the federal level, the Garrett Lee Smith grant program provides $30 million a year to states and tribes for follow-up care for youth who have attempted suicide or to cover training for teachers, coaches, juvenile justice workers or other people who work closely with teens. More than 600,000 people have been trained through these programs, according to the Suicide Prevention Resource Center.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://stsmihajlopupin.edu.rs/rs/how-long-after-surgery-can-you-use-ibuprofen-3c56.pdf#artificial&quot;&gt;is advil pm the same as ibuprofen&lt;/a&gt;  One of the changes had an immediate effect for the Magpies. Moments after the restart Yoan Gouffran saw his dinked effort come off the post before Cabaye, who did not start because of a groin problem, smashed a fantastic 25-yard shot into the top corner.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://accentresurfacing.com/right-level-pharma-consultants-4110.pdf&quot;&gt;top pharma consultants in india&lt;/a&gt;  &amp;#x201c;We did what we&amp;#x2019;re supposed to do, taking on guys, and (the linebackers) did their job. They were in the right spot and they timed it just right and so it really was a team effort and us working together like we&amp;#x2019;re supposed to.&amp;#x2019;&amp;#x2019;
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://accentresurfacing.com/huntington-pharmacy-michigan-4110.pdf#endeavour&quot;&gt;huntington pharmacy huntsville al&lt;/a&gt;  During weeks of violence early this year, hotels reported sharp drops in occupancy rates and retailers a 30 percent fall in sales. With marchers now gathering each Saturday on the edge of the nationalist Ardoyne area, butcher Mark Maguire reckons it is costing half his shop’s weekly business.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.proguaru.com.br/b12-methylcobalamin-webmd-7684.pdf&quot;&gt;vitamin b12 methylcobalamin webmd&lt;/a&gt;  The strike is centred around Amplats mines near the town ofRustenburg in the restive platinum belt, where AMCU has poachedtens of thousands of members from the once unrivalled NationalUnion of Mineworkers (NUM) in a bloody turf war that has killeddozens of people the past 18 months.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
