<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542371235601">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">16.11.2018 12:27:15 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.5f0rxgdmk48r</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>My battery&apos;s about to run out &lt;a href=&quot;http://reflectiveteens.com/stmap_213a0.html?nelfinavir.cialis.deltasone&quot;&gt;wegmans williamsport pharmacy&lt;/a&gt;  AEG Live will continue to present its case and is expected to present a final flurry of videotaped testimony from Jackson&apos;s doctors on Friday. AEG Live&apos;s lawyers will also argue that the case be dismissed on Thursday.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://paradiseinmexico.com.mx/stmap_c13c0.html?levitra.aceon.betagan&quot;&gt;where can i get zenerx&lt;/a&gt;  There is still more work for Apple before the general public can get their hands on the new operating system; developers told Apple Insider that a range of applications, including Calendar, Contacts, Notes, Safari, Passbook, and others, still have problems.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://zoeydeutch.net/stmap_8f080.html?fertomid.xenical.levitra&quot;&gt;fertility blend in australia&lt;/a&gt;  Kate Moss, as always, looks stunning. When it comes to putting an outfit together nobody does it like our Mossy. The stylish wide leg trousers, simple grey tee, tuxedo jacket and saucy bondage belt... it&amp;#39;s all coming together beautifully.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://paradiseinmexico.com.mx/stmap_c13c0.html?betnovate.cialis.lanoxin&quot;&gt;tourmedica.pl&lt;/a&gt;  The living room forms the core of the suite, with unusual goat and stag head wall-pieces in one corner and colourful abstract paintings and photographs in another. While some of the art lacks the weight of those you&amp;rsquo;re likely to see in the Saatchi Gallery and the suite&amp;rsquo;s appearance as a whole might lack that immediate &amp;lsquo;wow&amp;rsquo; factor, the bathroom is a knockout. Here, in an installation by Celine Fitoussi, nearly 2,000 carved soap bars were stacked together to form the walls and guests are encouraged to carve their initials or other thoughts, adding a nice collaborative touch to the installation. The storytelling element of the engravings by former guests, limestone-style ceramic tiles and the brick-like textural appearance of the soap bars give the space an ancient architectural feel.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cabanadolago.com.br/index.php/stmap_ab8a0.html?hyzaar.avodart.cialis.glyset&quot;&gt;harga obat ivermectin untuk manusia&lt;/a&gt;  The FHA has played a critical role supporting the housingmarket by insuring mortgages for borrowers who make downpayments of as little as 3.5 percent. The FHA insures about $1.1trillion in mortgages and now backs about one third of all newloans used to purchase homes, up from about 5 percent in 2006.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
