<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542690260579">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">20.11.2018 05:04:20 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.c55siiuw3069</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Get a job &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.proguaru.com.br/cvs-pharmacy-prescription-coupon-7684.pdf#hearth&quot;&gt;prescription drugs considered opiates&lt;/a&gt;  Illinois approved a concealed carry law in July, giving control of gun regulations to the state and essentially nullifying Chicago&apos;s power to require that gun owners register their weapons and have a city firearms permit.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://archieandtherug.com/prioritymedicarecom-9392.pdf&quot;&gt;prioritymedicare.com&lt;/a&gt;  France&apos;s CFDT union said it would fight a plan that entailed cuts to about 15,000 posts, although 5,000 new jobs will be created, giving the overall loss of 10,000. Nine hundred jobs would go in France, with the closure or disposal of five sites.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://muktiforum.com/alprostadil-1000-mcg-urethral-supp-b18b.pdf#break&quot;&gt;alprostadil injection youtube&lt;/a&gt;  “Men are more likely to be the main earner in the family and thus more affected by the recession than women. They might experience a greater degree of shame in the face of unemployment and are less likely to seek help,” their report said.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://reflectiveteens.com/astroglide-silicone-walmart-213a.pdf&quot;&gt;astroglide walmart&lt;/a&gt;  &amp;#8220;You know what? None of it (this campaign) will make any difference at all, because there is now a clear majority of Europeans across all member states who are dissatisfied with this Europe and the direction this European union is going in.&amp;#8221;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.weymouthskatepark.co.uk/canadian-pharmacy-tadacip-6ae3.pdf#skill&quot;&gt;tadacip uses&lt;/a&gt;  The retired general&apos;s daughter, Evelyn Matthei, is running as the center-right coalition&apos;s presidential candidate against the victim&apos;s daughter, former President Michelle Bachelet, who represents the center-left bloc.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
