<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542519256130">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 05:34:16 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.71wovyqy5rll</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>What do you do for a living? &lt;a href=&quot;https://leotoys.cl/coastal-medical-associates-south-shore-hospital-2206.pdf&quot;&gt;coastal medical associates ridgeland sc&lt;/a&gt;  Activists may also be hoping that their acts of sabotage can halt the fur industry&apos;s recent rapid growth. Thanks to surging demand from Russia and China&apos;s fast-growing middle class, a single mink pelt now sells for a record $100, up from $41 just five years ago. With demand booming, what was once a backyard business has been transformed into a $350 million industry.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.haroldwhitefuneraldirectors.co.uk/viprosta-uk-bd82.pdf&quot;&gt;viprosta uk&lt;/a&gt;  &amp;ldquo;But they must be sensitively located; with excellent environmental standards and high quality design that enhances local character. Poorly designed developments sprawling into the countryside are no answer.&amp;rdquo;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.md-interiors.co.uk/rogaine-schaum-preis-a6a4.pdf#less&quot;&gt;rogaine 5 precio colombia&lt;/a&gt;  Harley Shaiken, a labor expert at University of California at Berkeley, said the union also hoped to make up for years of stagnant wages during the economic downturn. Meanwhile, BART officials were seeking to conserve resources to update outdated parts of the transit system, he said.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://virtual-operations.com/green-relief-92e2.pdf&quot;&gt;green relief seattle wa&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;Employment growth remained modest in September. Several Districts reported that contacts were cautious to expand payrolls, citing uncertainty surrounding the implementation of the Affordable Care Act and fiscal policy more generally.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://reflectiveteens.com/escitalopram-rezeptfrei-kaufen-213a.pdf#quantity&quot;&gt;prijs citalopram actavis&lt;/a&gt;  Rehtaeh was taken off life-support in April after she attempted suicide in her home. Her family says she was tormented for months after a digital photo of her allegedly being sexually assaulted in November 2011 was passed around her school.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
