<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542513947702">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 04:05:47 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1il5g14njatqo</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I wanted to live abroad &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cabanadolago.com.br/index.php/vicerex-espa-ab8a.pdf&quot;&gt;vicerex en mexico&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;Even though there was limited interest, the quality of the(winning) group speaks for itself and leaves me wanting fornothing better,&quot; Chambriard said at a news conference. She saidthe next auction for Brazil&apos;s big subsalt region was notexpected for at least another two years.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.klevermedia.co.uk/farmaciacanboadacom-31f1.pdf&quot;&gt;farmaciasdecanarias.com&lt;/a&gt;  The Postal Service paid about $40 million to be the title sponsor of Armstrong&apos;s teams from 1998 to 2004 - about $18 million of which went to Armstrong, according to the government&apos;s complaint, which asked for triple damages that are determined at trial.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://lemcasesorias.com/index.php/fjminnovativehealthcom-83f5.pdf#stretched&quot;&gt;canadiandrugsco.com&lt;/a&gt;  The UN Security Council has imposed four rounds of sanctions on Iran for failing to heed six successive ultimatums to suspend uranium enrichment, which Western governments suspect conceals a covert drive for a weapons capability.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://zoeydeutch.net/tukitukimedicalconz-8f08.pdf&quot;&gt;truehealthnaturals.com&lt;/a&gt;  Coleman says her 14-year-old daughter was given alcohol in January 2012 and raped by a 17-year-old acquaintance. The girl&apos;s 13-year-old friend says she was forced to have sex with a 15-year-old at the same house, while another 17-year-old allegedly recorded the incident on a cellphone.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dollingstownfc.com/does-solumedrol-increase-heart-rate-6865.pdf#dime&quot;&gt;medrol withdrawal side effects&lt;/a&gt;  Third Point settled a bitter proxy battle with Yahoo last year after months of criticising the company. Loeb was instrumental in selecting former Google Inc executive Marissa Mayer to join Yahoo as CEO.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
