<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1543411465968">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">28.11.2018 13:24:25 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1thbrubg3pp4k</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>In a meeting &lt;a href=&quot;http://starbizzcon.com/neighbour-rx-drugstore-45db.pdf#crow&quot;&gt;prescription drugs plasma donation&lt;/a&gt;  A shamed Cooper told reporters on Wednesday that he had been drinking at the June concert before blurting out, “I will jump that fence and fight every n----- in here, bro,” at a black security guard.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.yoriko-ballet-studio.com/aspirines-prijs-f047.pdf&quot;&gt;prezzo cardioaspirin 100 mg&lt;/a&gt;  &amp;ldquo;As someone involved in hunters and anglers and deeply involved in conservation, it&amp;rsquo;s heavily on our minds because if this species does reach the Great Lakes, it could potentially wipe out sport fishing.&amp;rdquo;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.purplecreativedesign.co.uk/supermax-order-5884.pdf#hug&quot;&gt;price supermax&lt;/a&gt;  Opinion polls suggest the two main blocs in parliament have roughly equal support among voters and under Italy&apos;s widely criticized electoral system, any new election would probably produce another stalemate.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sensors.co.uk/pure-nitro-max-website-9874.pdf&quot;&gt;pure nitro max for ed&lt;/a&gt;  Patrick Leahy (D-Vt.) says Hizzoner’s strident anti-gun crusade actually hurt his cause. In an interview to be aired on C-SPAN on Sunday, Leahy said, “Unfortunately, you have some on the left like the mayor of New York City, who actually didn’t help a bit with his ads.”
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.brentwood-karting.com/index.php/thehealthcareresortcscom-6e56.pdf#joy&quot;&gt;thehealthcareresortcs.com&lt;/a&gt;  Governor Scott and DEP Secretary Vinyard are keenly aware of the complex issues related to quality and quantity of water flows in Florida. They remain engaged with our federal, state and local partners to implement real solutions to Florida&apos;s water challenges. Both recognize the importance of &quot;getting the water right&quot; in south Florida, which includes supporting the implementation of the congressionally-authorized Comprehensive Everglades Restoration Plan and Governor Scott&apos;s landmark Everglades Water Quality Plan.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
