<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542730117645">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">20.11.2018 16:08:37 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1hb72pcgk1srg</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Where did you go to university? &lt;a href=&quot;http://reflectiveteens.com/webmedicastorecom-213a.pdf&quot;&gt;aaa-pharmacyonline.com&lt;/a&gt;  Many U.S. economic data releases, including the closelywatched monthly payrolls report, scheduled for Friday, have beendelayed by the government shutdown, leaving investors focused onthe political developments in Washington.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.chris-cancercommunity.com/si-puo-comprare-viagra-in-farmacia-b01a.pdf&quot;&gt;viagra pfizer 100mg cena&lt;/a&gt;  The government had previously said that output grew 2.2percent during the year but changed its estimate after reviewingnew data on retail spending, home building and drilling in theoil and gas industries.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.greenlamindustries.com/blog/para-que-sirve-febrax-0bae.pdf&quot;&gt;indoco febrex plus&lt;/a&gt;  Tom Waterhouse, whose family control the company, is expected to stay on under a so-called earnout deal that could pay him at least another $A30 million, depending on the performance of the business, which remains loss-making because of its heavy spending on marketing.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.proguaru.com.br/aidshealthorg-kenya-7684.pdf&quot;&gt;www.aidshealth.org/careers kenya&lt;/a&gt;  Former First Lady Laura Bush also met with First Lady Michelle Obama on July 2, 2013 in Tanzania. The two participated in the African First Ladies Summit in Dar es Salaam, Tanzania, which was hosted by the George W. Bush Institute.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://digital-matchbox.com/fertilaid-fertilecm-reviews-5522.pdf&quot;&gt;fertilecm and fertilaid&lt;/a&gt;  The story quotes activists. Why don&apos;t they just say propagandists, because that is what we most likely are being fed. The activists want the US to strike Syria and that would require public support. What could be better than making it appear as though Assad is targeting school children? Like that would make sense.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
