<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542596641347">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 03:04:01 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.ik8vu33qr75r</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I&apos;d like to cancel this standing order &lt;a href=&quot;http://sjofartsbygningen.no/sinclair-pharma-usa-7ef0.pdf&quot;&gt;sinclair pharmacy tech&lt;/a&gt;  The app is designed to work with Windows 8.1&apos;s side-by-side snap view of multiple running apps. Its Start screen tile shows updates (with the Friend&apos;s profile picture), and the lock screen can show notifications, as can the lock screen.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lovemycase.com/febrex-plus-syrup-f2c2.pdf#spotless&quot;&gt;febrex a.s&lt;/a&gt;  Norwegian Air&apos;s formal request on Saturday for Boeing to take charge of fixing the plane throws a spotlight on an often overlooked facet of the 787&apos;s performance: reliability. And it shows how quickly a plane that cannot fly can hit a carrier&apos;s bottom line.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://digital-matchbox.com/aleve-bodybuilding-5522.pdf#fatal&quot;&gt;aleve bodybuilding&lt;/a&gt;  Apple recently hired Paul Denever, the outgoing chief executive of fashion house Yves Saint Laurent. His brief on &amp;lsquo;special projects&amp;rsquo;, reporting directly to Mr Cook, is thought to include watches.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://sjofartsbygningen.no/cloridrato-de-tamsulosin-0-4mg-generico-7ef0.pdf#statement&quot;&gt;flomax generic costco&lt;/a&gt;  Ryan said a better running game might have alleviated some of the pressure on the quarterbacks — the Jets managed just 2.3 yards per carry — but the line may not have been without blame for the poor running game as well.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.chris-cancercommunity.com/bluepearl-veterinary-partners-oklahoma-city-b01a.pdf&quot;&gt;bluepearl veterinary partners southfield mi&lt;/a&gt;  As China has become more unequal, they say that guanxi has become a way for the rich and powerful to keep the benefits locked within their class. In this view, &amp;ldquo;guanxi&amp;rdquo; is little more than a euphemism for crony capitalism.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
