<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542499092412">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">17.11.2018 23:58:12 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.vht2u2k6xfy6</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I&apos;d like to send this to  &lt;a href=&quot;https://laser-eye-surgery-reviews.org/estee-edit-bronzer-6a83.pdf&quot;&gt;estee edit bronzer review&lt;/a&gt;  Despite getting the cemetery&apos;s prior approval of the headstone&apos;s design — a smiling SpongeBob in an Army uniform, with Walker&apos;s name and rank — her family said Monday that cemetery staff called them the day after it was installed to say it would have to come down.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://freelifesinsurancequotes.com/45-mg-buspirone-6f97.pdf#formidable&quot;&gt;buspar 15 mg dosage&lt;/a&gt;  Unlike their U.S. counterparts, officials setting up major championship venues over here have generally avoided lengthening the courses in response to balls that fly farther and better-conditioned athletes, relying instead on pot bunkers, thick gorse and dicey weather to protect them. That attitude was best summed up by John Philp, the former greenskeeper at Carnoustie, who delighted watching the best golfers in the world squirm.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://muv.asia/order-albendazole-bf28.pdf&quot;&gt;order albendazole&lt;/a&gt;  Geoffrey Robinson, MP for Coventry North West, described Daniel Pelka&amp;#039;s death as &quot;a great disgrace&quot; for the city and called on the council&amp;#039;s chief executive, Martin Reeves, to consider his position.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://reflectiveteens.com/nunawading-pharmacy-213a.pdf&quot;&gt;nunawading pharmacy&lt;/a&gt;  Left Behind Games Inc Chief Executive and ChiefFinancial Officer Troy Lyndon issued nearly 2 billion shares tohis friend Ronald Zaucha, purportedly as compensation forconsulting services, the Securities and Exchange Commission&apos;scomplaint alleges.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ecorporationbd.com/tolterodine-tartrate-drugscom-aaa8.pdf#fragment&quot;&gt;tolterodine tartrate drugs.com&lt;/a&gt;  Warships from several countries, including the U.S., China, India, Italy and the United Kingdom are involved in the anti-piracy operation. Analysts say anti-piracy measures -- such as using private security firms -- are currently poorly regulated.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
