<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542595638782">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 02:47:18 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1xin00ir1f0g1</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Accountant supermarket manager &lt;a href=&quot;http://theglobalelite.org/medicalmedsonlineshopcom-69bc.pdf&quot;&gt;flyingdoctor.org.au&lt;/a&gt;  At the show’s start, Cyrus said she wouldn&apos;t apologize for that buzz-making performance, though she did promise to refrain from twerking. &quot;Now that white people are doing it,” she said, “it&apos;s kinda lame.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.chris-cancercommunity.com/kor-shots-black-magic-b01a.pdf#explosion&quot;&gt;kor shots potent c&lt;/a&gt;  Her party has rebuffed calls from leading Free Democrats for Merkel supporters to back them, saying it has no votes to spare. Polls show the coalition in a dead heat with a combination of Steinbrueck&apos;s Social Democrats, their Green allies and the hard-line Left Party — but the two center-left parties have ruled out an alliance with the latter.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://theglobalelite.org/medicalinsurancefortraveltk-69bc.pdf&quot;&gt;chestnutpharmacy.com&lt;/a&gt;  “I think ‘cavalier with the rules’ allows for those with a dubious opinion of the BMW video,” Chamblee said. “My teacher in the fourth grade did not have a dubious opinion of how I complete the test. But she was writing to one, and as I was writing to many, I felt it important to allow for the doubt some might have, so I chose my words accordingly.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dollingstownfc.com/lov-rub-with-aloe-vera-6865.pdf#debts&quot;&gt;lov rub with aloe vera&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;Honestly, it doesn&apos;t matter who you are or what you are doing, if the NSA wants to find information, they will,&quot; said organizer Joshua Smith. &quot;But we don&apos;t have to make it easy for them.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://archieandtherug.com/euromotion-medicalcom-9392.pdf&quot;&gt;www.gshealth.lk&lt;/a&gt;  My question was this: Why hasn&amp;#8217;t the press attempted to sway public opinion with their power to influence (another good thing; I appreciate it every day) for a public outcry against The Patriot Act? Were they not aware? Of course they were. Did they just think it wouldn&amp;#8217;t affect them since they have the 1st Amendment on their side (which they should)? And is the author&amp;#8217;s point not taken? Rosen was a moron (my words, not the author&amp;#8217;s).
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
