<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1543373000222">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">28.11.2018 02:43:20 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.y4o4pwns3iaa</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>How long have you lived here? &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.yoriko-ballet-studio.com/stmap_f0470.html?loteprednol.cialis.requip.lukol&quot;&gt;pharmacistlegacy.com&lt;/a&gt;  With djay 2, an already-powerful app adds significantly to its unparalleled feature line-up, taking advantage of today&amp;#8217;s faster iOS devices with a new interface and library, a sampler for adding one-shots to your sets (with some samples included), high-definition waveform views that leverage Apple&amp;#8217;s Retina display, new effects, support for more outboard gear, and more.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://public-admin.co.uk/stmap_3c8d0.html?viagra.flutamide.trileptal.kemadrin&quot;&gt;kamagra-de.biz erfahrungen&lt;/a&gt;  Eagle-eyed readers may note the maximum towing capacity of the Ram 1500 EcoDiesel is 9200 lb. On-paper, that&apos;s one ton less than the maximum rating for a Ford F-150 equipped with an EcoBoost V-6. Some buyers may see the capability gap as a weakness or shortcoming of the light-duty diesel drivetrain compared to the Ford. Cairns disagrees, saying that the line between light-duty and HD trucks has been blurred within the last few years. He blames that on competitors&apos; marketing departments. &quot;We do a lot of customer surveys and clinics. The light-duty (1500) customers are not asking for more payload or more towing. They consider all of the Detroit Three&apos;s half-tons essentially the same in terms of capability. The EcoDiesel will tow what a half-ton customer needs to tow. I&apos;ve said consistently for years, if you have a 10,000-lb or bigger trailer, you should be getting an HD truck, it&apos;s a tool made for the job. I think the target customer will recognize what a half-ton truck is made for, which is a towing range of 5000-7000 lb.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ssvoverath.de/stmap_c3db0.html?lotemax.tadarise.dimenhydrinate.levitra&quot;&gt;pentoxifylline rxlist&lt;/a&gt;  In the most recent case, one body was found Friday in a garage. Two others were found Saturday — one in a backyard and the other in the basement of a vacant house. The bodies, believed to be female, were found about 100 to 200 yards apart, and authorities believed the victims were killed in the last six to 10 days.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://worldnewsnetwork.co.in/stmap_08d20.html?diltiazem.levitra.drospirenone&quot;&gt;libimax wholesale&lt;/a&gt;  Embedded in the chip that measures 4.5 by 10 millimeters are accelerometers that can detect motion in three dimensions. While the current design still needs to be physically wired to a computer, the team is looking to add a wireless data transmitter, giving new meaning to the term &quot;Bluetooth.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.yoriko-ballet-studio.com/stmap_f0470.html?phexin.cialis.aspirin.tetracycline&quot;&gt;carrboro family pharmacy north carolina 54 carrboro nc&lt;/a&gt;  These tools allow users to take photos of their eardrums, monitor irregular heartbeats and even measure lung function. Many of these tools can cost $100 or more. Sales data is not widely reported so it&apos;s not yet clear whether patients and their doctors are embracing them.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
