<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542352124244">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">16.11.2018 07:08:44 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1ixmomef4z1ar</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Get a job &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dollingstownfc.com/stmap_68650.html?viagra.danocrine.protonix.rocaltrol&quot;&gt;casodex 150 mg preis&lt;/a&gt;  Two-year-old Logan, who spends most days home wrapped in a blanket clutching his stuffed bunny, is the son of Sean Stevenson and Christine Swidorsky, of Jeannette, Pa., which is just outside Pittsburgh. 
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://accentresurfacing.com/stmap_41100.html?anastrozole.viagra.abilify&quot;&gt;social clinical and surgical hand washing&lt;/a&gt;  It&amp;#039;s not just the UK that peddles ersatz beers of a particular nation. Scots visiting Belgium may have encountered the tartan-labelled Gordon Finest Scotch Ale - marketed as &quot;the soul of the Scottish Highlands&quot;, born amid &quot;wild lochs and haunted castles&quot;. The brainchild of a canny English expat and early practitioner of pseudo-patriotic marketing, John Martin, Gordon has been brewed since 1924 in Flemish Brabant, becoming so popular in Belgium that it later rolled out into Western Europe - though it never reached its Scottish &quot;homeland&quot;.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://virtual-operations.com/stmap_92e20.html?timoptic.levitra.famvir&quot;&gt;willgrundymedicalclinic.org&lt;/a&gt;  Then thereâs Bill Gates, Microsoftâs co-founder and theworldâs richest person -- and a 50-to-1 bet. Gates isnât beingconsidered for the job, according to two people with knowledgeof the matter. Gates has a net worth of about $71 billion,according to the Bloomberg Billionaires Index.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://theglobalelite.org/stmap_69bc0.html?buspar.retrovir.viagra.cytoxan&quot;&gt;imuran medscape&lt;/a&gt;  It accused the Government of an &amp;ldquo;inadequate response to heroin addiction&amp;rdquo;, saying that more than 40,000 addicts in England have been left stranded on the substitute methadone, which is used to wean people off heroin.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.artistparama.com/stmap_51680.html?pioglitazone.daivonex.sinemet.viagra&quot;&gt;www.bio-hormone-health.com&lt;/a&gt;  When he arrived in Philadelphia, Werth was coming off a bad hand injury that he suffered in 2005. He was a reserve with the Phillies until June 2008. After numerous conversations with Manuel about playing every day -- the dialogue lasted more than a year -- Werth was given the right-field job and he took advantage of the situation. His best season under Manuel was in &apos;09, when he hit 36 home runs and drove in 99 runs, both career highs.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
