<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542579535143">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 22:18:55 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1jey3ne5z2c98</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Do you know each other?  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mcmpovos.com/keystone-pharmacy-services-llc-62bd.pdf#dictum&quot;&gt;keystone pharmacy easton pa&lt;/a&gt;  Many on the right see Sarkozy as the only person who can reunite a party that fractured into two feuding camps, one with a hardline stance on immigration and the other more moderate, after his May 2012 defeat to Socialist Francois Hollande.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://virtual-operations.com/botanic-pharmacy-klang-92e2.pdf#line&quot;&gt;botanic pharmacy klang&lt;/a&gt;  The ad-sales trend in Italy and Spain last month wasslightly better than in the first half, Milan-based Mediasetsaid in a statement yesterday. The company, which competes withRupert Murdoch’s pay-TV provider Sky Italia, predicted it willreach its target ahead of schedule in a three-year plan to 2014to cut 450 million euros ($595 million) of costs, creating “afurther significant improvement” in cash generation this year.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://virtual-operations.com/dr-ho39s-perfectback-rest-with-air-comfort-cushion-92e2.pdf&quot;&gt;perfectback rest&lt;/a&gt;  The dominant CDU/CSU would also get more ministries and moreof its policy aims into a coalition agreement with the smallerGreens party than it would in coalition with the SPD, which hasthree times as many parliamentary seats as the Greens.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://paradiseinmexico.com.mx/gourmedgr-c13c.pdf&quot;&gt;allensdrugsindia.com&lt;/a&gt;  However, analysts said it would take a long time for Chinato clean up excess capacity in the labour intensive shippingindustry as any large-scale closures would hurt employment andcould threaten social stability.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.artistparama.com/online-intimate-response-5168.pdf#ominous&quot;&gt;intimate response&lt;/a&gt;  The Yankees are still within striking distance, but the wild-card race figures to be a tight one the rest of the way. If they miss out by one game, plenty of people will point to Rivera’s blown save Thursday and the bullpen’s implosion Friday as the two games that sank the season.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
