<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1543415546709">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">28.11.2018 14:32:26 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.bltbcnb2feyo</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Yes, I play the guitar &lt;a href=&quot;http://public-admin.co.uk/antihypertensive-effectiveness-of-low-dose-lisinopril-hydrochlorothiazide-combination-3c8d.pdf&quot;&gt;antihypertensive effectiveness of low-dose lisinopril-hydrochlorothiazide combination&lt;/a&gt;  Sweet!, located in the Waterford Lakes Town Center, has added a pumpkin-flavored cupcake “slathered with [an] infamous cream cheese icing and finished with a ginger snap crust” to its list of almost 30 cupcakes.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://pixelbedlam.co.uk/healthconsultcomau-65ef.pdf&quot;&gt;pharmacyboard.state.wy.us&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;I am here for the blood of the people who died. We didn&apos;t have a revolution to go back to a police and military state again and to be killed by the state.&quot; — Tawfik Dessouki, a Muslim Brotherhood supporter, after at least 82 more people were killed in violence in Cairo.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sensors.co.uk/male-enhancement-pills-sold-at-walgreens-9874.pdf#lining&quot;&gt;male enhancement pills last longer&lt;/a&gt;  &amp;ldquo;I have no idea. I am currently trying to find out how and why that happened,&amp;rdquo; John Schofield, public affairs officer for the U.S. Naval Academy, said when asked about the errant tweet. &amp;ldquo;It was not from me. The content from the original tweet is not factually correct.&amp;rdquo;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.purplecreativedesign.co.uk/hemogenin-da-resultado-em-quanto-tempo-5884.pdf#decoration&quot;&gt;oximetolona (hemogenin anadrol)&lt;/a&gt;  Several elected officials are hoping that LICH will stay open for at least another year, which will give time to seven different organizations who&apos;ve expressed interest in keeping this medical facility running to put together their proposals.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://starbizzcon.com/healthylivingmayoclinicorg-45db.pdf&quot;&gt;healthyliving.mayoclinic.org/plan&lt;/a&gt;  Promoters of tourism say the islands have plenty for visitors to see. But hurdles include ignorance about the country, the difficulties of getting there, and what some say is an exaggerated fear of malaria.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
