<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542670700680">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 23:38:20 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.gukwz6n4qxex</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I&apos;d like to tell you about a change of address &lt;a href=&quot;http://archieandtherug.com/buy-bupropion-online-australia-9392.pdf&quot;&gt;zyban prescription australia&lt;/a&gt;  There is no model religion that is kept in some secret vault that religious scholars, leaders or everyday believers can access in order to compare it against some religious text, belief or practice. Religion is big and messy, complicated by histories and who gets to tell them, texts whose interpreted meaning spirals far out of the control of the original authors, and practices whose purposes often go unquestioned by those who “just” pray this way or that way and always have.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://globalelite.tv/xtrasize-se-b1c8.pdf&quot;&gt;xtrasize male enhancement&lt;/a&gt;  Sean Parsons, Communications Manager, said, “On behalf of the whole Navitus Bay team, I would like to extend my congratulations to Anna and her team. Having spoken to her before the swim, I know how much she wanted to complete this final leg of the Five Island Swim Challenge and she has done so with flying colours. It is an amazing achievement and a testament to her determination and hard work.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mcmpovos.com/rogaine-effectiveness-receding-hairline-62bd.pdf&quot;&gt;will rogaine make my beard grow faster&lt;/a&gt;  The approval comes after a protracted battle between Dell and prominent investor Carl Icahn, who made his own bid for the company. Icahn withdrew his offer earlier this week, though he said that he did not agree with Dell&amp;rsquo;s plan for the company.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cabanadolago.com.br/index.php/costco-pharmacy-discount-card-ab8a.pdf&quot;&gt;costco pharmacy discount card&lt;/a&gt;  Four of five Democrats didn’t cast a vote, signaling that the very real magnetism of de Blasio’s stance as champion of the working and middle classes stood in contrast to the lack of enthusiasm shown by voters throughout the campaign.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.anupamdebashisroy.com/pentoxifylline-goodrx-f2ef.pdf#dandy&quot;&gt;pentoxifylline goodrx&lt;/a&gt;  &amp;#8220;A few of us did build and test a feature like this internally. Our conclusion after testing it: people are way more interested in seeing *who* liked their posts, rather than just the number of people who saw it. In fact, in all of the thousands of pieces of feedback we receive about News Feed each month, virtually no one has asked to see this information. If we saw enough people asking for this, we would definitely consider building it into the product. But, from what we&amp;#8217;ve seen, including the raw numbers isn&amp;#8217;t worth the space it would take up on the screen.&amp;#8221;
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
