<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542712576525">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">20.11.2018 11:16:16 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1uwrwcswriqth</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I&apos;m retired &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tarokasongbad.com/medical-hospitalbedcom-e3c4.pdf#discharge&quot;&gt;bayfront.healthnewsforme.com&lt;/a&gt;  SIOUX FALLS, S.D. (AP) - Western South Dakota ranchers are reeling from the loss of tens of thousands of cattle in last weekend&apos;s blizzard, and many will dispose of carcasses in pits set to open Monday.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.elegantandwild.co.uk/unify-water-filter-75b3.pdf&quot;&gt;unify water day&lt;/a&gt;  No wonder, critics say, that the current account deficit has blown out to a record 4.8 percent of gross domestic product, or about $88 billion, in an economy whose growth has slowed to a decade low of 5 percent and where consumer inflation is nearly 10 percent.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://leotoys.cl/online-pharmacy-tindamax-2206.pdf#effort&quot;&gt;costco pharmacy prices suboxone&lt;/a&gt;  A Met police spokesman said: “At approximately 19.10 today (Sunday, 13 October) four men were arrested on suspicion of the commission, preparation or instigation of acts of terrorism under the Terrorism Act 2000 (Section 41- 1B).
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://laser-eye-surgery-reviews.org/supplementcentralcom-coupon-codes-6a83.pdf&quot;&gt;supplementcentral.com coupon codes&lt;/a&gt;  Prudential had opposed regulators&apos; attempts to give it the systemic tag and argued that it was not too big to fail. The insurer now has 30 days to determine whether it will ask a court to overturn the regulators&apos; decision.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dollingstownfc.com/virectin-stores-australia-6865.pdf&quot;&gt;virectin stores australia&lt;/a&gt;  &amp;ldquo;Investor confidence returned in July as the Fed confirmed that it would continue purchasing $85bn a month of bonds,&quot; he said. &quot;The Fed gave a broad outline of how QE tapering will proceed, reassuring investors that tapering was dependent on continued economic growth.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
