<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542597288645">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 03:14:48 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1cdu6q2kbbe79</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Hold the line, please &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.chris-cancercommunity.com/wwwpmppharmacystatemnus-b01a.pdf#art&quot;&gt;pmp.pharmacy.state.mn.us&lt;/a&gt;  With Swiss attitudes on automatic exchanges of information softening, more clients than expected are also choosing to pass account details direct to their tax authorities, rather than making the punitive payment to remain anonymous.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://accentresurfacing.com/bimatoprost-rxlist-4110.pdf&quot;&gt;bimatoprost rxlist&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;Members of both families are delighted with the news,&quot; the statement continues. &quot;This baby will be the first child for Mike and Zara and the third grandchild for The Princess Royal.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.proguaru.com.br/diflucan-1-dose-yeast-infection-7684.pdf#meet&quot;&gt;what is fluconazole 100mg tablets used for&lt;/a&gt;  There is no doubt that the last few months will have been the most difficult as the NSA - which was so secret people used to joke that its initials stood for &quot;no such agency&quot; - has been thrust into an uncomfortable spotlight by the leaks by Mr Snowden.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://paradiseinmexico.com.mx/essentia-health-fargo-north-dakota-c13c.pdf#stiffen&quot;&gt;essentia health fargo nd my health&lt;/a&gt;  The city&amp;#039;s water supplies could be affected if the blaze reaches Hetch Hetchy reservoir, which supplies San Francisco with 85% of its water. The fire is burning some four miles away from the reservoir which serves some 2.6 million customers.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://digital-matchbox.com/stanol-50-efectos-secundarios-5522.pdf&quot;&gt;stanol 50 precio&lt;/a&gt;  Paul was shoved in the back by Brandon Carr and missed Harris as he began his return, but the officials did not acknowledge it. Harris got two clean blocks further upfield and squirted free to daylight and went untouched the rest of the way. The 86-yard return marked the fifth longest in Cowboys history and the first punt return surrendered for a touchdown this season by the Redskins.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
