<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542698307262">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">20.11.2018 07:18:27 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.18cr36n88lvn7</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I can&apos;t stand football &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.greenlamindustries.com/blog/chirocarehealthca-0bae.pdf#arduous&quot;&gt;simcoehealth.ca&lt;/a&gt;  As for the rest, they were nowhere, with McLaren&apos;s Sergio Perez next up, but a staggering 2.212secs behind Hamilton, closely followed by Toro Rosso&apos;s Jean-Eric Vergne and Esteban Gutierrez in his Sauber.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lovemycase.com/prescription-drugs-statistics-canada-f2c2.pdf&quot;&gt;street price of drugs 2011&lt;/a&gt;  Israeli archaeologists have discovered a 2,700-year-old seal that bears the inscription &quot;Bethlehem,&quot; the Israel Antiquities Authority announced Wednesday, in what experts believe to be the oldest artifact with the name of Jesus&apos; traditional birthplace.&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2012/05/23/ancient-bethlehem-seal_n_1538605.html&quot; target=&quot;_hplink&quot;&gt;Ancient Bethlehem Seal Unearthed In Jerusalem&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2012/05/23/dig-proves-bethlehem_n_1538665.html&quot; target=&quot;_hplink&quot;&gt;Archaeologists Discover Evidence That Bethlehem Existed Centuries Before Jesus&lt;/a&gt;
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://digital-matchbox.com/tug-valley-arh-pharmacy-5522.pdf&quot;&gt;tug valley arh pharmacy hours&lt;/a&gt;  Opponents dispute those findings, warning that the measure would stifle the local economy. They describe the ordinance, whose wage mandates could be waived by collective bargaining agreements, as an attempt by organized labor to refight a battle it lost in the past decade as many airport jobs went from union positions to so-called at-will contracts, which do not offer job security.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://kssgrp.com/how-effective-is-duloxetine-for-migraines-5457.pdf#helping&quot;&gt;cymbalta generic release date&lt;/a&gt;  Austrian Vice Chancellor Michael Spindelegger (L) of the People&apos;s Party (OeVP) and Chancellor Werner Faymann of the Social Democratic Party (SPOe) address the media after a cabinet meeting following parliamentary elections in Vienna October 15, 2013.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lucky-websolutions.com/how-long-should-you-take-tetracycline-for-acne-0a7b.pdf#trusted&quot;&gt;tetracycline acne reviews&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;Do not mistake this momentary episode in American politics as anything more than a moment of politics,&quot; U.S. Secretary of State John Kerry told reporters at an Asia-Pacific leaders conference in Bali, Indonesia, on Saturday.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
