<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1543412450211">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">28.11.2018 13:40:50 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1herdz9ysy328</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>A book of First Class stamps &lt;a href=&quot;http://teerandaz.com/testofen-hair-loss-131c.pdf&quot;&gt;testofuel for sale&lt;/a&gt;  answer to matthewslyman: I don&amp;#8217;t know and i don&amp;#8217;t care whether they have read the Quran or Proust. I know a Muslim by how they behave, not by their name or what they proclaim, just like I designate a civilized person by how they behave not by their identity or ethnicity. In first world countries as in the third world ones there are 1st, 2nd, and 3rd grade citizens as in good, bad and dreadful. “Beings” gifted with universal consciousness r judged according to what they do with this gift in the eyes of who Made them be, and Muslims are none the less. “Muslim” means, “accepting peacefully”, put in context it is believing in an extraordinary unique God as the maker of any existence, believing that Monotheism is divinely revealed by Him, adoring and following His guidance, “unedited”. The antagonists above in the article are simply opposed to that guidance, so they are as much Muslims as they are Civilized.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://oktandrammen.no/drammen-ny/elyeconomydrugcom-e52c.pdf#bathroom&quot;&gt;rx-quality.net&lt;/a&gt;  LONDON/STOCKHOLM, July 16 (Reuters) - A financial crunch atiron ore miner Northland Resources demonstrates the impact ofmetal price falls on small-scale mine exploration in the Nordicregion and is scaring away already rattled investors.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://oktandrammen.no/drammen-ny/i-pharm-consulting-mnchen-e52c.pdf&quot;&gt;i-pharm consulting&lt;/a&gt;  The original iPad flip cover was perfect in its simplicity as it folded up to create a stand for the iPad to rest on. But, it was so simple that Apple can expand on it and make it an even more attractive accessory - perhaps making it easier to use for commuters sitting down and holding it on their laps.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ssvoverath.de/maxwell-pharma-parwanoo-c3db.pdf#emerged&quot;&gt;maxwell pharmaceuticals pvt ltd&lt;/a&gt;  NEW YORK, Oct 14 (Reuters) - U.S. stocks fell broadly onMonday, focused on events in Washington after weekend talksbetween Republicans and Democrats showed some progress butfailed to remove the risk of a possible U.S. default in threedays, pressuring stocks.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://worldnewsnetwork.co.in/zenegra-100-tablets-08d2.pdf#secret&quot;&gt;how to take zenegra 100&lt;/a&gt;  Fitting indeed is the recognition of the valor of a warrior who rescued his fellows from the line of fire, pausing to kiss a wounded comrade on the forehead before he was helicoptered from the battlefield. Captured on video by a helmet camera worn by the copter’s crew, that moment is one for the ages.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
