<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542662795986">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 21:26:35 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.vodophfxnttt</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I want to report a  &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.wychwoodcabinetmakers.co.uk/paracetamol-500-mg-50-tabletek-cena-e0f9.pdf#whispering&quot;&gt;paracetamol al comp kosten&lt;/a&gt;  I&amp;#8217;m confused. How can there ever be a &amp;#8216;TWO STATE SOLUTION&amp;#8217; when there are in fact THREE STATES (ie West Bank, Israel, and Gaza). Folks, geography is everything. People form governments and ideologies within geographic entities. Remember back when India was partitioned and there were supposedly Two States, ie India and Pakistan, but &amp;#8216;Pakistan&amp;#8217; actually had an East Pakistan and a West Pakistan? Well folks, that didn&amp;#8217;t work. Each geographical entity worked out it&amp;#8217;s own political destiny and the two &amp;#8220;Pakistans&amp;#8221; ended up splitting into two countries &amp;#8211; ie Pakistan and Bangladesh. This should be a lesson. The only way a two state solution can come about in the mid-east is if there were to be a POPULATION EXCHANGE between Gaza nad the Israeli settlements in the West Bank. Then all the Palestinians will be within the contiguous borders of the West Bank and all the Jews will be within the contiguous borders of an Israel which includes Gaza. There is no other way to the mythical, phantasmagorical, &amp;#8216;Two State Solution&amp;#8217;.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://accentresurfacing.com/care-more-pharmacy-4110.pdf&quot;&gt;care more pharmacy&lt;/a&gt;  Indeed, the Mortgage Bankers Association says applications for new mortgages decreased 2.6% for the week ending July 12 and another 1.2% last week, continuing a trend of declining new-loan activity. Refinance activity has dropped to its lowest level since July 2011, according to the MBA.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sarah-hyland.net/atomic-7-ice-cream-bangalore-79a8.pdf&quot;&gt;atomic 7 ice cream bangalore&lt;/a&gt;  Michael Morrison, president and publisher of HarperCollins, said: &quot;It feels not in keeping with Elmore&amp;#039;s &amp;#039;no fuss&amp;#039; persona to try to pay tribute to this great man. But Elmore was a true legend - unpretentious, unbelievably talented and the coolest dude in the room....
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://globalelite.tv/where-to-buy-viagra-in-canada-b1c8.pdf#stupid&quot;&gt;viagra with american express canada&lt;/a&gt;  Members of the &quot;X-Men&quot; cast feature in a plethora of otherfranchises with avid followings at Comic-Con - McKellan with&quot;Lord of the Rings,&quot; Stewart with &quot;Star Trek,&quot; Lawrence with&quot;The Hunger Games,&quot; Anna Paquin with HBO&apos;s &quot;True Blood&quot; TVseries, and Peter Dinklage from HBO&apos;s &quot;Game of Thrones.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://stsmihajlopupin.edu.rs/rs/wellbutrin-75-mg-twice-a-day-3c56.pdf#renewed&quot;&gt;wellbutrin sr patient assistance&lt;/a&gt;  Straumann used to be the proud owner of an Aston Martin DB5 – which was used to promote the James Bond film Thunderball – but sold it last year along with his stake in luxury watchmaker H. Moser &amp; Cie.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
