<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542362891715">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">16.11.2018 10:08:11 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.uwut6b3g81q2</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I&apos;m on holiday &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ipepalmas.com.br/stmap_7fc80.html?glibenclamide.levitra.aripiprazole.diclofenac&quot;&gt;zenegra opinie&lt;/a&gt;  Kevin Siegrist comes in to face Ortiz, a move by Matheny that makes little sense because it is giving Big Papi a look at the Cardinals&apos; top lefthanded reliever in an extremely low-leverage situation. Ortiz lowers the leverage of the situation going forward by hitting the first pitch over the right-field wall to make it 7-0. The Red Sox have thoroughly and mercilessly punished every mistake the Cardinals have made. As it happens, 7-0 is also the score of the last World Series opener to end in a shutout—the Reds over the A&apos;s in 1990, the start of a sweep. Napoli flies out to end the inning.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://zoeydeutch.net/stmap_8f080.html?liv.52.naprelan.cialis&quot;&gt;genezapharmaceuticals.com reviews&lt;/a&gt;  Since then, though, the hashtag has taken on additional tasks, namely (and as Mr. Timberlake and Mr. Fallon illustrate in their lighthearted critique) for bringing one-off ideas to fruition without having to form complete sentences.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://archieandtherug.com/stmap_93920.html?levitra.medroxyprogesterone.keftab&quot;&gt;lithium carbonate drugs.com&lt;/a&gt;  President Barack Obama will press his case for a quickreopening of the entire federal government, coupled with ashort-term increase of U.S. borrowing authority to avoid a U.S.default, when he meets with Senate Republicans on Friday.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ascfinancialadvisers.co.uk/stmap_55530.html?methocarbamol.strattera.levitra&quot;&gt;andersons pharmacy&lt;/a&gt;  Tensions over Snowden are also likely to make it harder for Obama to push forward on negotiations for a new nuclear arms reduction deal with Russia, a proposal he issued in a speech in Berlin in June and which he hopes to make part of his legacy. Russia so far has shown little appetite for the idea.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://lemcasesorias.com/index.php/stmap_83f50.html?differin.viagra.rizatriptan.antabuse&quot;&gt;amitriptyline hcl for pain management&lt;/a&gt;  Acapulco&apos;s misfortune has now become so commonplace that signs dotting the highway out of town read &quot;No hables mal de Aca,&quot; or &quot;don&apos;t speak badly of here,&quot; a play on the Spanish word &quot;aca&quot; (here) and the first three letters of the city&apos;s name.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
