<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1543406118448">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">28.11.2018 11:55:18 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1vnh6o25pfmmv</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I came here to work &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sensors.co.uk/replay-lucienne-skinny-9874.pdf#fantastic&quot;&gt;replay lucienne skinny&lt;/a&gt;  How can I put this politely. Fuck those guys and they&amp;#8217;re deliberately opaque billing practices and your welcome for the tax-payer bailout while charging everyone mafia interest rates. I had a dispute with them a few years back. Long story short I didn&amp;#8217;t pay, they terminated my platinum account, I kept $350 a year for not having the privilege of letting them make money on my charges. They tacked on a truck load of fees onto the &amp;#8216;sign and travel&amp;#8217; account I kept with them. I balked and told them to cough up the agreement that authorized them to add a dime beyond the balance. I wanted specific language tied in any way to my signature. Their guys sent over what amounted to a blatantly bogus document which they legally tried to pass off as the original agreement &amp;#8212; what any layperson would call a forgery. And don&amp;#8217;t get me started on the harassing phone calls from their collections goons making one false statement after another, they sounded like a bunch of out of work lawyers from barely credible law schools. It went to court, (the amount was less than the minimum necessary to take it to the bigger civil court) so without a lawyer I had their case dismissed as it was plainly obvious they a) mismanaged their old records, b) couldn&amp;#8217;t find my original agreement and c) fabricated legal documents. During a mediation later on they were brow-beaten into accepting repayment without the nearly 30% in added fees or any accrued interest. I only wanted them to report the &amp;#8216;sign and travel&amp;#8217; as &amp;#8216;paid in full&amp;#8217;. When I followed up to make sure they had done so, it was an epic waste of time, one phone after another, they couldn&amp;#8217;t even locate the records because they were shit-canning one subcontracted lawyer after another. 9 in 10 people I spoke with at the actual company had no idea what the hell I was talking about. It was a revealing show of incompetence coupled with shady actions from what I thought to be the top shelf brand in the credit card industry. I keep one credit card now in case I never need to rent a car. Debit card all the way. I see what goes in and what goes out in real time. Put it this way, when I first heard about the industry foaming out of the mouth because people were going towards debit card in tectonic type movements, I had a feeling I was picking the best option.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://tynerblain.com/blog/seriser-viagra-shop-ef2c.pdf&quot;&gt;viagra pharmacie belge&lt;/a&gt;  The whole package from Elysium costs just $1,990. That seems miniscule compared to how much it costs to send a living person into space. &amp;#8220;Space burials&amp;#8221; have been offered for a few years now, but Elysium seems to be the most affordable game in town.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.greenlam.com/index.php/sensoria-fitness-socks-reviews-7741.pdf#treatment&quot;&gt;sensoria fitness socks bundle&lt;/a&gt;  She said she hadn&apos;t communicated with their dad in three months and found it sad when Jean called police last week after she and a group of her dad&apos;s friends, relatives and co-workers showed up at the mansion&apos;s gate toting large cardboard signs.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://starbizzcon.com/skinbodyhealthclickbooknet-45db.pdf&quot;&gt;familydoctorreviews.com&lt;/a&gt;  State and local authorities are increasingly desperate to stop their advance. Trapping and shooting are the primary means of eliminating wild pigs, but researchers are also trying to develop poisons and birth control to control the population.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bombeirodf.com.br/test-prop-tren-ace-dbol-cycle-50f8.pdf&quot;&gt;gp test prop 100 review&lt;/a&gt;  The figure of 5,748, based on tallies of missing persons from around the country, was the first official estimate following weeks in which the numbers of dead and missing fluctuated wildly from a few hundred to several thousand.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
