<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542722979853">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">20.11.2018 14:09:39 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.izb1cwa0nr6f</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>How many would you like? &lt;a href=&quot;http://globalelite.tv/doctorsonlineco-b1c8.pdf&quot;&gt;doctorsonline.co.in&lt;/a&gt;  Kilusang Magbubukid ng Pilipinas (KMP) described the uprooting as a “legitimate resistance by farmers against Golden Rice.&amp;#8221; &amp;#8220;The people’s health and food safety should be of paramount importance,” KMP deputy secretary general Willy Marbella who joined the protest action said.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.artistparama.com/wwwmedizinhhude-5168.pdf#alignment&quot;&gt;www.medizin.hhu.de/berufungsverfahren&lt;/a&gt;  (NEWTOWN, Conn.) — Activists from the Connecticut town where 26 people were gunned down in a mass shooting at an elementary school in December headed to Washington on Tuesday to lobby again for gun control, a trip that took on new urgency in the wake of the massacre in the capital that killed 13, including the gunman.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.infocalcbba.edu.bo/fairness-cream-yahoo-answers-9e88.pdf&quot;&gt;wow fairness cream yahoo&lt;/a&gt;  He had emailed me in the afternoon, it transpired, to say: &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ll be at my work, text me when you get down this way, and I&amp;rsquo;ll come down.&amp;rdquo; Not receiving any such communication, he assumed I was late or in transit. Eventually he went down to the pub to check, but by then I had gone. It was for him beyond the realms of plausibility that I hadn&amp;rsquo;t received any of the emails, texts or calls.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.haroldwhitefuneraldirectors.co.uk/can-diflucan-cure-uti-bd82.pdf#hermione&quot;&gt;diflucan for systemic yeast infection&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;We offered to hear from Canadians on this issue and they have already spoken loud and clear. They overwhelmingly do not want to open the issue,&quot; Dimitri Soudas, a spokesman for Mr Harper, said at the time.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://contactconsultoria.com/index.php/buy-muscle-rev-xtreme-australia-a511.pdf&quot;&gt;muscle rev xtreme&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;Usually the district provides $100 to $150 for supplies. Some years it is less, some years it might be a little more,&quot; Pitts said. &quot;But for the most part that buys folders, pencils, crayons, basics. It doesn&apos;t go as far as the creative mind of a teacher would go.&quot;
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
