<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1543403678311">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">28.11.2018 11:14:38 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1wksffjlk9hm0</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Canada&gt;Canada &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.brentwood-karting.com/index.php/prosolution-pills-6e56.pdf#pain&quot;&gt;prosolution pills&lt;/a&gt;  It said two batches of milk powder had been removed from shops last month after Sri Lanka&apos;s Ministry of Health had said they tested positive for DCD, a nitrate inhibitor used in fertilizers. Sri Lanka also imposed a ban on advertising by Fonterra&apos;s Anchor powder brand.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.aicpuglia.it/portalendymedcom-2397.pdf&quot;&gt;lewiscountyhealthdept.org&lt;/a&gt;  In a posting, he wrote, &quot;I&apos;m going to prison or death sentence for killing my wife. Love you guys, Miss you guys .... My wife was punching me, and I am not going to stand any more with the abuse so I did what I did. I hope u understand me.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.greenlam.com/index.php/healpharmacycom-reviews-7741.pdf#powerful&quot;&gt;healpharmacy.com reviews&lt;/a&gt;  This is no joke, and the Court of Appeals took the matter very, very seriously. It had to, because the court opened the door to just this kind of insane argument by torturing what had been a readily understandable, common sense homicide statute into a dictate for mind-reading exercises.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ssvoverath.de/foundation-medicine-precision-enrollment-c3db.pdf&quot;&gt;foundation medicine&lt;/a&gt;  The landlord shouldn&apos;t withhold money for normal wear and tear, but if you damage the unit, you may be on the hook for repairs. What&apos;s the difference between normal wear and tear and actual damage? &quot;If you have little kids and they&apos;re rubbing their hands on the wall, that&apos;s normal wear and tear,&quot; Deegan says. &quot;If they&apos;re punching holes in the wall, that&apos;s a different story.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.greenlam.com/index.php/party-pillsbiz-7741.pdf&quot;&gt;admin.medicalinteractive.com&lt;/a&gt;  While a number of lawmakers on both sides of the politicalaisles said on Sunday talks shows that they do not expect agovernment shutdown, Democratic House Leader Nancy Pelosi saidshe believes a lot of conservative Republicans want one.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
