<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542708155314">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">20.11.2018 10:02:35 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.175ztg9gxrxm0</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I&apos;d like some euros &lt;a href=&quot;http://theglobalelite.org/ft-belvoir-pharmacy-annex-hours-69bc.pdf&quot;&gt;ft belvoir pharmacy annex hours&lt;/a&gt;  Elkington&amp;rsquo;s original Tweet, posted on Friday evening, was soon deleted. However, a second Tweet appeared on his Twitter account on Saturday morning, claiming that &amp;ldquo;a couple of caddies got rolled by some Pakis...&amp;rdquo; That post was also removed soon afterwards.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.klevermedia.co.uk/true-vision-healthcom-31f1.pdf&quot;&gt;www.ucihealth.com/my healthcare&lt;/a&gt;  France&apos;s government summoned the U.S. ambassador over the report and U.S. President Barack Obama discussed the allegations with Hollande by phone. Obama acknowledged &quot;legitimate questions for our friends and allies about how these capabilities are employed&quot;.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.chris-cancercommunity.com/calcitriol-yahoo-b01a.pdf#neighbourhood&quot;&gt;calcitriol yahoo&lt;/a&gt;  Shares of the largest candle maker in the U.S. continued itsrally on Monday after a SeekingAlpha report said the company&apos;sstock could make a &quot;parabolic&quot; move higher in the very nearfuture. The stock rose 17 percent on Friday.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.haroldwhitefuneraldirectors.co.uk/erecaid-ez-ring-bd82.pdf&quot;&gt;osbon erecaid manual esteem system&lt;/a&gt;  Italy and India are separately investigating charges thatAgustaWestland paid bribes to win the 2010 deal for the AW101helicopters. India froze payments to the company in February asthe scandal unfolded.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://contactconsultoria.com/index.php/betamethasone-valerate-cream-usp-1-a511.pdf#gay&quot;&gt;betamethasone valerate uses&lt;/a&gt;  “The lesson for everyone is simple: Introducing alcohol into any situation can affect not only your life, but the lives of your friends and family,” Williams said. “Nathan’s friends need to remember him before they think of consuming alcohol.”
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
