<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542709567954">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">20.11.2018 10:26:07 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.8aw7fuuda0mw</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I&apos;d like a phonecard, please &lt;a href=&quot;http://lemcasesorias.com/index.php/the-green-pharmacy-by-james-a-duke-phd-83f5.pdf&quot;&gt;the green pharmacy by james a duke phd&lt;/a&gt;  NEW YORK, Aug 12 (Reuters) - It was just another hot Augustafternoon for New York electricity grid chief Rick Gonzales, ashe sat in the control room helping to make sure the state&apos;s 8million homes had enough power to keep the lights on and the airconditioning running.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://zoeydeutch.net/aldenmedicalsupplycom-8f08.pdf&quot;&gt;aldenmedicalsupply.com&lt;/a&gt;  While acknowledging the Daily Mail - which has a circulation of more than 1.8 million - was a &quot;popular&quot; newspaper, he suggested many of its readers agreed with him that it had &quot;overstepped the mark&quot;.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.techdesighn.com/abditincom-b26f.pdf#fitting&quot;&gt;canadapharmacy247.com&lt;/a&gt;  The amount of bearish, or short, positions in 10-yearTreasury futures held by speculators exceeded bullish - or long- positions by 66,432 contracts on Aug. 13, according to theCFTC&apos;s latest Commitments of Traders data.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tarokasongbad.com/virgin-butea-superba-u00f6l-e3c4.pdf&quot;&gt;butea superba male enhancement&lt;/a&gt;  European aristocratic glamour was provided by Prince Girolamo Strozzi, his wife Irina and their two daughters. They are close friends of the Blairs, who have enjoyed free holidays at the Strozzis&amp;rsquo; 16th century Tuscan palace.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cabanadolago.com.br/index.php/glucophage-xr-pharmacy2us-ab8a.pdf&quot;&gt;glucophage xr pharmacy2us&lt;/a&gt;  The poll, taken before weekly inventory reports from theAmerican Petroleum Institute (API) on Tuesday and the U.S.Department of Energy&apos;s Energy Information Administration (EIA)on Wednesday, forecast that crude stocks fell 2.4 millionbarrels on average in the week ended July 19. (Editing by Jason Neely)
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
