<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542366969504">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">16.11.2018 11:16:09 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.d7gde71tqyj4</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Gloomy tales &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.haroldwhitefuneraldirectors.co.uk/stmap_bd820.html?chlorpromazine.tadadel.lithium.viagra&quot;&gt;fox family pharmacy hardin il&lt;/a&gt;  But the future, NASA felt, was in reusable spacecraft. All previous US spacecraft had been single-shot affairs, but in order to make access to space truly affordable, NASA envisioned their next craft as fully reusable end-to-end. It would launch like a rocket, ferry people or cargo to space, land like a plane, be refitted, and launch again days later. NASA initially wanted this Space Transport System, or STS, to fly dozens of times in any given month. Space flight would become safe, cheap, and routine.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cabanadolago.com.br/index.php/stmap_ab8a0.html?renagel.adefovir.azathioprine.viagra&quot;&gt;best drugs used for anxiety&lt;/a&gt;  Japan&apos;s finance minister also pressed the United States on Tuesday to quickly resolve the deadlock while the International Monetary Fund&apos;s chief economist said a U.S. default could lead to a recession &quot;or even worse&quot;.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.haroldwhitefuneraldirectors.co.uk/stmap_bd820.html?viagra.aralen.ditropan&quot;&gt;does filagra 50 work&lt;/a&gt;  Bernanke has kept silent about his future plans, but he is widely expected to depart when his current term as Fed chairman expires on January 31. Nor has he pushed back against perceptions that he is ready to return to private life.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://zoeydeutch.net/stmap_8f080.html?delgra.levitra.atenolol.ansaid&quot;&gt;amoxicillin trihydrate ca used for&lt;/a&gt;  The GPS system is still less accurate than dropsondes but GPS is cheaper, lower weight, and needs less power. It could even be installed on a drone. Scientists plan to use both the GPS and dropsondes together to get a better picture of these storms.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dollingstownfc.com/stmap_68650.html?emsam.tenoretic.malegra-dxt.levitra&quot;&gt;medwoche.de&lt;/a&gt;  The man, dressed in a thin brown uniform a little bit too big for him, is not threatening us for coming too close, but pleading. Repeatedly, two fingers go to his lips - the global sign language for &quot;have you got a smoke?&quot;
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
