<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542622136030">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 10:08:56 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.j3mcsnffa02g</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I came here to work &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.anupamdebashisroy.com/cerebra-ultra-f2ef.pdf&quot;&gt;cerebra ultra&lt;/a&gt;  Balmain&amp;#39;s SS/14 and Resort collections were working on a theme - lots of denim, quilting and 1980s styling with many looks featuring this large chain belt. A big accessory like this is a brilliant contrast to such a feminine and pretty dress. It&amp;#39;s like wearing a pair of chunky biker boots with a floaty floral number - it just works.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://stsmihajlopupin.edu.rs/rs/rite-aid-pharmacies-number-of-stores-are-there-3c56.pdf&quot;&gt;rite aid pharmacies near my location&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;I&apos;m a little upset,&quot; said Grayson, who earned the job over sophomore Conner Smith and freshman Nick Stevens. &quot;I think things would be different if I would&apos;ve gone out there and executed differently. I&apos;m going to take the blame for it. I&apos;m willing to do that for the team.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://leotoys.cl/wwwdrhauschka-meddevortragsabend-2206.pdf&quot;&gt;natur-pharm.ge&lt;/a&gt;  Geist: Before he gets to the &quot;Today&quot; set every morning, Geist is holding court with the political classes,  co-hosting MSNBC&apos;s &quot;Morning Joe,&quot; a Washington D.C. obsession. Known as &quot;The Oracle of MSNBC,&quot; Geist clearly gets the ins and out of politics, but can he appeal to those outside the Beltway?
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.haroldwhitefuneraldirectors.co.uk/all-generic-medscom-forum-bd82.pdf#tramp&quot;&gt;all-generic-meds.com&lt;/a&gt;  Glencore, which is due to report full half-year earningsnext week, gave no update on its closely-watched tradingdivision, but met market expectations with higher volumes in notonly copper, but also coal and agricultural products.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sarah-hyland.net/seaford-clinic-fax-number-79a8.pdf&quot;&gt;seaford clinic&lt;/a&gt;  A group of British scientists at Scotland&apos;s Rural College in Edinburgh were awarded the Probability Prize for scientifically proving that the longer a cow has been lying down, the more likely it is to stand up, and for the related discovery that once a cow has stood up it is extremely difficult to say how much time will pass before it lies down again.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
