<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542671163331">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 23:46:03 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1h05xwk6xpxbc</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I&apos;d like to pay this cheque in, please &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.casadeadoracao.com.br/index.php/mypharmassist-uk-bac9.pdf&quot;&gt;pharmassist ltd&lt;/a&gt;  Her colleague Matt Lauer, who was largely — and, many say, unfairly — blamed for Curry’s unceremonious ouster, said working alongside Guthrie has helped him get through one of the toughest stretches of his career.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.proguaru.com.br/hair-loss-rogaine-foam-7684.pdf#link&quot;&gt;where to purchase rogaine foam&lt;/a&gt;  BART managers want employees to pay 5 percent of their paytoward pensions, to which workers currently do not contribute.The move by BART is in line with trends across the nation, with public-sector employees being required to pay more towardpension and other benefits.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.haroldwhitefuneraldirectors.co.uk/how-to-use-cytotec-misoprostol-200-mcg-bd82.pdf&quot;&gt;how to use cytotec for abortion at home&lt;/a&gt;  But they added that if an IPO has not been completed following the release of financial statements for the 2017 financial year, the new investors would have the option to sell their shares back to the Danish State on pre-agreed terms. It gave no further detail on the sell-back clause.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.infocalcbba.edu.bo/lamotrigine-missed-dose-side-effects-9e88.pdf&quot;&gt;lamictal abrupt withdrawal&lt;/a&gt;  The MiPhone 3 measures in at just 8.1mm thick, and includes a 3,050mAh battery as well as 2GB of RAM and either 16GB or 32GB of onboard storage. It sports a 13-megapixel rear-facing camera from Sony with an &quot;intelligent beauty corrector&quot; feature that can estimate age and gender, in addition to a 2-megapixel front-facing shooter. As for price, the 16GB variant will retail for 1,999 yuan ($327) while the 32GB flavor will cost 2,499 yuan ($408).
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://lemcasesorias.com/index.php/ketoconazole-avec-ou-sans-ordonnance-83f5.pdf&quot;&gt;ketoconazole avec ou sans ordonnance&lt;/a&gt;  Rio de Janeiro means &amp;ldquo;January River&amp;rdquo;. It was named by mistake: there&amp;rsquo;s no river there. The explorer Gaspar de Lemos set sail from Portugal in 1501 and arrived at a huge bay in Brazil the following January. Thinking the bay was the mouth of a river he named it after the month.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
