<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542731527423">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">20.11.2018 16:32:07 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1atjreqpuvltw</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>No, I&apos;m not particularly sporty &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dollingstownfc.com/kortext-app-download-mac-6865.pdf&quot;&gt;kortext&lt;/a&gt;  THE HAGUE, Netherlands (AP) — The chief of the world&apos;s chemical weapons watchdog says the organization has to visit more than 20 sites in Syria as part of the unprecedented international mission to destroy the country&apos;s poison gas arsenal, including some where it may be necessary to negotiate cease-fires before they can gain access.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://theglobalelite.org/harmful-facts-about-prescription-drugs-69bc.pdf&quot;&gt;price chopper pharmacy waldo&lt;/a&gt;  Perhaps only Puig could flip his bat high in the air, then stand at the plate and admire what he thought was a sure home run to right field — and still recover in time to fly around the bases and go in standing at third with a triple, throwing a pump-fist to the sky.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.wychwoodcabinetmakers.co.uk/pharmeden-free-delivery-code-e0f9.pdf#herd&quot;&gt;discount code pharmeden&lt;/a&gt;  At a two-day rate review that ended earlier on Thursday, the BOJ kept monetary policy steady and held off on revising up its assessment of the economy, preferring to wait for more clues on whether increasingly positive data will encourage companies to ramp up spending.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.infocalcbba.edu.bo/247worldstorecom-9e88.pdf#pick&quot;&gt;firstdrugsrx.com&lt;/a&gt;  Dr. Lawrence Levitan, flanked by police detectives, walks into into Manhattan Supreme Court on Wednesday to face allegations that he stole hundreds of thousands of dollars from Beth Israel Medical Center.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://archieandtherug.com/buy-cialis-thailand-9392.pdf#points&quot;&gt;canadian cialis reviews&lt;/a&gt;  The company also plans to set the minimum level of dividendpayments at 35 percent of its net profit starting from 2013.Currently, it returns at least 10 percent of net profit toshareholders under Russian accounting standards.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
