<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542705423565">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">20.11.2018 09:17:03 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1v9lbi52uwiho</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I&apos;d like to send this to  &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dollingstownfc.com/matrixmedicalnetworkcom-6865.pdf&quot;&gt;matrixmedicalnetwork.com&lt;/a&gt;  The Zamboanga fighting has also cast doubts on the government&apos;s efforts to bring an end to 40 years of Muslim rebellion that has killed 120,000 people, displaced 2 million and created a cycle of humanitarian crisis. About 750,000 people were displaced in 2008 by conflict in another part of Mindanao.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.anupamdebashisroy.com/sustinex-pdf-f2ef.pdf#converted&quot;&gt;sustinex 30 price in india&lt;/a&gt;  The arrival of a female chief signals a change for a school that has seen its share of sexual scandals, most recently the dismissal of cadet Jamil Cooks after his April conviction on a charge of abusive sexual conduct after he pleaded guilty to the unlawful entry into the rooms of two female cadets.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.elegantandwild.co.uk/mailmypharmacycommy-75b3.pdf&quot;&gt;mypharmacy.com&lt;/a&gt;  The dollar was flat at 79.767 against a basket ofcurrencies, not far from the previous session&apos;s trough of79.627, its lowest since early February. The dollar was on trackfor its fourth consecutive week of losses.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.artistparama.com/kool-grill-ebay-au-5168.pdf#authors&quot;&gt;kool grill ebay au&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;Two weeks of therapy will not end decades of bad behavior,&quot; City Councilmember Kevin Faulconer said in a statement. &quot;Bob Filner should leave to receive the help he obviously needs, but he shouldn&apos;t take the office of the mayor and San Diego city government with him. He needs to resign and seek long-term treatment as a private citizen.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mikasafloors.com/precio-plavix-en-venezuela-bdec.pdf&quot;&gt;prix plavix&lt;/a&gt;  The rate of economic change hasn&amp;#039;t been matched by political reform, with the Communist Party - the world&amp;#039;s largest political party - retaining its monopoly on power and maintaining strict control over the people. The authorities still crack down on any signs of opposition and send outspoken dissidents to labour camps.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
