<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542369116388">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">16.11.2018 11:51:56 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.15mce21qr1b76</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Your cash is being counted &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tarokasongbad.com/stmap_e3c40.html?levitra.revatio.omeprazole.lamprene&quot;&gt;donde puedo comprar viagra sin receta en tijuana&lt;/a&gt;  NOTES: As part of Rivera&apos;s farewell, the Texas Rangers honored him before the game with a donation of $5,000 to the Mariano Rivera Foundation. ... The Yankees announced that Alex Rodriguez (quad injury) was examined by a team doctor Thursday and he would not be in the lineup Friday. ... Texas&apos; Adrian Beltre extended his league-best 18-game streak in which he has not struck out.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://virtual-operations.com/stmap_92e20.html?vrikshamla.dapoxetine.cialis&quot;&gt;dunbar medical hurricane&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;When BloomReach detects that the intent and behavior on a single merchant&apos;s web and mobile sites are significantly similar, the system observes and correlates the anonymous users to determine if its the same person,&quot; according to Joelle Kaufman, BloomReach director of marketing. &quot;Once the engine is reasonably confident, the BloomReach Mobile application will begin to incorporate behavior from the website into the mobile experience through &apos;Just for You&apos; dynamic categories and even the priority of search suggestions.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://leotoys.cl/stmap_22060.html?pfiagara.cialis.levodopa.seromycin&quot;&gt;astellas pharma careers singapore&lt;/a&gt;    The ship, which has a flight deck that is nearly 820 feet long, is designed to carry up to 14 helicopters. Japanese officials say it will be used in national defense -- particularly in anti-submarine warfare and border-area surveillance missions -- and to bolster the nation&apos;s ability to transport personnel and supplies in response to large-scale natural disasters, like the devastating earthquake and tsunami in 2011.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.anupamdebashisroy.com/stmap_f2ef0.html?methylcobalamin.cafergot.levitra.femcare&quot;&gt;dan fitzgerald pharmacy whitefish bay wi&lt;/a&gt;  Carrying 129 pounds as the high weight in the one-mile contest, Wise Dan was spotting his rivals anywhere from 11 to 14 pounds, including King Kreesa, who was carrying 117 pounds under jockey Irad Ortiz Jr.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dollingstownfc.com/stmap_68650.html?nifedipine.abacavir.viagra&quot;&gt;preco pariet 20mg&lt;/a&gt;  He&apos;s reformed now and a big screen super hero, but here Robert Downey Jr. is shown Nov. 25, 2000, after his arrest at the Merv Griffin Resort in Palm Springs, Calif., on Saturday for drug possession.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
