<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542607388598">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 06:03:08 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.8qja0pr14fa4</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I went to  &lt;a href=&quot;http://lemcasesorias.com/index.php/medsonline-365com-83f5.pdf&quot;&gt;globalcosmed.de&lt;/a&gt;  Of course, the Red Sox were still trailing by a run when Peavy left the game. With no Green Monster to take aim at, the Red Sox manufactured a good old-fashioned rally in the seventh against lefty Jake McGee.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.casadeadoracao.com.br/index.php/womenshealthmagnltablet-bac9.pdf&quot;&gt;womenshealthmag.nl/bodyenfit&lt;/a&gt;  Co-heading their list, Jürgen Trittin said he isn&amp;#8217;t worried: &amp;#8220;It&amp;#8217;s normal, in all the Greens&amp;#8217; campaigns, for 20 years it&amp;#8217;s been this way. Things start out high, then go down, but in the end they come back up again.&amp;#8221;
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lovemycase.com/biologic-infusion-pharmacy-cypress-f2c2.pdf&quot;&gt;biologic infusion pharmacy&lt;/a&gt;  Looking at the camera app, there actually aren&amp;#8217;t too many changes between the stock Android camera and HTC&amp;#8217;s version. In either camera app, you&amp;#8217;ll see that both interfaces use the entire screen as the viewfinder with button overlays.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://muv.asia/wwwconsettmedicalcentrecouk-bf28.pdf&quot;&gt;www.consettmedicalcentre.co.uk&lt;/a&gt;  Lao Airlines is the national carrier of the communist state and has operated since 1976. Its aircraft carried 658,000 passengers last year and it has a fleet of just 14 planes, mostly propeller-driven.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://reflectiveteens.com/pharmworkscom-213a.pdf#communicated&quot;&gt;medix.hr.urlabc.fr&lt;/a&gt;  The trust turned to Strata’s resource matching software to address the issue. It helps staff find the most appropriate, available source of care for a patient − in real time. “We set matching criteria − which type of care was best for which type of patient − and put in place e-referral for all the community beds across Buckinghamshire,” explains Mr Schick. “This allowed a better balance between step-up and step-down.”
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
