<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542640855898">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 15:20:55 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1e3aktykcyve2</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I&apos;m a housewife &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ecorporationbd.com/mediquote-south-africa-aaa8.pdf&quot;&gt;mediquote telephone number&lt;/a&gt;  On Thursday, Mr Obama thanked congressional leaders for their help ending the government shutdown and raising the debt limit, but said both had &quot;inflicted completely unnecessary damage on our economy&quot;.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.md-interiors.co.uk/buy-paxil-cr-a6a4.pdf#escape&quot;&gt;paroxetine 30 mg picture&lt;/a&gt;  The aerospace and defense company said there could be delaysin its jetliner deliveries, including its new 787 Dreamliner,because thousands of U.S. aviation officials needed to certifythe planes have been idled. The delays would also affectnumerous programs and products in the company&apos;s defensebusiness.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.infocalcbba.edu.bo/spedra-avanafil-prix-9e88.pdf&quot;&gt;avanafil donde comprarlo en colombia&lt;/a&gt;  1. I realize it&amp;#8217;s summertime, and maybe standards are relaxed, but, Mark Potter is identified as the editor of this copy. Couldn&amp;#8217;t he have edited this text more carefully? Couldn&amp;#8217;t the opening sentence have been been stated more clearly?! I assume the purpose was to say Steinbrück accused Merkel &amp;#8220;of covering up *UNTIL the looming election* the likelihood that German taxpayers will have to fund further euro zone bailouts,&amp;#8221; NOT that &amp;#8220;German taxpayers will have to fund further euro zone bailouts *DUE TO a looming election*&amp;#8221;… The funding of the future bailouts doesn&amp;#8217;t result from the &amp;#8220;looming election&amp;#8221;! It&amp;#8217;s not necessitated by the &amp;#8220;looming election&amp;#8221;! He&amp;#8217;s accusing Merkel of concealing the need to fund the bailouts, and he&amp;#8217;s saying that her motive for the concealment is to hide this information from German voters until after the election. Aren&amp;#8217;t print journalists professional writers and shouldn&amp;#8217;t they strive for clarity? Aren&amp;#8217;t editors expected to compensate for inevitable &amp;#8220;goofs&amp;#8221;?
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.artistparama.com/cialis-tadalafil-prezzo-5168.pdf&quot;&gt;acquistare il cialis on line&lt;/a&gt;  Once this common ground was established, officials got to work. Mr Zarif used a PowerPoint presentation on his black Lenovo laptop to outline a plan to end the conflict over Iran&amp;#039;s nuclear ambitions.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mikasafloors.com/wwwdariosilvasurgery-blog-bdec.pdf&quot;&gt;www.dariosilva.surgery blog&lt;/a&gt;  Without progress in the nuclear dispute, Israel hasthreatened to bomb the Iranian nuclear installations, andinternational negotiators are keen avoid any military actionthat could inflame the region.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
