<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1543371332573">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">28.11.2018 02:15:32 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.ga8rci83rag</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I&apos;m not interested in football &lt;a href=&quot;https://worldnewsnetwork.co.in/stmap_08d20.html?lamotrigine.ipratropium.viagra&quot;&gt;ostarine mk-2866 cycle&lt;/a&gt;  Under its proposal, investors who have held stock in theissuer or 60 days or more would qualify to be included inprivate placements, but their investments would be capped atC$10,000 ($9,800) per company per year.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bombeirodf.com.br/stmap_50f80.html?ziac.viagra.amoxicillin.escitalopram&quot;&gt;body brew bod systems&lt;/a&gt;  An all-female jury found Zimmerman not guilty of fatally shooting unarmed teenager Trayvon Martin, after 15 hours of deliberation following a 13-day trial. The case became a public cause celebre, involving race and the rights of individuals to defend themselves against perceived danger.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://tynerblain.com/blog/stmap_ef2c0.html?retin-a.levitra.nizoral&quot;&gt;ims physiotherapy toronto&lt;/a&gt;  Dr Mark Porter, head of the British Medical Association, said publishing the data was an &quot;important step&quot; towards improving transparency across the NHS, informing and empowering patients and identifying under-performing hospitals.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://teerandaz.com/stmap_131c0.html?amoxil.bupron.tizanidine.viagra&quot;&gt;metoprolol hexal 95 mg&lt;/a&gt;  Real gross domestic purchases -- purchases by U.S.residents of goods and services wherever produced -- increased2.4 percent in the second quarter, compared with an increase of1.4 percent in the first.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://teerandaz.com/stmap_131c0.html?levitra.dulcolax.vepesid&quot;&gt;metoprolol hexal 95 mg&lt;/a&gt;  Over 230 people have been killed in violence linked to BokoHaram in the last six weeks, according to a Reuters count - oneof the bloodiest periods since Jonathan declared a state ofemergency and launched a military crackdown in threenortheastern states in May.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
