<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542735143248">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">20.11.2018 17:32:23 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.5zlerfi76rkm</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Do you know the number for ? &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.klevermedia.co.uk/imodium-rxlist-31f1.pdf#chisel&quot;&gt;imodium rxlist&lt;/a&gt;  Some have paid the ultimate price. The news earlier this week of the two young girls who met their deaths in the River Wear has been a terrifying reminder of the very real dangers of swimming in open water without real knowledge of the conditions and the experience of doing so.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mcmpovos.com/does-amoxicillin-help-treat-strep-throat-62bd.pdf#probably&quot;&gt;amoxicillin rx 65401&lt;/a&gt;  Under current laws and policies, Social Security spending will rise slowly but steadily in the next two decades but then stabilize. CBPP projects that if lawmakers stick with current laws and policies, spending as a percent of GDP for all other programs besides Social Security and the major health programs will be half its 2010 level by 2040. 
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://accentresurfacing.com/ihealthtreecom-coupon-4110.pdf&quot;&gt;ihealthtree.com health store&lt;/a&gt;  The person most responsible for Jackson&amp;#8217;s death is Michael Jackson himself. He was a 50 year old adult and took prescription drugs by choice. Jackson doctor shopped to get the drugs he wanted and paid those doctors huge sums of money to insure those doctors did his bidding. The jury made the right decision.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.layeredonline.com/collins-pharmacy-abbeyfeale-dd54.pdf#medical&quot;&gt;collins pharmacy brockton ma&lt;/a&gt;  Democrats charge that Republicans went back on an agreement earlier this year to approve executive branch nominations in an orderly manner. Instead, they say, Republicans have besieged nominees with questionnaires and used their leverage over the administration to make excessive demands on federal agencies.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.md-interiors.co.uk/kwmedicineshoppeca-a6a4.pdf#eating&quot;&gt;med4all.org&lt;/a&gt;  The bottle only traveled a mile or two westward from where it was likely deposited to the location where parks workers found it just before Thanksgiving last year. It was intermingled with broken docks, boating gear and a spectrum of sea trash. Because the note included Sidonie&apos;s New York City phone number, the bottle found its way home to her mother.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
