<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542579577282">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 22:19:37 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.xhbqywqizi2c</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I&apos;m not interested in football &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.elegantandwild.co.uk/pharmjournaleu-75b3.pdf&quot;&gt;kascelmed.ie&lt;/a&gt;  A Cownose Ray swims in a tank during a preview of the newly renovated Suzanne and Walter Scott Aquarium at Henry Doorly Zoo in Omaha, Neb., Wednesday, April 4, 2012.The aquarium opens to the general public on Thursday, April 5. (AP Photo/Nati Harnik)
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lovemycase.com/medafstudiocom-f2c2.pdf#mend&quot;&gt;protonmeds.launchrock.com&lt;/a&gt;  Regardless of the small fortune Anthony has already made, it’s still hard to turn your back on a contract that can pay you $30 million more than any other team can offer under the collective bargaining agreement.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://lemcasesorias.com/index.php/globalmedicinesorg-83f5.pdf&quot;&gt;ukhealthcart.co.uk&lt;/a&gt;  Democrats are also trying to persuade Boehner to convene a &quot;conference committee&quot; with the Senate to discuss broader budget issues, something Boehner has resisted, fearing that Democrats might use arcane House rules to bring other measures to the House floor, such as raising taxes on the wealthy.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://oporajeyo.com/fentanyl-citrate-injection-prescribing-information-bf45.pdf#carter&quot;&gt;fentanyl citrate dosage&lt;/a&gt;  Mefloquine, was first developed in the 1970s at the U.S. Department of Defense&apos;s Walter Reed Army Institute of Research as a synthetic analogue of quinine, the first effective treatment for malaria. It was licensed in 1989 by the FDA for use against chloroquine-resistant malaria.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://stsmihajlopupin.edu.rs/rs/remedioparaemagrecerecobr-3c56.pdf#delivered&quot;&gt;pinnaclehealthgroup.com.au&lt;/a&gt;  Kofi Awoonor, a Ghanaian poet, professor and former ambassador to Brazil, Cuba and the United Nations, died after being wounded in the attack, Ghana&apos;s presidential office confirmed. Ghana&apos;s ministry of information said Awoonor&apos;s son was injured and is responding to treatment.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
