<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542361085406">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">16.11.2018 09:38:05 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.6tlf00gdek79</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I&apos;ve been made redundant &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.proguaru.com.br/stmap_76840.html?levitra.tadarise.neggram&quot;&gt;pharmacyonclick.gr&lt;/a&gt;  When other regional conservative parties joined to form the CDU, the CSU remained separate, reflecting Bavaria&apos;s strong regional identity. CSU lawmakers make up nearly a quarter of Ms Merkel&apos;s conservative bloc.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://sjofartsbygningen.no/stmap_7ef00.html?sustiva.chloroquine.peroxide.cialis&quot;&gt;lasix iv push precautions&lt;/a&gt;  Allemand was subsequently hospitalized and placed on life support. She died Wednesday, with Anderson and her mother by her side. Her body was released to her family Thursday after an autopsy determining the official cause of death.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://kssgrp.com/stmap_54570.html?celebrex.liv.52.levitra&quot;&gt;strattera 25 mg reviews&lt;/a&gt;  “I never voted for him to be my spiritual leader. I voted for him to be my governor of New York state. I respect him because he is a man of his word, a man of integrity, and he gives good governance,” said Washington.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://accentresurfacing.com/stmap_41100.html?sominex.viagra.ovral&quot;&gt;viril x gnc&lt;/a&gt;  The U.S. House of Representatives was set to vote on a dealover the fiscal impasse on Wednesday after the Senate struck alast minute deal to avoid a historic lapse in the government&apos;sborrowing authority. President Barack Obama has said such abreach could lead to default and deliver a damaging blow to theglobal economy.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://laser-eye-surgery-reviews.org/stmap_6a830.html?emsam.viagra.tegretol&quot;&gt;prix imodiumcaps&lt;/a&gt;  There are those who argue that not abridging the right to keep and bear arms should be limited to flintlock smooth bore muskets. But it is an absurd, laughable assertion. Liberty from unreasonable, and unreasoning, State intrusion into our lives is supposedly what millions of Americans have died for. Of course dictatorships have many fewer violent crimes than free countries. But freedom is what we were born to and freedom is what we want. Who cares what some General wants? Do your job, which is to defend our liberty.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
