<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542543896818">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 12:24:56 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1erghlm4opx5r</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I&apos;ve been made redundant &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.proguaru.com.br/atenolol-tab-medscape-7684.pdf&quot;&gt;atenolol overdose medscape&lt;/a&gt;  James Runcie, Head of Literature and the Spoken Word at the Southbank Centre said: &quot;Our scope is deliberately broad and I&amp;rsquo;m particularly looking forward to our poetry extravaganza pegged to the 60th anniversary of our Saison Poetry Library.&amp;rdquo;
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.klevermedia.co.uk/norvasc-other-names-31f1.pdf&quot;&gt;amlodipine 1a pharma 5 mg tabletten n&lt;/a&gt;  Soros Fund Management LLC is holding onto its 7.9 percent stake in Penney, a source familiar with the matter said on Monday. The firm backed by billionaire financier George Soros had reported earlier this year a big stake in the department store operator.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mcmpovos.com/chemopharma-pvt-ltd-62bd.pdf&quot;&gt;chemopharma viden spol.s r.o&lt;/a&gt;  Well of course there is still no shutdown solution. Our government is run by spoiled, temper tantrum throwing, if I don&apos;t get my way, no one will be happy, BRATS. I shouldn&apos;t insult kids that way, because even they know what compromise means.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ascfinancialadvisers.co.uk/pharmacywikiorg-5553.pdf#represent&quot;&gt;medicantnutrients.com&lt;/a&gt;  Brokerage Barclays Capital started its coverage of the oilservices company with an &quot;overweight&quot; rating and target price of$35, citing the benefits from the surging deepwater drillingactivity, a strong balance sheet and high margins.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.haroldwhitefuneraldirectors.co.uk/healtharizonainslineovcom-bd82.pdf&quot;&gt;healtharizona.inslineov.com&lt;/a&gt;  Nearly 150 people in the United States died in 2007 and2008, and hundreds suffered serious reactions, after they weretreated with contaminated heparin, according to the U.S.Pharmacopeial Convention, the body that sets standards for drugquality and purity.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
