<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542621086128">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 09:51:26 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1sgq7j7zz8o8e</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I need to charge up my phone &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mcmpovos.com/nexium-alternatives-natural-62bd.pdf&quot;&gt;nexium alternatives natural&lt;/a&gt;  The outcome of a shareholder vote scheduled for Thursday onthe offer is too close to call. Dell may decide to delay thevote to gain time to win support for the deal, a person familiarwith the matter said earlier on Tuesday.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.layeredonline.com/saw-palmetto-women-reviews-dd54.pdf#shipwreck&quot;&gt;saw palmetto description&lt;/a&gt;  So as the Earth&apos;s climate changes &amp;ndash; as dry areas get drier and wet areas get wetter &amp;ndash; such inland superstorms will only become more likely because of the &quot;brown ocean&quot; effect. And hurricane-watching won&apos;t be confined just to communities along the coast. We&apos;ll all need to pay attention.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.artistparama.com/body-scanning-technology-5168.pdf#stressed&quot;&gt;body scanning machine&lt;/a&gt;  The fullest moon of the month fell on the night of September 18-19, but as NASA points out in this video, the moon is in the midst of a string of days during which it rises at sunset. And when that happens, the horizon-moon illusion combines with the sunset colors to redden it.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://reflectiveteens.com/testoroid-protein-powder-213a.pdf#nervously&quot;&gt;testoroid review protein&lt;/a&gt;  Clarity on control could help the company avoid the fate ofhigh profile mergers such as the Daimler-Chrysler deal of thelate 1990s. This suffered from cultural clashes and a lack ofoverlap in the cars they sold until it was unravelled.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://reflectiveteens.com/viagra-walmart-prices-213a.pdf#doctrine&quot;&gt;viagra walmart prices&lt;/a&gt;  As far as camera gear goes, we’re a Nikon shop here at the university and we just took delivery of a D4 earlier this year. It’s a great camera with speedy autofocus and a beautiful file. We also have a D800 which offers a bigger file but doesn&amp;#8217;t seem to do quite as well with autofocus speed and accuracy, which proved critical for this shoot as some of the animals like to move around. Many are also very small which required macro equipment and the resulting focus tolerances are very narrow, even at the high apertures I was using and again rendering autofocus accuracy critical. For the first animal &amp;#8212; an 8-10” Henkel&amp;#8217;s leaf-tailed gecko (Uroplatus henkeli) &amp;#8212; I was able to use a 70-200mm lens but for all the others I reverted to a 50mm 1.4 coupled with my personal Canon 250D closeup lens. While not ideal for this sort of work, the combination did just fine.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
