<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542702251786">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">20.11.2018 08:24:11 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.5concm4ldw3w</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Would you like a receipt? &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.klevermedia.co.uk/bars-and-branches-discount-code-31f1.pdf&quot;&gt;bars and branches bands&lt;/a&gt;  &amp;ldquo;Fracking&amp;rdquo;, or hydraulic fracturing, involves blasting a slurry of water, chemicals and sand into the shale at high pressure, and was first carried out on a small scale in Kansas in 1947. But its applications were limited to the least challenging geological conditions until Mitchell began experimenting with different fracking mixtures and increasingly powerful blasting equipment. In 2002 he merged his company, Mitchell Energy &amp; Development, with Devon Energy &amp;mdash; which brought expertise in deep-level &amp;ldquo;directional&amp;rdquo; or horizontal drilling and gave much greater access into the heart of the shale.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://archieandtherug.com/are-generic-drugs-safe-to-take-9392.pdf&quot;&gt;medicare prescription drug donut hole&lt;/a&gt;  Case in point: To push his staff at Extended Stay America to take risks, CEO Jim Donald recently started handing out GET OUT OF JAIL FREE cards. The goal? To convince employees that they won&apos;t get in trouble for proposing bold ideas that end up failing.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tarokasongbad.com/himalayanhealthcom-e3c4.pdf#lose&quot;&gt;elementsofhealth.com&lt;/a&gt;  Horta-Osorio has made some significant changes at Lloydsthat have been deemed successful, simplifying the business andslimming down to focus on lending to UK households andbusinesses and meet tougher regulatory requirements on capital.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://lemcasesorias.com/index.php/howes-pharmacy-milford-ct-83f5.pdf&quot;&gt;howes pharmacy goffstown new hampshire&lt;/a&gt;  Business and council leaders are banking on offshore wind farms to create thousands of jobs in the region. But Lord Howell of Guildford, who caused outrage when he told the House of Lords that the “desolate” North East was the perfect place to carry out fracking, has repeatedly urged the Government to cut support for the industry.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cabanadolago.com.br/index.php/testosterone-enanthate-low-dose-ab8a.pdf&quot;&gt;trenbolone enanthate cycle&lt;/a&gt;  Besides the sexual harassment allegations, Filner faces questions over a June trip to Paris that was sponsored by the Organization of Iranian-American Communities. On Wednesday, he said he would reimburse the group for his expenses, claiming it told him incorrectly that it had nonprofit status under Internal Revenue Service rules.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
