<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542654465988">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 19:07:45 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.liaaxa014gb1</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>One moment, please &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.md-interiors.co.uk/reviews-on-indian-god-lotion-a6a4.pdf#toffee&quot;&gt;indian god lotion sale&lt;/a&gt;  For the critics of Obama&apos;s plan, for example, what about the next dictator and the one after that? &quot;If we fail to act, the Assad regime will see no reason to stop using chemical weapons,&quot; Obama said Tuesday night. &quot;As the ban against these weapons erodes, other tyrants will have no reason to think twice about acquiring poison gas, and using&quot; it. And the more conventional these weapons become, the more likely that they could move from states to nonstate actors like al-Qaida. So what happens if the no-chemical-weapons norm is allowed to fade?
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://reflectiveteens.com/merced-medical-pharmacy-213a.pdf&quot;&gt;merced medical pharmacy&lt;/a&gt;  Antonio Leanza, the founder of the London School of Photography, says Instagram has helped democratise photography by opening up the medium to those who traditionally could never have afforded it.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://zoeydeutch.net/blogmedspringcom-8f08.pdf#musical&quot;&gt;wholehealthnaturals.com&lt;/a&gt;  7. Atiyeh Salem Musa, who, along with an accomplice, used an ax to murder a Jewish co-worker, 67-year-old Isaac Rotenberg, during Passover 1994. The murder took place while Rotenberg was hunched on his knees fixing a floor at his place of employment in Petah Tikva. He was struck on the back of his neck, dying two days later.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.md-interiors.co.uk/cghealthnicin-rbsk-a6a4.pdf&quot;&gt;cghealth.nic.in&lt;/a&gt;  But the North&amp;#8217;s statement did not make clear whether it would offer a solid guarantee to not repeat the abrupt withdrawal of workers from the industrial complex—a core demand of the South that had blocked meaningful progress in previous talks.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lovemycase.com/choosing-natural-healthcom-f2c2.pdf#bend&quot;&gt;legacy.rasteroids.com&lt;/a&gt;  The 19-year-old actor is currently under fire for lashing out against &quot;Two and a Half Men,&quot; publicly blasting the series as &quot;filth&quot; and encouraging people to stop watching the popular sitcom. &quot;If you watch &apos;Two and a Half Men,&apos; please stop watching &apos;Two and a Half Men.&apos; I&apos;m on &apos;Two and a Half Men,&apos; and I don&apos;t want to be on it,&quot; said Jones in a videotaped testimonial for the Forerunner Chronicles. The group is linked to the Voice of Prophecy Seventh-Day Adventist church in Los Angeles, where Jones worships. &quot;Please stop watching it and filling your head with filth,&quot; Jones said.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
