<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542552855840">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 14:54:15 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.axvsivu8j22s</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>How long are you planning to stay here? &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.proguaru.com.br/king-fahad-medical-city-career-7684.pdf#swamp&quot;&gt;king fahad medical city career&lt;/a&gt;  Venezuela and Guyana have long argued about the status ofthe disputed Essequibo region, an area on the border about thesize of the U.S. state of Georgia, and over rights to the oceanresources that lie offshore. Venezuela calls it a reclamationzone but in practice it functions as Guyanese territory.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://paradiseinmexico.com.mx/mediflowcom-c13c.pdf&quot;&gt;memorialhealthcare.org&lt;/a&gt;  After a tense skirmish on the Maersk, during which the crew of 20 men took refuge in a locked engine room, Philips was forced to board a 28-foot fiberglass lifeboat with the pirates. Another five days passed, as the destroyer USS Bainbridge waited nearby for an opportunity to free him using psychological and technoloiical warfare tactics.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tarokasongbad.com/inhalehealthbg-e3c4.pdf#distance&quot;&gt;willowcreekhealthmart.com&lt;/a&gt;  In 2011, Greek and Norwegian shipping companies accusedGrand China Logistics, another HNA Group subsidiary, ofwithholding payments on chartered vessels, and in the same yearChina Cosco Holdings temporarily halted charter payments toforce renegotiation of contracts it deemed overpriced.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ascfinancialadvisers.co.uk/treatmenttravellercom-5553.pdf&quot;&gt;umanmedical.com&lt;/a&gt;  &amp;#8220;If there was ever a test of whether the Senate could move forward in a bipartisan way, this afternoon was it,&amp;#8221; said Sen. Amy Klobuchar, a Minnesota Democrat who helped lead the Jones confirmation fight. &amp;#8220;The last thing we want right now is to leave with a radioactive blowup.&amp;#8221;
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://accentresurfacing.com/a1medicalsuppliesflcom-4110.pdf&quot;&gt;medshop-health.net&lt;/a&gt;  Microsoft ranks fourth on Wall Street in terms of actualcash payouts, behind Apple, Exxon Mobil and AT&amp;T Inc. In terms of dividend yield, it ranks fourth among U.S.information technology companies, lagging only Intel Corp, Seagate Technology and Microchip TechnologyInc, according to S&amp;P Dow Jones Indices.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
