<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1543365530323">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">28.11.2018 00:38:50 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1szf8jx85e3h8</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>In a meeting &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.purplecreativedesign.co.uk/stmap_58840.html?doxazosin.levitra.acetazolamide&quot;&gt;indianamedicaid.com&lt;/a&gt;  The sponsor of the jury bill, Democratic Assemblyman Bob Wieckowski, expressed dismay at the veto, likening rules disqualifying permanent residents from jury service to long-discarded laws that kept black people and women from serving.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.brentwood-karting.com/index.php/stmap_6e560.html?viagra.zeagra.tegretol&quot;&gt;600 mg boldenona&lt;/a&gt;  Staff Sgt. Robert Bales, an Ohio native and father of two from Lake Tapps, Wash., pleaded guilty in June to avoid capital punishment for killing the civilians, mostly women and children, on March 11, 2012.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://worldnewsnetwork.co.in/stmap_08d20.html?benazepril.vilagra.omnicef.levitra&quot;&gt;ap-medical.com&lt;/a&gt;  The news came as a House of Representatives subcommittee on cybersecurity held a hearing to discuss the system, called the Hub. Republican lawmakers and panel witnesses raised questions about the ability to secure the system ahead of the Oct 1 launch.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bombeirodf.com.br/stmap_50f80.html?thorazine.primaquine.levitra&quot;&gt;drugs-online.tk&lt;/a&gt;  Brett Gardner worked a walk to open the game, but Darvish got Robinson Cano to ground into a 4-6-3 double play to end the first. The Bombers didn&apos;t have another baserunner until the fifth, when Lyle Overbay blooped a single to left field for the Yankees&apos; first hit of the night.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bombeirodf.com.br/stmap_50f80.html?mebendazole.viagra.mevacor.cabergoline&quot;&gt;pharmfinders address&lt;/a&gt;  Michael Coscia, founder and sole owner of New Jersey-based Panther Energy Trading, was ordered to pay a total of $2.8 in fines and disgorgement of profits by the US Commodity and Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) and banned from trading for a year, while the UK&amp;rsquo;s Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) hit him with a £597,993 fine.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
