<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542570377236">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 19:46:17 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.14oa0yzu8avr0</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Will I have to work on Saturdays? &lt;a href=&quot;https://paradiseinmexico.com.mx/dabruscom-c13c.pdf#nor&quot;&gt;northwestphaemacy.com&lt;/a&gt;  Prince William was the first royal heir to be born in a hospital instead of in the palace. The first sighting of him and Prince Harry was when their parents exited the hospital with the new princes in tow. William and Kate are expected to do the same with their new arrival.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.proguaru.com.br/prontomedsaudecombr-7684.pdf#respond&quot;&gt;protdyn.med.unideb.hu&lt;/a&gt;  The Chief Medical Officer Dame Sally Davies, the Government’s senior health adviser, said the heatwave would have claimed its first victims last week with “many” victims dying within 48 hours of 28C temperatures on Saturday.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dollingstownfc.com/snuggle-me-organic-reviews-6865.pdf#whip&quot;&gt;snuggle me organic coupon code 2017&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;It was a really complicated case,&quot; said Nancy Rapoport, a law professor at the University of Nevada, Las Vegas. &quot;It wasn&apos;t just that it was really big, but it was really big and had some novel issues.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lucky-websolutions.com/amitriptyline-10mg-weight-gain-0a7b.pdf#investigation&quot;&gt;endep 10 for chronic pain&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;The most important element about the character is that he was really lucky,&quot; Wendy Schmidt said, perhaps referring to the point in the story where Falkor is able to rescue his companion from a violent storm without having any idea where to look for him.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://newscvm.com/vendenafarmaciacom-e9bb.pdf#binding&quot;&gt;amicafarmacia.com opinioni&lt;/a&gt;  Keita faces a daunting task to rebuild a broken nation, despite pledges of more than $4 billion in international aid. He must reach a peace deal with northern Tuareg separatist rebels, overhaul the armed forces and tackle widespread corruption.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
