<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1543366053649">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">28.11.2018 00:47:33 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.dr6edu64842t</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Where&apos;s the nearest cash machine? &lt;a href=&quot;http://teerandaz.com/stmap_131c0.html?serophene.malegra.viagra.valtrex&quot;&gt;pillarsanportella.com&lt;/a&gt;  The majority Republicans in the House are expected toconduct a symbolic vote to repeal the law on Friday - the 40thtime the chamber has voted to either repeal or defund the law.The measure will likely die in the Democratic-controlled Senate.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://starbizzcon.com/stmap_45db0.html?naprelan.bentyl.viagra&quot;&gt;walgreens land o lakes pharmacy&lt;/a&gt;  Libertarian philosophy is rooted in mistrust in government power. It fits nicely alongside the founders well-earned dislike of centralized power &amp;#8211; so much distrust that they split powers up so that the government could not do biiiig thiiiings. i.e. this is a feature, not a bug.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.greenlam.com/index.php/stmap_77410.html?valtrex.cialis.loxitane&quot;&gt;zyvoxid 600 mg infusion preis&lt;/a&gt;  Currently, third-party traders are forced to charge the same amount on any other platform as they do on Amazon but independent and rival websites can now undercut it, according to the consumer watchdog.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sensors.co.uk/stmap_98740.html?oxytetracycline.ruagra.viagra&quot;&gt;buy dapoxetine paypal&lt;/a&gt;  While earnings for the second quarter have largely come instronger than expected so far, only a small percentage of S&amp;P500 components have reported to date. This week will see resultsfrom dozens of components, including numerous Dow components.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://pixelbedlam.co.uk/stmap_65ef0.html?salbutamol.volmax.carvedilol.viagra&quot;&gt;topsteroids.me&lt;/a&gt;  Dewhurst, who is running for re-election in 2014, continued to ask what he needed to do to get the relative out of police custody. The sergeant once again explained the procedure and provided him with the number to Collin County, where the relative was going to be transferred.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
