<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542602242272">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 04:37:22 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.2bndnjaaqpmg</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Do you have any exams coming up? &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.haroldwhitefuneraldirectors.co.uk/anabolicsteroidsnl-bd82.pdf#cancel&quot;&gt;anabolicsteroids.nl ervaring&lt;/a&gt;  nomoreamnesty: Ummm, actually I beg to differ. My niece &amp; her moron husband (who works but gets his wages garnished for failure to support 2 sons from 2 other women before he met/married my niece) gets much more per month in food stamps/debit card than $600. She couldn&apos;t even afford the 5 kids she had before she married her current idiot husband, so what did she do? She &amp; her hubby got pregnant &amp; had twins last year. On top of that, the twins were preemies &amp; both in Neonatal ICU for about 4 mo&apos;s. So, several tens of millions of dollars later, she now gets $900. PER MONTH in food stamps/debit card. She lives in the state of NV, not sure if what state or county one lives makes a difference but I&apos;m sure family size does count. So I suppose if she &amp; her idiot hubby decide the taxpayers need to do more, maybe she&apos;ll have baby #8. Her oldest will be 18 yrs old next March &amp; she&apos;s been getting free medical all of her children&apos;s lives. We taxpayers have forked over close to $500 million, no doubt, for all her children from birth to now. ObamaCare won&apos;t change anything for the people who get it free now &amp; have been years &amp; years before ObamaCare. I&apos;m too sick to work &amp; my hubby whom had open heart surgery 1 yr ago and also advanced Osteoarthritis in both hips is the only one working (complete loss of cartilage in his joints). We can&apos;t afford monthly health ins. premiums for me since one sole income is barely enough to pay rent, let alone gas in the car. ObamaCare will end up costing us much more, so we are forced to have my husband add me to his company&apos;s ins. policy. They go by his gross income, not taking into account taxes withdrawn out of his check, etc so we don&apos;t qualify for any kind of voucher to help pay premiums. Damn can&apos;t afford to go to the doc. though as we would get my hubby&apos;s wages garnished just to pay the medical bills. Only way I could afford care, even with ins, is to divorce my hubby &amp; I&apos;ll never do that. F if we do, F if we don&apos;t. I&apos;d also live off the land too, but only if we could afford the land, taxes, etc. Life isn&apos;t always fair, I bitch but it doesn&apos;t help!
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://leotoys.cl/vigrx-uk-reviews-2206.pdf#harsh&quot;&gt;price of vigrx plus&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;We were led to believe there was more support than there was&quot; at the previous institution, said his mother, who found herself having to constantly help Tony from afar. Tony says simply: &quot;It was horrible.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://globalelite.tv/1001pharmaciescom-b1c8.pdf&quot;&gt;1001pharmacies.com avis livraison&lt;/a&gt;  On top of additional airwaves the deal will substantiallyincrease the prepaid base at AT&amp;T. Of its roughly 107 millionwireless customers, only 7 million are prepaid. Leap has 5million prepaid customers.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.greenlamindustries.com/blog/donepezilo-precio-argentina-0bae.pdf#their&quot;&gt;onde comprar donepezil&lt;/a&gt;  Jordan will get each subsequent chunk of cash if the IMFdecides it has sufficiently complied with the conditions of theprogram, which include getting the government&apos;s finances inorder and cutting subsidies for electricity and fuel. An IMFseal of approval can also help mobilize support from otherdonors.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.wychwoodcabinetmakers.co.uk/visiondrugimpexcom-e0f9.pdf#energy&quot;&gt;tmtpharmacy.com&lt;/a&gt;  While June data met expectations for a $27.1 billion tradesurplus, imports dipped 0.7 percent, versus an expected 8percent growth, while exports dropped 3.1 percent, far below aprojection for 4 percent growth.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
