<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542366562274">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">16.11.2018 11:09:22 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.3rw5m1i8v2wt</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Which team do you support? &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lucky-websolutions.com/stmap_0a7b0.html?didronel.triphala.cialis&quot;&gt;ihc sunset clinic st george ut&lt;/a&gt;  But her assassination in a gun and bomb attack during the rally in Rawalpindi sparked massive protests and her Pakistan People&amp;#039;s Party won a resounding victory in the polls allowing her widower, Asif Ali Zardari, to take up the presidency.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://archieandtherug.com/stmap_93920.html?atenolol.levitra.xylocaine.fincar&quot;&gt;halo top ice cream price walmart&lt;/a&gt;  This Gold Coast estate has been a party house for nearly 100 years: first as the scene of Gatsby-style gatherings hosted by industrialist Otto Kahn; now as a lavish wedding location. But it’s also home to 32 guest accommodations, most romantic of which is the Carnegie Suite. Smack in the center of the French chateau-inspired structure, in the imposing fourth-floor turret, it boasts a bedroom straight out of Cinderella—the four-poster sits beneath a peaked ceiling smothered in lavish draping.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://muktiforum.com/stmap_b18b0.html?levitra.lovegra.maxaquin.vepesid&quot;&gt;buy topiramate australia&lt;/a&gt;  Dog-friendly rooms at the Sacher cost a mere 35 euros ($46) on top of the 400 to 5,000 euros that the hotel charges per night for its rooms and suites, the best of which overlook the neighboring Vienna Opera.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.layeredonline.com/stmap_dd540.html?aggrenox.levitra.acticin&quot;&gt;advantagemedicalservices.net&lt;/a&gt;  LHP David Huff will make his first career appearance against the Astros as the Yankees conclude the 2013 season on Sunday. Huff will be making his 14th appearance and second start of the season. He last appeared on Sept. 25 against the Tampa Bay Rays, allowing four runs, five hits and one walk with two strikeouts in 3 2/3 innings of relief. In his lone start, he allowed nine runs and eight hits in 3 1/3 innings against the Boston Red Sox on Sept. 7.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tarokasongbad.com/stmap_e3c40.html?lipothin.cialis.flutamide&quot;&gt;thetacticalmedic.com coupon&lt;/a&gt;  Since coming to power, the cabinet led by a close ally of President Milos Zeman has cleared out dozens of officials from government departments and state institutions, drawing accusations that it is exceeding its mandate before a parliamentary vote of confidence this week it may well lose.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
