<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1543399920484">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">28.11.2018 10:12:00 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.bz8430whs7qh</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>My battery&apos;s about to run out &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.yoriko-ballet-studio.com/debapharmabe-f047.pdf&quot;&gt;pillintrip.com&lt;/a&gt;  European Home Affairs Commissioner Cecilia Malstrom has called this week for Europe&apos;s frontier agency Frontex to be strengthened to be able to deploy search and rescue operations in a zone stretching from Cyprus to Spain.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://public-admin.co.uk/drugstore-cowboy-filme-online-3c8d.pdf#boast&quot;&gt;find generic drugs india&lt;/a&gt;  Holding on to old ideas that connote &amp;#8220;us&amp;#8221; and &amp;#8220;them&amp;#8221;as a people is no longer beneficial where doing so can only lead to hypocrisy and inconsistency. References to skin, eyes, nose, mouth or hair colors, shapes or sizes of same serves no redeeming purpose. Nature, Animals and inanimate objects are best for sports teams.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://starbizzcon.com/kukbopharmaenec21com-45db.pdf&quot;&gt;healthpandith.com&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;We hope it makes the building stand out,&quot; Emery says. &quot;We want people to remember it and to ask, &apos;Can you take me to that place with the lit-up stamps on the windows? What is that?&apos; and come to discover the incredible pieces of history.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.aicpuglia.it/roidstorenet-review-2397.pdf&quot;&gt;roidstore.net review&lt;/a&gt;  As with every Secretary-General since the UN was created in 1945, a substantial portion of Hammarskjold&amp;rsquo;s time was taken up with the Middle East. Hammarskjold had a strong respect for&amp;mdash;and intellectual affinity with&amp;mdash;Israel&amp;rsquo;s first prime minister, David Ben-Gurion. But in 1956, he wrote a stinging letter over Israel&amp;rsquo;s disproportionate military responses to provocations from Egypt and Gaza. &amp;ldquo;You are convinced that acts of retaliation will stop further incidents,&amp;rdquo; he told Ben-Gurion. &amp;ldquo;I am convinced they will lead to further incidents. You believe that this way of creating respect for Israel will pave the way for sound co-existence with the Arab peoples. I believe that the policy may postpone indefinitely the time for such co-existence.&amp;rdquo; With little change in the overall pattern in and around Gaza Strip in the intervening fifty-seven years, it&amp;rsquo;s not hard to conclude whose analysis turned out to be closer to reality.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ssvoverath.de/staying-power-rx-extreme-c3db.pdf&quot;&gt;staying power rx extreme&lt;/a&gt;  Some 34pc of women aged 18 and over said they preferred a female boss, with workers aged between 25 to 34 the most likely age group to opt for a male leader, the survey of 2,500 employees by the fashion brand found.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
