<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1543401640235">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">28.11.2018 10:40:40 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.ktrj73q3tsep</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>This is your employment contract &lt;a href=&quot;https://worldnewsnetwork.co.in/expressdoctorcouk-08d2.pdf&quot;&gt;expressdoctor.co.uk&lt;/a&gt;  Cell phones don&amp;#8217;t work on airliners once the airliner gets above the level of the cell phone towers, and not below that level either unless there is a clear line of sight between a cell phone tower antenna and the cell phone antenna (e.g. through a window) and a tower is close enough to be within range. Cell phone signals are much too weak to interfere with aircraft electronics. Cell phones were banned on airliners after 9/11 when the government announced that the passengers on flight 93 had called their families on their cell phones, something which is physically impossible. They didn&amp;#8217;t want the public to find out that cell phones don&amp;#8217;t work on airliners, at least those who did not already know.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bombeirodf.com.br/pharmaciebioparis18com-50f8.pdf&quot;&gt;vetrahealth.com&lt;/a&gt;  The Android 4.3 roll-out for the HTC One has already begun in the US, but despite plans to release the software this month HTC has announced a delay that will see the UK release pushed back to late November or even early December.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://pixelbedlam.co.uk/harga-nutrilite-saw-palmetto-65ef.pdf&quot;&gt;comprar saw palmetto curitiba&lt;/a&gt;  The revelations follow Office of National Statistics figures which show the number of women without children has almost doubled since the late 1990s, as more seem to be following the choices of celebrities like Dame Helen Mirren and Cameron Diaz, who have openly said they didn&amp;rsquo;t want children.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.purplecreativedesign.co.uk/black-rhino-9-3000-5884.pdf#fifteen&quot;&gt;black rhino 9000&lt;/a&gt;  A member of the Muslim Brotherhood and supporter of deposed Egyptian President Mohamed Mursi walks near a huge poster of Mursi, after late night clashes, at the entrance to their campsite near the Tomb of the Unknown Soldier, close to Rabaa Adawiya Square, in Nasr city area, east of Cairo July 28, 2013.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sensors.co.uk/imuran-pharmacy2us-9874.pdf#entertain&quot;&gt;imuran pharmacy2us&lt;/a&gt;  Europe&apos;s top shares were down 0.9 percent, near atwo-week low, while emerging stocks fell 1.3 percentto trade at a five-week low, though both indexes had recoveredslightly during the morning session.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
