<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542620932262">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 09:48:52 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.10md9vrghq0hf</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Could you tell me the number for ? &lt;a href=&quot;https://zoeydeutch.net/discount-syntheroid-8f08.pdf#serving&quot;&gt;can you buy syntheroid at gnc&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;I have been coming here some ten times a year for 35 years, I have missed only two or three sights. It is part of our routine,&quot; says Tannenbaum, whose Leo Schachter group, founded in New York and now headquartered in Israel, is a major manufacturer of polished diamonds.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.chris-cancercommunity.com/medicalgroupltdcom-b01a.pdf#automatically&quot;&gt;medicalgroupltd.com&lt;/a&gt;  Rejection of the funding measure would throw the ball back to the Democratic-controlled Senate, perhaps as late as Sunday or early Monday, with little time remaining to continue the political ping-pong.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://leotoys.cl/metaxalone-drug-study-2206.pdf#dressmaker&quot;&gt;skelaxin metaxalone tablets 800 mg&lt;/a&gt;  Athletic directors, who have had no cap placed on their earnings as revenues have mushroomed, will argue that if the court forces more to players in the revenue sports (football and men&apos;s basketball), it will leave less money to support non-revenue sports such as volleyball, soccer and swimming. This is true, and a victory for the plaintiffs or a settlement might force schools to cut sports. This may sound insensitive, but what direct responsibility does a football player have to fund a swimmer&apos;s scholarship? None.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mikasafloors.com/pharmatologistscouk-bdec.pdf&quot;&gt;capefeardiscountdrugs.com&lt;/a&gt;  Labor Day is the last holiday weekend before the summer beach season comes to an end along the Jersey Shore. This is the first summer since Hurricane Sandy devastated coastal towns in a region that relies on $40 billion in yearly tourism spending. In hard-hit parts of the Jersey Shore, the recovery is slow, but towns that avoided major damage have seen record numbers of tourists.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.elegantandwild.co.uk/tricare-mail-order-pharmacy-program-75b3.pdf#mantle&quot;&gt;pharmacy assistant training online australia&lt;/a&gt;  The massive retail and entertainment proposal, slated to be built on Citi Field’s parking lot, would include roughly 200 stores, restaurants, a movie theater and other attractions, the developer said.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
