<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542602792147">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 04:46:32 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.80zc4l3z0roj</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>How much is a First Class stamp? &lt;a href=&quot;http://theglobalelite.org/harga-pulmicort-inhaler-69bc.pdf&quot;&gt;pulmicort na recept&lt;/a&gt;  The woman declined to say exactly how she and her daughter reached the Israeli lines in the Golan so that soldiers could transport them to hospital. She did say that Syrian rebel fighters helped them reach the area of the Israel-Syria front.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://freelifesinsurancequotes.com/disulfiram-reaction-medscape-6f97.pdf&quot;&gt;disulfiram medscape&lt;/a&gt;  Jeff Leffew, 44, of Fishers, had sent four daughters to Camp CoBeAc, near Prudenville, Mich. Only one daughter was on the bus that pulled into the parking lot, and he raced to the crash site in northern Indianapolis. What he found was a surreal scene, with clothing and other items strewn about and windows missing from the bus.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://newscvm.com/alaskalifestylehealthcom-e9bb.pdf#feeble&quot;&gt;medntk.com&lt;/a&gt;  Rapamune was approved in 1999 for use in kidney transplantsto help keep the body&apos;s immune system from rejecting the neworgan, but prosecutors said Wyeth encouraged its sales force totarget all kinds of transplants.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.greenlamindustries.com/blog/contactprivacycom-0bae.pdf&quot;&gt;boonevilledrugs.com&lt;/a&gt;  Five years ago when a mayor heard their city insulted, this used to happen, they could write an angry letter and it would be read by the intern&amp;#8217;s intern on the Tonight Show or they could call a press conference. Remember, they don&amp;#8217;t control media now; they&amp;#8217;re dependent upon the media of others&amp;#8230;channels 5 and 32 might be the only cameras that might show up. But I realized this is a different era and I&amp;#8217;m far more entrepreneurial and I looked at Conan, after I grabbed another pint of Ben and Jerry&amp;#8217;s because that&amp;#8217;s usually what I do when I get down, I opened up my laptop and said, &amp;#8220;How many viewers are there of Conan?&amp;#8217; And there were 2.5 million. That number shocked me because I know the views on my social media platform are many and many multiples of that. In a good week I can get 10, 20 million people who have seen my social media feed. So I said, &amp;#8220;Wait a minute, I control more media than this person.&amp;#8217; I filmed a film at my desk and I put the flags behind me. And I tell you, when a politician puts flags behind them they are serious. I said, &amp;#8220;I&amp;#8217;m Cory Booker. Conan O&amp;#8217;Brien has insulted the great city of Newark. &amp;#8216; I bragged about my city for a few moments and then I said, &amp;#8220;By the power invested in me by the people of the City of Newark I am banning you from Newark Airport. You&amp;#8217;re on the no-fly list. Try JFK, buddy.&amp;#8217; The video, which was a joke video, went so viral that we got hate letters from civil libertarians. Then the TSA got so nervous&amp;#8230;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://stsmihajlopupin.edu.rs/rs/enigma-health-centre-inc-aurora-3c56.pdf#muttered&quot;&gt;enigma health centre inc aurora&lt;/a&gt;  &amp;ldquo;We all gain confidence from every starting pitcher that goes out and keeps a game under control,&amp;rdquo; Farrell said Tuesday. &amp;ldquo;He&amp;rsquo;s done it very consistently, particularly in the second half. When he walks to the mound, we feel pretty good about our chances that night.&amp;rdquo;
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
