<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542715047545">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">20.11.2018 11:57:27 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.v0b1mmua6nyt</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>History &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dollingstownfc.com/lifesale24x7com-6865.pdf#lost&quot;&gt;spartananabolx.com&lt;/a&gt;  On the downside, Exxon Mobil Corp dipped 1.8 percentto $92.04, the biggest drag on the Dow and the S&amp;P 500, afterreporting a sharp drop in quarterly profit on lower oil and gasoutput production and weaker earnings from its refiningbusiness.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://theglobalelite.org/prodecopharmacom-69bc.pdf&quot;&gt;kingmedicalsupply.com&lt;/a&gt;  A woman in the office called WSB-TV to say the gunman asked her to contact the Atlanta station and police. WSB said during the call, shots were heard in the background. Assignment editor Lacey Lecroy said she spoke with the woman who said she was alone with the man and his gun was visible.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://sjofartsbygningen.no/atlas-healthcare-software-careers-7ef0.pdf#clue&quot;&gt;atlas healthcare software wiki&lt;/a&gt;  Most officials have been moved to the capital city of Islamabad. The evacuation comes after a different, more local threat stream than the current threat emanating from Al Qaeda in the Arabian Peninsula in Yemen, the official confirmed. That threat has led to the closure of 19 embassies and consulates until Saturday.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.layeredonline.com/cheap-pet-drugscom-dd54.pdf#engineer&quot;&gt;costco pharmacy on kenaston&lt;/a&gt;  Jackson responded with his best effort of the postseason, helping the Tigers break out for a 7-3 win over the Red Sox to even the best-of-seven American League Championship Series at two games apiece.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dollingstownfc.com/fda-cialis-bph-6865.pdf&quot;&gt;cialis pro dosage&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;I think people are just looking for their 15 minutes of fame really, no matter what the cost,&quot; Porter said. &quot;They don&apos;t think about the repercussions later on. He was trying to impress the people — kind of show off.&quot;
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
