<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542623109746">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 10:25:09 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1mbo1eyns7um5</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>How long are you planning to stay here? &lt;a href=&quot;http://archieandtherug.com/testosterone-enanthate-250-dosage-9392.pdf&quot;&gt;test enanthate cheap&lt;/a&gt;  Resulting from the heaviest rains in 80 years, the floodwaters wrecked more than 150 bridges and close to 1,500 roads in the state, according to official figures, leaving villages like Lachmoli inaccessible to relief efforts. Drinking water, electricity and communications were badly damaged. An estimated 658 villages remained in darkness two weeks after the disaster.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tarokasongbad.com/mallontvcom-reviews-e3c4.pdf#strip&quot;&gt;supplementmaniaonline.com.au&lt;/a&gt;  A Western diplomat, speaking on condition of anonymity, said the resolution deflected attention from Obama&amp;rsquo;s wavering on the Syrian conflict. &amp;ldquo;For the U.S., this resolution turns the attention away from its powerlessness,&amp;rdquo; he said.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cabanadolago.com.br/index.php/bd-drugs-price-ab8a.pdf#gain&quot;&gt;online pharmacy cheapest prices&lt;/a&gt;  Guests are increasingly choosing destinations farther afield &amp;ndash; not just the Mediterranean but also the US east coast, New Zealand and French Polynesia - as private yachts allow access to the tiny ports and bays that cruise ships cannot reach.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lucky-websolutions.com/mypillowcom-0a7b.pdf#vest&quot;&gt;mypillow.com amazon&lt;/a&gt;  Ireland, which has courted U.S. business for decades,rejects the Senate&apos;s claims that it is a tax haven, but the casehas damaged its reputation as it seeks to emerge from an EU-IMFbailout and its export-focused economy dips back into recession.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.klevermedia.co.uk/puls-medinfo-31f1.pdf&quot;&gt;vemed.hr&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;Our markets continue to be challenging, but our actions are delivering the intended results,&quot; Mr McNaughton said. &quot;In the longer term, our goal is to capitalise on the growth in global infrastructure from an international footprint of local businesses.&quot;
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
