<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542632324988">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 12:58:44 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1gkble01emjt6</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Can I use your phone? &lt;a href=&quot;http://sjofartsbygningen.no/metabolicforcehealthcom-7ef0.pdf#sitting&quot;&gt;adhdchildremedy.com&lt;/a&gt;  ** Energy majors Exxon Mobil Corp and Royal DutchShell are among the suitors advancing to the next roundof bidding for Newfield Exploration Co&apos;s Malaysian andChinese oil and gas fields valued at about $1.2 billion, peoplefamiliar with the matter said.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tarokasongbad.com/greatwhitepeptidecom-review-e3c4.pdf&quot;&gt;greatwhitepeptide.com review&lt;/a&gt;  That exchange led to a testy retort by Ralph Hall (R-Tex.). &quot;You got a better answer than I received from Mrs. McCarthy about a year ago before the science committee,&quot; Hall told McCarthy. &quot;I may have asked you a question you didn&apos;t like and your answer was, ‘I&apos;m not in the business of creating jobs.’”
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://stsmihajlopupin.edu.rs/rs/martin-pharmacy-san-juan-3c56.pdf#overtime&quot;&gt;san martin pharmacy huntington park hours&lt;/a&gt;  New York playground legend Dean (The Dream) Meminger, who rose to become a New York Knick but later sank into drugs and hard living, was found dead in a Harlem hotel Friday of what cops said is a possible overdose. He was 65.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://accentresurfacing.com/ponstel-cvs-4110.pdf#cannon&quot;&gt;ponstel cvs&lt;/a&gt;  After shocking investors with a financial warning on FridayBlackBerry said on Monday that it had agreed to be bought by aprivate firm but some investors were doubtful as to whether thedeal will end up closing.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.casadeadoracao.com.br/index.php/supplementsninjanet-bac9.pdf&quot;&gt;bestmedspharmacy.com&lt;/a&gt;  Here is what Chief Justice Stuart Rabner of New Jersey’s Supreme Court wrote on Friday in a decision upholding a lower court order allowing gay marriage in his state, thus denying the delay that Gov. Chris Christie had sought as part of a bad, dumb, losing game:
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
