<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542699908139">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">20.11.2018 07:45:08 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1979mo2g07j0k</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>History &lt;a href=&quot;https://paradiseinmexico.com.mx/healbe-gobe-amazon-c13c.pdf&quot;&gt;healbe gobe review 2017&lt;/a&gt;  In the near-term, Europe needs help in addressing crime -countries such as Moldova lie on important trafficking routestowards the EU. In the Caucasus, territorial disputes such asthat between Armenia and Azerbaijan could hurt Europe&apos;s energyaims and pull it into conflict with Russia.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://sjofartsbygningen.no/brainstorm-elite-7ef0.pdf&quot;&gt;brainstorm elite side effects&lt;/a&gt;  NEW YORK, Aug 15 (IFR) - US retailers could see the cost ofinsuring their debt against default rise in coming months ifrecent results are anything to go by, as a slowdown in consumerspending starts to bite.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://theglobalelite.org/ropharmaro-69bc.pdf#informs&quot;&gt;polimed.com.tr&lt;/a&gt;  The Pentagon said over the weekend that it would recallaround 350,000 of its furloughed civilian workers. The rest ofthe 800,000 or so federal employees idled by the shutdown facedanother week off the job.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://reflectiveteens.com/myhealthrecordcom-213a.pdf#bands&quot;&gt;myhealthrecord.com&lt;/a&gt;  Guy had in fact called for help and stayed on the phone with the 911 dispatcher until paramedics arrived.  He even knew to lock up the family&amp;#8217;s dog when the police arrived so that the dog wouldn&amp;#8217;t bother them.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://sjofartsbygningen.no/portamedic-services-7ef0.pdf#bade&quot;&gt;colette portamedic services&lt;/a&gt;  One yet to be identified rider unclipped his helmet, which he used to smash open the driverâs side window of Lienâs car. Edwards punched at the window to the backseat, where Lienâs daughter was sitting, police sources said.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
