<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542613113315">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 07:38:33 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1a4844vjmgle3</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Accountant supermarket manager &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.wychwoodcabinetmakers.co.uk/anacyclus-pyrethrum-common-name-e0f9.pdf#consists&quot;&gt;anacyclus pyrethrum common name&lt;/a&gt;  Good morning and welcome. We&amp;#039;ll be bringing you the day&amp;#039;s business headlines, as well as company results, economic data and the best of the BBC&amp;#039;s business stories as they happen. You can get in touch by emailing bizlivepage@bbc.co.uk or tweeting @BBCBusiness.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.chris-cancercommunity.com/cvs-saw-palmetto-recall-b01a.pdf&quot;&gt;saw palmetto cvs&lt;/a&gt;  Moby Dick, a bar in San Francisco&apos;s Castro neighborhood, joined the boycott last week but its owner, Joe Cappelletti, said he stopped it on Wednesday after learning that Stolichnaya has been a longtime advocate of gay rights.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://zoeydeutch.net/cost-venlafaxine-uk-8f08.pdf&quot;&gt;venlafaxine buy online uk&lt;/a&gt;  Thousands of firefighters fought to snuff out or at least contain blazes that had burned more than 40,000 acres of timber and range land across Oregon on Friday, 5,000 acres more than on Thursday, said Carol Connolly, a spokeswoman for the Northwest Interagency Coordination Center.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://digital-matchbox.com/precio-anafranil-5522.pdf&quot;&gt;precio anafranil mexico&lt;/a&gt;  After the 11 September 2001 attacks in the US, the challenge of securing the 9,000-km Canada-US border from possible terrorist infiltration prompted both countries to look at ways of sharing information.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://sjofartsbygningen.no/otcwholesalecom-7ef0.pdf#swollen&quot;&gt;www.otcwholesale.com/tens-units.html&lt;/a&gt;  Now in order to address those trends, let&apos;s turn to our business segment results, beginning with our Publishing segment. Once again, this quarter, our all-access content subscription model provided notable momentum and strong financial returns during the quarter. Against this backdrop, however, the continued softness and macroeconomic trends caused advertising revenues to decline about -- by about 5% again during the quarter. Despite this, total circulation revenue gains of 6% nearly fully offset these declines, demonstrating the growing strength of the investments we&apos;ve made in our Publishing segment. As a result, Publishing segment revenues were just 2% lower for the quarter on a year-over-year basis.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
