<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542549939354">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 14:05:39 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.84clve46atql</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Get a job &lt;a href=&quot;http://lemcasesorias.com/index.php/ciprofloxacina-500-mg-comprimidos-para-que-sirve-83f5.pdf&quot;&gt;is ciprofloxacin used for sinus infections&lt;/a&gt;  Until now, the industry, while booming, has remained mostly under the radar. But in August, a million cockroaches escaped from a farm in Jiangsu province, making headlines in the Chinese media.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.proguaru.com.br/buying-doxycycline-tablets-7684.pdf#fear&quot;&gt;doxycycline dosage dogs lyme&lt;/a&gt;  Michael Starzan, a 42-year-old investment banker in New York City, said One Medical Group, the practice where he generally goes for care, sent out an email recently saying it had flu shots available and inviting patients to make an appointment.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.haroldwhitefuneraldirectors.co.uk/jhoots-pharmacy-bristol-jobs-bd82.pdf#railway&quot;&gt;jhoots pharmacy castle bromwich&lt;/a&gt;  These conversations are difficult for a U.S. AttorneyGeneral, because he or she often does not want to be seeninternally as caving to pressure from people or companies beingprosecuted, said a former senior employee at the JusticeDepartment.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ascfinancialadvisers.co.uk/medrol-dose-pack-40mg-5553.pdf#galaxy&quot;&gt;medrol dose pack 40mg&lt;/a&gt;  &amp;#8220;Most of the outbreaks we&amp;#8217;ve seen in the past have been associated with fresh produce that have been imported from other countries,&amp;#8221; said Jessica Rigler with the Arizona Dept. of Health Services.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ascfinancialadvisers.co.uk/latissedoctorcom-5553.pdf#instinctive&quot;&gt;latissedoctor.com&lt;/a&gt;  The National Sleep Foundation suggests that preschoolers between 3 and 5 years old get about 11 to 13 hours of sleep a night, while kids up to the age of 12 need around 10 to 11 hours of nightly shut-eye.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
