<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542534373006">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 09:46:13 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.k6a5yuhyrzcm</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>How many are there in a book? &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.klevermedia.co.uk/rhino-11-platinum-15000-31f1.pdf#hike&quot;&gt;rhino 11 platinum 15000&lt;/a&gt;  A UK parliamentary report says the country’s plans for the roll-out of superfast broadband to rural and country areas are in chaos. The report, from Parliament’s influential Public Accounts Committee (PAC), reserved most of its criticism for BT but also accused the UK government of “mismanagement” in awarding BT near-monopoly status in the handling of broadband deployment.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.haroldwhitefuneraldirectors.co.uk/ea-hawse-health-center-moorefield-wv-bd82.pdf&quot;&gt;hawse health center baker west virginia&lt;/a&gt;  “Development in this country is not for the people, it is for the small few – the government and the big company,” says Tep Vanny, 32, who will work as an election observer on Sunday and has led protests against the eviction of more than 3,000 families from around Phnom Penh&apos;s Beoung Kak lake – once a popular tourist draw but now a walled-off landfill awaiting the building of a hotel by a company linked to the CPP.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.artistparama.com/megiclinic-5168.pdf#dance&quot;&gt;megi.clinic&lt;/a&gt;  But by the summer of 2010, Costolo felt confident enough inhis concept that he began seeking a deputy to ramp up thecompany&apos;s sales effort. For months, he courted Adam Bain, arising star at News Corp, and at the same time began assiduouslycourting marketers, from corner suites on Madison Avenue toindustry conferences on the French Riviera.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.artistparama.com/medbroadcastcom-5168.pdf#captain&quot;&gt;medbroadcast.com&lt;/a&gt;  The Chinese Red Cross said it was shipping 200 tents, 1,000 sets of household items, and 2,000 jackets to the area and sending teams from both Lanzhou and Beijing to help with relief work and assess further needs.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.layeredonline.com/apex-pharmacy-marketing-pte-ltd-singapore-dd54.pdf&quot;&gt;apex pharmacy 199 old street&lt;/a&gt;  IBM is entrenched in corporations across the globe; and withone of the industry&apos;s biggest research budgets, is likely toremain so for some time. But it and other players like Oracle are taking note of AWS as cloud computing takes off.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
