<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542546574521">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 13:09:34 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.15ckc87at8y6x</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Through friends &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ecorporationbd.com/amoxicillin-trihydrate-500-side-effects-aaa8.pdf#crow&quot;&gt;amoxicillin ratiopharm 250 mg 5 ml dosierung&lt;/a&gt;  Humana said it had spent 83.4 percent of premiums it took inon medical benefits, down from 83.5 percent a year earlier. Ithad 12.37 million medical members at the end of the quarter, andanother 8.27 million people were in dental, vision and othersupplemental benefit plans.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lovemycase.com/how-to-take-cialis-5mg-f2c2.pdf#continually&quot;&gt;cialis 20 mg online pharmacy&lt;/a&gt;  The Nigerian Maritime Administration and Safety Agency(NIMASA) had blocked liquefied natural gas ships from leavingthe Bonny terminal for the past three weeks because of a disputeover unpaid levies, which NLNG argued it was exempt from paying.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.artistparama.com/atrazine-4l-label-5168.pdf#barley&quot;&gt;atrazine label southern ag&lt;/a&gt;  The Yankees and Dodgers are seemingly headed in opposite directions. Don Mattingly’s bunch is 27-6 in its last 33 games – the best 33-game stretch in the franchise’s illustrious history – surging to a 3 ½-game lead in the National League West.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.anupamdebashisroy.com/extensive-ageless-serum-f2ef.pdf#traverse&quot;&gt;extensive ageless serum reviews&lt;/a&gt;  &amp;ldquo;The facts remain the same. He&apos;s a very valued player, an absolute magician on the football field. We&apos;ll communicate in some way nearly every day, either through text or through a conversation. Luis is a real competitor, a real winner.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://newscvm.com/naproxen-500-dosage-e9bb.pdf&quot;&gt;naprosyn 250 mg yan etkileri&lt;/a&gt;  SMEs need to seek a good return on their marketing investment, according to Mark Cropper, chairman of the family-run paper-maker James Cropper. &amp;ldquo;Budgets are limited. We can&amp;rsquo;t afford to take out adverts,&amp;rdquo; he explains.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
