<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542605559283">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 05:32:39 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.h94u30y64hi4</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Another service? &lt;a href=&quot;https://virtual-operations.com/cvs-pharmacy-photo-price-92e2.pdf&quot;&gt;best discount pharmacy hcg&lt;/a&gt;  Coming in for the assist is the American Israel Public Affairs Committee (AIPAC). The group announced it will unfold an all-out effort on Capitol Hill, a landmark move for an organization that has sat out rounding up members for votes on other resolutions in the past. 
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sarah-hyland.net/testosterone-max-price-in-india-79a8.pdf&quot;&gt;where can i buy testosterone max&lt;/a&gt;  &amp;#8220;A few of us did build and test a feature like this internally. Our conclusion after testing it: people are way more interested in seeing *who* liked their posts, rather than just the number of people who saw it. In fact, in all of the thousands of pieces of feedback we receive about News Feed each month, virtually no one has asked to see this information. If we saw enough people asking for this, we would definitely consider building it into the product. But, from what we&amp;#8217;ve seen, including the raw numbers isn&amp;#8217;t worth the space it would take up on the screen.&amp;#8221;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://sjofartsbygningen.no/best-anti-cellulite-creams-in-india-7ef0.pdf&quot;&gt;best anti cellulite creams&lt;/a&gt;  The IPCC commissioner, Tom Davies, said: &quot;This has been a thorough and painstaking investigation which has required careful scrutiny of thousands of documents and hundreds of statements, and interviews have been carried out with relevant officers.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://zoeydeutch.net/healthpharmacom-8f08.pdf#afford&quot;&gt;thequestforhealth.net&lt;/a&gt;  A record number of mayoral candidates were standing as independents in the first local election since Portugal turned to the International Monetary Fund and European Union for the 78 billion euro ($106 billion) bailout in 2011 - a sign of disenchantment with the traditional parties.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://paradiseinmexico.com.mx/princess-mask-c13c.pdf#affairs&quot;&gt;princess mask making&lt;/a&gt;  Kendraâs Law was intended to reduce violent acts by people who sought treatment for mental illness but failed to comply with it over time. However, researchers say thatâs not the goal of the services mandated by some judges.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
