<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542537590680">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 10:39:50 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1vkwcznft9o60</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>What&apos;s the exchange rate for euros? &lt;a href=&quot;https://leotoys.cl/drugspills24com-2206.pdf#mug&quot;&gt;health.bizcalcs.com&lt;/a&gt;  Syria&apos;s civil war has killed more than 100,000 people and divided the Middle East between Sunni Gulf states and Turkey which mostly support the rebels, and Shi&apos;ite Iran and Hezbollah which have backed Assad.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dollingstownfc.com/bragghealthorg-6865.pdf&quot;&gt;esmarthealth.com&lt;/a&gt;  “I’m not a 20-year-old girl living with her parents who just finished college,” says Kensil, who loves her 1.5-carat showstopper. “I’ve got a career. I’m established. I had a house and a car before I even met Nick. I can contribute to this.”
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.proguaru.com.br/vici-clinic-fryzjer-krakw-7684.pdf#sweetness&quot;&gt;vici clinic kriolipoliza opinie&lt;/a&gt;  Steady winds and rising temperatures stoked the fire Wednesday afternoon, sending large clouds of brownish-black smoke into the sky. The fire was still only about 25 percent contained, said Utah fire official Mike Eriksson.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://sjofartsbygningen.no/blue-monster-drink-caffeine-7ef0.pdf&quot;&gt;tpc blue monster at doral scorecard&lt;/a&gt;  Luckiest will be the owners of the $115 million two-story, six-bedroom, six-bath penthouse with 360-degree views offering “the opportunity to experience the magnitude of New York from a truly breathtaking vantage point.”
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://accentresurfacing.com/nutrex-lipo-6x-opinie-4110.pdf#constraints&quot;&gt;nutrex lipo 6 cla price&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;In exchange for the commitments I have made over almost 20 years in favour of my country and coming almost at the end of my public life, I have been rewarded with accusations and a verdict that is founded on absolutely nothing, that takes away my personal freedom and my political rights.&quot;
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
