<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542597947493">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 03:25:47 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.p9yrmr2bpgqg</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I&apos;m sorry, she&apos;s  &lt;a href=&quot;http://reflectiveteens.com/makemedicinesaffordableorg-213a.pdf&quot;&gt;ourhealthybody.net&lt;/a&gt;  Plans to sell a 10 percent stake in Coal India have alreadybeen scaled back to 5 percent because of resistance from unionsthat now oppose any privatisation of the world&apos;s largest coalcompany. They plan a three-day strike next month to stop the 5percent sale from going ahead.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://virtual-operations.com/captopril-yahoo-92e2.pdf&quot;&gt;captopril yahoo&lt;/a&gt;  In particular, it underlines the need to limit the &quot;marginof discretion&quot; or extent of any powers given to a body that willdecide about the closure or &apos;resolution&apos; of a bank in a eurozone state. It questions the right, for example, to use aEuropean fund for tackling problem banks.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://leotoys.cl/nicholls-pharmacy-nicholls-georgia-2206.pdf#whirl&quot;&gt;nicholls pharmacy&lt;/a&gt;  They have also prompted Savills estate agents to amend their house price forecast. It believes that property values will increase by 3.5% this year, compared with its previous forecast of no change, and will go up by 4.5% next year, instead of a predicted 1.5% rise.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tarokasongbad.com/can-you-take-ibuprofen-with-sudafed-decongestant-liquid-e3c4.pdf&quot;&gt;is it safe to take ibuprofen and breastfeeding&lt;/a&gt;  Last winter, Verbier enjoyed the best snow in living memory. But even in normal seasons, it&amp;rsquo;s pretty safe to book early or late. From the resort at 1500m, heights of more than 2700m can be reached by two consecutive gondola rides that take under 11 minutes in total. There, the high altitude guarantees abundant snow.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.proguaru.com.br/keeverpharmacycom-7684.pdf&quot;&gt;artsforhealth.com&lt;/a&gt;  Eduardo Santos de Oliveira, an aggressive federalprosecutor, has already launched a case against the port todetermine civil liability for alleged environmental damage.Oliveira, the prosecutor in Campos de Goytacazes, the largestcity near the port, has previously drawn global attention forlaunching Brazil&apos;s largest-ever environmental lawsuit.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
