<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542730278931">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">20.11.2018 16:11:18 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.13gtmjzxea87i</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>What company are you calling from? &lt;a href=&quot;https://laser-eye-surgery-reviews.org/prescription-drugs-used-to-treat-fibromyalgia-6a83.pdf&quot;&gt;what happens when you mix alcohol and prescription drugs&lt;/a&gt;  With borrowing authority set to run out on Thursday, Senate Majority Leader Harry Reid and Republican leader Senator Mitch McConnell &quot;are very close&quot; to an agreement, Representative Chris Van Hollen, a top House Democrat, told MSNBC late Tuesday night.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://leotoys.cl/ayurslim-bodybuilding-2206.pdf&quot;&gt;ayurslim bodybuilding&lt;/a&gt;  As well as the tax fraud case, Berlusconi is also fighting a separate conviction for paying for sex with a minor, in the notorious &quot;bunga bunga&quot; prostitution case that tarnished his final months in office in 2011.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.md-interiors.co.uk/proxeed-bustine-indicazioni-a6a4.pdf#drank&quot;&gt;proxeed plus yan etkileri&lt;/a&gt;  The statement from Lionsgate is nice, but the premiere reads beyond hand-wavey to me. Whatever any one person chooses to do is their business, and I don&amp;#8217;t have a problem with what anyone decides re: seeing the film. Benefits are nice, though I hope they don&amp;#8217;t affiliate with HRC because that&amp;#8217;s a whole other kettle of problematic fish, and I&amp;#8217;d like to see money going to something like Lambda Legal which is doing the actual legal work to fight what NOM is doing, but I don&amp;#8217;t want anyone thinking this makes things okay. Any money Card receives from paid work is still being tithed to the CoLDS (which also funded Prop 8) and being put into NOM. Residuals, back-end points, etc., put money in his pockets. To me, that&amp;#8217;s a problem. If the perception is that the film is being let off the hook of Card&amp;#8217;s utter failure at humanity allows people to stop thinking about how they consume media, then we&amp;#8217;re back to square one. My hope for this entire situation is not that EG will fail at the box office, (I don&amp;#8217;t know that the general public is aware enough for that) but that perhaps we can look at the ethical considerations of our media consumption. I don&amp;#8217;t require the art I love to be made by good people, that&amp;#8217;s an irrational expectation of life. Card may be a perfectly nice person to the people around him, make art that people love which does no harm to anyone, and still be incredibly dangerous to our society because he has the money and authority to pursue a bigoted agenda and make it stick. If we don&amp;#8217;t question our consumption of media in the face of his actions, when will we?
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://lemcasesorias.com/index.php/tiziana-pharma-share-price-83f5.pdf#vacation&quot;&gt;coupon code for pharmacy rx one&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;Eight officers were injured, two requiring hospital treatment for head injuries,&quot; Northern Ireland police said in a statement. There were eight arrests for public order offences. Police did not specify what triggered the violence.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cabanadolago.com.br/index.php/aman-pharmacy-ab8a.pdf#bandy&quot;&gt;aman pharmacy&lt;/a&gt;  Think about it, this dirt was being shoveled long before kickoff. Ditching the hyperbole spewed by these pregame gasbags, the reality is this: The Giants have officially crossed the border into the land of media irrelevance. In terms of coverage they are on their way to becoming an afterthought. Reporters covering the team are looking at only having the draft to look forward to.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
