<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542532373318">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 09:12:53 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.usezsxbb5pyq</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I&apos;m interested in this position &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lovemycase.com/amedeerocherhatenablogcom-f2c2.pdf#jumble&quot;&gt;amedeerocher.hatenablog.com&lt;/a&gt;  Lincoln led the North in the Civil War during the 1860s and signed the Emancipation Proclamation that started the process of ending slavery. A century later, Johnson broke free from his past as a senator from segregated Texas and signed the Civil Rights Act of 1964 and the Voting Rights Act of 1965 as part of his embrace of the civil rights movement.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ascfinancialadvisers.co.uk/zyprexa-6-weeks-5553.pdf#web&quot;&gt;zyprexa use in autism&lt;/a&gt;  Jean Adams, a senior lecturer in public health at Newcastle University, who carried out the research with Graham, said that children in particular were affected by exposure to drinks brands on TV. &quot;Children who don&apos;t drink, who are exposed to alcohol marketing, are more likely to start drinking earlier in their lives,&quot; she said. &quot;And children who are already drinking are more likely to drink more after exposure to alcohol marketing.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://reflectiveteens.com/medicinecareers360com-213a.pdf#that&quot;&gt;medicine.careers360.com/latest&lt;/a&gt;  A minor difference, Instagram includes a slightly transparent frame around the video, in shooting mode. (Notice the white writing on the blue card in the screengrab above.) Depending on the user, this will either improve or confuse video shooting. You may find it helps to frame your video, if you&apos;re very particular. For others, this outside-frame movement may get in the way.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cabanadolago.com.br/index.php/cialis-gnstig-bestellen-ab8a.pdf&quot;&gt;cialis cena w aptece&lt;/a&gt;  The gunman then kicked his way into a third-floor apartment, where he shot to death Patricio Simono, 54; his wife Merly Niebles, 51; and their 17-year-old daughter. Family members said Simono worked at a car wash and Niebles cleaned hotel rooms. Their daughter wanted to be a nurse.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ecorporationbd.com/medterracbdcom-aaa8.pdf#consisted&quot;&gt;psychtreatment.com&lt;/a&gt;  This marked the industry&apos;s first year-on-year sales declinein more than two years. There were two fewer shopping days inSeptember compared with the previous year, and part of the LaborDay shopping weekend fell in August.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
