<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542865121370">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">22.11.2018 05:38:41 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1t575s814y0lk</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>very best job &lt;a href=&quot;https://muv.asia/iforce-nutrition-thermoxyn-detox-bf28.pdf&quot;&gt;iforce nutrition thermoxyn&lt;/a&gt;  Information in this press release that involves the Company&apos;s expectations business prospects, plans, intentions or strategies regarding its future are forward-looking statements that are not facts and that involve substantial risks and uncertainties. You can identify these statements by the use of words such as &quot;anticipate,&quot; &quot;estimate,&quot; &quot;expect,&quot; &quot;project,&quot; &quot;intend,&quot; &quot;should,&quot; &quot;plan,&quot; &quot;goal,&quot; &quot;believe,&quot; and other words and terms of similar meaning in connection with any discussion of future operating or financial performance. Among the factors that could cause the Company&apos;s actual future results to differ materially from those expressed in the forward-looking statements set forth in this release include the following: the ability to maintain or renew the Company&apos;s licenses; competitive developments affecting the Company&apos;s current products; first-party price reductions; the ability to successfully market both new and existing products domestically and internationally; difficulties or delays in manufacturing; unanticipated product delays; or a downturn in the market or industry. A further list and description of these and other factors, risks, uncertainties and other matters can be found in the Company&apos;s most recent annual report, and any subsequent quarterly reports, filed with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission and the Canadian Securities Administrators. The forward-looking statements in this release are based upon information available to the Company as of the date of this release, and the Company assumes no obligation to update any such forward-looking statements as a result of new information or future events or developments. Forward-looking statements believed to be true when made may ultimately prove to be incorrect. These statements are not guarantees of the future performance of the Company and are subject to risks, uncertainties and other factors, some of which are beyond its control and may cause actual results to differ materially from current expectations.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
