<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1543416078351">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">28.11.2018 14:41:18 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.f1p800fgnsu6</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>What&apos;s the exchange rate for euros? &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.purplecreativedesign.co.uk/methotrexate-yahoo-5884.pdf#motive&quot;&gt;methotrexate yahoo answers&lt;/a&gt;  Brazil&apos;s telecommunications agency said on Monday it wouldinvestigate whether local operators had violated customerprivacy rules in alleged surveillance of Braziliantelecommunications data by the U.S. spy agencies.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.purplecreativedesign.co.uk/ookisa-hair-products-5884.pdf#management&quot;&gt;ookisa shampoo where to buy&lt;/a&gt;  The slight fall in gold production was not enough to put off analysts at heavyweight broker JPMorgan Cazenove, who said that Fresnillo remained their preferred stock for exposure to precious metals, and dismissed the company&amp;rsquo;s gold forecast downgrade as a &amp;ldquo;distraction&amp;rdquo;.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.purplecreativedesign.co.uk/apollo-pharmacy-cyber-city-5884.pdf&quot;&gt;apollo pharmacy cyber city&lt;/a&gt;  Subic Bay is a natural deep harbor that can accommodate two large warships acquired recently by the Philippines from the United States, a defense treaty ally, he said, especially compared to shallower harbor at the naval fleet base at Sangley Point in Cavite province, south of Manila.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://worldnewsnetwork.co.in/europharmacyca-08d2.pdf&quot;&gt;smtxonline.navihealth.us&lt;/a&gt;  Before coming to the helm of JPL, he played an important role on the science teams for lab&amp;#39;s early Mariner missions, using images captured by the spacecraft to start constructing a geologic history for the Red Planet. He was also part of the Mariner 4 imaging team that captured the first close-up of Mars in 1964. After leaving NASA, Murray became a professor of planetary science and geology at Caltech.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.brentwood-karting.com/index.php/mennenmedicalcom-6e56.pdf#enlarge&quot;&gt;healthyglow.com&lt;/a&gt;  No other wildfire had claimed more firefighters in 80 years, and it was the deadliest single day for fire crews since the terror attacks of Sept. 11, 2001. The Granite Mountain team was unique among the nation&apos;s roughly 110 Hotshot crews as the first and only such unit attached to a municipal fire department.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
