<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542655209074">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 19:20:09 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1xn85iwf0fe2f</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Would you like to leave a message? &lt;a href=&quot;http://archieandtherug.com/genrx-reviews-9392.pdf#decay&quot;&gt;genrx pharmaceuticals private limited&lt;/a&gt;  The clickable touch pad, well, that&apos;s another story. It works reasonably well enough for basic one-finger navigation around Chrome OS, but for two-finger scrolling or multifinger gestures, it&apos;s lousy. There&apos;s no inertial scrolling, so Web page browsing becomes herky-jerky. Tap-and-drag moves were also hard to pull off consistently. It&apos;s a far cry from the smooth feel of better-made laptops or the touch screen on any tablet. And, in the 10 or so months since I last reviewed the Acer C7, it&apos;s even less impressive compared with the wonderful feel, say, of the Chromebook Pixel&apos;s touch pad. Good touch pads can be done on Chromebooks, just not on this one.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.proguaru.com.br/ukhealthcarechairscouk-7684.pdf&quot;&gt;balancetreatment.com&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;He&apos;s doing great, but the thing that doctors have warned us about is that even though his residual tumor is stable, the reality is that half of kids with Jack&apos;s illness relapse in the future,&quot; dad Andy said.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://leotoys.cl/busted-buying-drugs-online-2206.pdf&quot;&gt;costco pharmacy norfolk va hours&lt;/a&gt;  Americans may think they&amp;#39;ve attained a state of relative gender parity, but some antiquated laws still on the books in a number of states indicate otherwise. Although these bizarre laws are no longer enforced by any reasonable police agency, they&amp;#39;re also hard to remove: meaning that some of these odd strictures are still technically valid. Here&amp;#39;s a sampling:
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cabanadolago.com.br/index.php/uk-rxcartcom-review-ab8a.pdf&quot;&gt;uk-rxcart.com&lt;/a&gt;  “I was already in a place of bliss, I had been doing sit down meditation for 20 years but it opened up my ability to sense more and more subtle things and my appreciation for men,” said Lorre, who admitted she had been a skeptic at first about orgasmic meditation, also called OMing.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.wychwoodcabinetmakers.co.uk/mental-bright-e0f9.pdf&quot;&gt;mental bright ingredients&lt;/a&gt;  The first-round pick of the Phils in 2007, d’Arnaud has twice been traded for Cy Young-winning pitchers. He was dealt to the Blue Jays in the deal that brought Roy Halladay to Philadelphia and then again for Dickey.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
