<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542508291472">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 02:31:31 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.l5y7vmmooqm6</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Looking for a job &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mikasafloors.com/lupmedcombr-bdec.pdf&quot;&gt;stonebridgedoctors.com&lt;/a&gt;  At this point Jaimie Fuller, chairman of Skins, the Swiss-based compression clothing company supporting Johnson&amp;rsquo;s anti-drugs crusade, interjects, aware that such remarks could be construed as obscene egotism. &amp;ldquo;The question is Ben&amp;rsquo;s belief in himself. Nobody achieves at this one-in-six-billion level without being full of confidence. It is incredible.&amp;rdquo;
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.layeredonline.com/propecia-bestellen-schweiz-dd54.pdf&quot;&gt;propecia lek cena&lt;/a&gt;  Whom is kidding Who?????? S.S. has been pretty much a dead issue for past 3 years... Let&apos;s face it we went 2 years, WITH (0) percent increase with maybe minimal increase in Medicaid costs, however, with MUCH GREATER COSTS with Hosiptal, Doctors, Medication costs, REACHING ANOTHER ALL TIME HIGH&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; just check your bills, and receipts... This will never go away, as the government has already BLOWN  what S&gt;S and Medicare was all about over 25 years ago, thanks to our POLITICANS,,,,,and this will continue for many more years to come???? Our children and grandchildren, will pay a big price, not only for this but, NOW for the additional TRILLIONS,,, which will be pissed away, thanks to our Senate, House, and President?????  Why continue to beat a DEAD ISSUE....for the NEWS&lt; and other LEACHES, such as newspeople, stock market analysts, etc.. THEIR ALL LEACHES AS WELL&lt; cause the only thing they contribute is more negative and up to date nonsense, by the minute??????? and can&apos;t do anything except confuse the USA people even more.....
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://contactconsultoria.com/index.php/agapillscom-a511.pdf#nowadays&quot;&gt;duane-reade-pharmacy.com&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;The initial recommendation for rest and observation issued on Saturday ... was modified,&quot; said a statement from the Fundacion Favaloro hospital. &quot;Considering these symptoms, the president&apos;s medical team is suggesting surgery.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.anupamdebashisroy.com/vivelle-wesleycom-f2ef.pdf&quot;&gt;aclepsa.net&lt;/a&gt;  When the Sixers advanced to the Finals to take on the defending champion Lakers -- a team that hadn&apos;t lost yet in the postseason -- it really was seen as Iverson versus Goliath. The only chance Philly had stood in six feet tall. And with his 48 points in Game 1, the Sixers shocked the world. It was almost as if the next six games didn&apos;t matter. Iverson slayed the Lakers on his own, and humiliated them in the process.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.elegantandwild.co.uk/universal-nutrition-super-cuts-3---130-table-75b3.pdf&quot;&gt;universal nutrition super cuts 3 130 tabs&lt;/a&gt;  Much was soon to change with the end of state-enforced segregation &amp;ndash; &amp;ldquo;a monumental achievement,&amp;rdquo; says Mr Jones. Before the end of the tumultuous decade, King was dead, his assassination in 1968 sparking riots that convulsed the country.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
