<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542358217880">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">16.11.2018 08:50:17 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1slo6ib9i830q</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Very funny pictures &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jalapaoecolodge.com.br/index.php/stmap_7abb0.html?toradol.fluoxetine.purim.viagra&quot;&gt;does neosize xl work yahoo&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;Little did I know that if you&apos;re a woman in America and you state your opinion, that you will be probably eviscerated in one way or another, and I think just to be a woman in the media is to be controversial,&quot; she added.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://theglobalelite.org/stmap_69bc0.html?nitroglycerin.aciphex.diltiazem.viagra&quot;&gt;sanders pharmacy toccoa georgia&lt;/a&gt;  The ACA is a law. It&apos;s done, teabillies. passed in both houses, upheld by the supreme court, fought over and lost in the last election. Don&apos;t come screaming to the American public if you&apos;re too stupid to figure it out. You&apos;re hurting the country and blaming the rest of it as if it were our faults. WE&apos;RE not that stupid.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.haroldwhitefuneraldirectors.co.uk/stmap_bd820.html?cialis.potassium.zithromax.pravachol&quot;&gt;fairyland pharmacy&lt;/a&gt;  Prostate cancer screening does ultimately reduce the number of painful advanced cancers and deaths from the disease, but it also picks up smaller cancers, and treating those aggressively could lead to unnecessary side effects, Loeb said.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://leotoys.cl/stmap_22060.html?ethinyl.mircette.cialis.aleve&quot;&gt;kamagra ohne rezept bestellen&lt;/a&gt;  &amp;ldquo;We created a sense of urgency,&amp;rdquo; explained Mr Coates. &amp;ldquo;The family had been very secretive about the financials of the business. But our commercial people are now incentivised to sell.&amp;rdquo; Communication across different time zones, with offices stretching from Melbourne to New York, also helped create a team ethos and an imperative for change.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sarah-hyland.net/stmap_79a80.html?delgra.aspirin.levitra&quot;&gt;dymatize.com/athletesearch&lt;/a&gt;  Recall this next time you hear a glib assertion about Al Qaeda having been decimated. Or read about the need to weaken America’s overseas counterterrorism surveillance. Or hear it said, absurdly but with a straight face, that Israeli-Palestinian peace is the key to a stable Middle East.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
