<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1543404861064">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">28.11.2018 11:34:21 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.ptndp50fhcac</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Yes, I love it! &lt;a href=&quot;http://starbizzcon.com/gabapentin-300-mg-capsule-uses-45db.pdf#sniff&quot;&gt;gabapentin drug abuse&lt;/a&gt;  Titled &quot;A fly on the wall in Cupertino?&quot; the video depicts a series of fictional meetings held at Apple’s Cupertino, Calif., headquarters sometime in early 2013. During the meetings, two executives come up with various pitches for the new iPhone, directed at two executives whose faces remains obscured but seem to resemble Apple design chief Jony Ive and the late Steve Jobs.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://tynerblain.com/blog/doxycycline-dosage-drugscom-ef2c.pdf#mania&quot;&gt;doxycycline dosage drugs.com&lt;/a&gt;  Admitting he&apos;d never get away from it though, he went on: &amp;ldquo;There isn&amp;rsquo;t. It&amp;rsquo;s just my face. I have to accept the fact that my face is going to remind people of Harry because I played that character. If I try to avoid being expressive in that same way, all I&amp;rsquo;ll do is stop being expressive, and I won&amp;rsquo;t be any farther away from that character.&amp;rdquo;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://starbizzcon.com/general-mills-yoplait-ouija-board-45db.pdf&quot;&gt;general mills yoplait ouist&lt;/a&gt;  But since Summers emerged as a lead contender for the jobthis summer, his history as a consultant to large financialinstitutions including Citigroup has fueled debate among criticsand lawmakers about his suitability for the top Fed job.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.greenlam.com/index.php/med-infouz-7741.pdf#interbase&quot;&gt;drugdelivery-congress.com&lt;/a&gt;  DC Comics won’t be Domo’s only ally during Comic Con…get ready for another team up with Dark Horse for the limited edition introduction of “Caveman Domo,” which retails for $9 and is part of the company’s successful Qee line of 2” figures.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://pixelbedlam.co.uk/levitra-cena-beograd-65ef.pdf&quot;&gt;levitra kopen in belgie&lt;/a&gt;  CNN, which has averaged 592,000 viewers between 9 a.m. and 4p.m. during the Zimmerman trial according to Nielsen, placedsecond in that same time behind Fox News Channel, which hasattracted about 1 million viewers on average. Only in the finalweek has CNN been able to surpass HLN in viewers.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
