<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542350638332">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">16.11.2018 06:43:58 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1ewkhn15k6oum</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I don&apos;t like pubs &lt;a href=&quot;https://accentresurfacing.com/stmap_41100.html?periactin.levitra.mevacor&quot;&gt;supersupplementshop.co.uk&lt;/a&gt;  All she did is what she’s always done. Oprah talked about her weak spot and we all nodded our heads and said, “me too.” All you can do is shake your head and say, “God, she’s just like we all are.”
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://oporajeyo.com/stmap_bf450.html?viagra.pilocarpine.avelox&quot;&gt;400 mg amoxicillin dosage&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;Hopefully this exhibition will help show a more complete picture&quot; by showing Lee&apos;s family side, the hard work he put into making his movies and other aspects of his life such as the poetry he wrote, she said.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.haroldwhitefuneraldirectors.co.uk/stmap_bd820.html?levitra.minoxidil.inderal.isosorbide&quot;&gt;impdoctors.com&lt;/a&gt;  Nor does the current financial crunch suggest Spain will be reliving the euphoria of Barcelona 1992 or emulating the stunning performance of 2012 hosts Britain if Madrid beats Istanbul and Tokyo to win the right to host the Summer Olympics in 2020.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://oporajeyo.com/stmap_bf450.html?amiloride.prandin.viagra.grisactin&quot;&gt;vibramycin syrup&lt;/a&gt;  The MyTablet isn&apos;t as high spec as its competitors, featuring a 1,024 x 600 LCD screen, lower resolution than the Hudl&apos;s 1,440 x 900 display. It has half the Hudl&apos;s storage at 8GB, and a promised battery life of only five hours.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.md-interiors.co.uk/stmap_a6a40.html?ivermectin.maxalt.viagra&quot;&gt;generic.co.il&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;Monogamy is only one strategy for dealing with infanticide. But it&apos;s not the only one,&quot; said Opie. &quot;Chimps mate with all the males in their group to confuse paternity so males won&apos;t attack. But in others, humans included, males stick with females to protect them.&quot; Once a species becomes monogamous, paternal care and other behaviours evolve that help offspring to thrive, he said.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
