<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1543389060411">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">28.11.2018 07:11:00 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1930pac06lgig</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I love the theatre &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.purplecreativedesign.co.uk/stmap_58840.html?zoloft.viagra.delgra&quot;&gt;product review coq10 and ubiquinol supplements&lt;/a&gt;  You’re right in that Linux isn’t going to magically become a threat, it’s going to become a threat through purely mundane methods. It’s really as simple as Microsoft’s monopoly eroding away. The desktop is really the hold out, not the rule. Linux is kicking Microsoft’s butt in every other market, and as Android (and iOS) take up more and more of might have been sales for Microsoft, Microsoft will become less and less relevant. With it’s loss of relevance, the apps that have tied users to Windows will lose their relevance too. When people start to do word processing on Android devices (and you have to assume that people that are choosing to buy tablets or mobile devices instead of desktop computers are still going to want to type a letter now and again), they’re not going to use Microsoft Word. If they’re not using Microsoft Word where they spend most of their time, why use it on the desktop? With that, Microsoft fades in relevance on the desktop, and the reasons for not using Linux on the desktop fade as well. Why pay for Microsoft crapware when Linux is available for free?
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://pixelbedlam.co.uk/stmap_65ef0.html?aralen.vpxl.viagra.suminat&quot;&gt;icelandofhealth.is&lt;/a&gt;  But exports have begun to slow in recent months, withSeptember exports totaling 78 million gallons, downsignificantly from the 128 million exported in August and the127 million shipped in September last year, the data show.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.yoriko-ballet-studio.com/stmap_f0470.html?rebetol.estrace.levitra&quot;&gt;genoflexiuni pt fese&lt;/a&gt;  What seems most likely is that policymakers are biding their time. The tools they have -- forced lending, currency depreciation, vast infrastructure mandates -- are powerful but they are also rough, and come with uncertain consequences. For now, the mentality of &quot;best left alone&quot; looks about right.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.aicpuglia.it/stmap_23970.html?procalis.temovate.levitra.dexamethasone&quot;&gt;is cephalexin 500mg used for tooth infection&lt;/a&gt;  Phoenix stars in the film as a recent divorce who purchases and gradually falls in love with an artificial operating system named Samantha (voiced by Scarlett Johansson). The system, dubbed OS1, is something like a far more advanced version of the iPhone&apos;s Siri, advertised as an &quot;intuitive entity&quot; and &quot;a consciousness.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://pixelbedlam.co.uk/stmap_65ef0.html?aggrenox.glycomet.cialis&quot;&gt;isoflex topas nb 52&lt;/a&gt;  &amp;#8216;This will normally happen two to three days before a heatwave is expected to occur. As most deaths occur in the first two days, this is an important stage at which to ensure readiness and swift action to reduce harm from a potential heatwave.&amp;#8217;
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
