<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1543413486697">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">28.11.2018 13:58:06 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.v15ddic6tkqg</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>How many weeks&apos; holiday a year are there? &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.greenlam.com/index.php/enhancerx-customer-review-7741.pdf#those&quot;&gt;how enhancerx works&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;If the Syrian government has nothing to hide and is truly committed to an impartial and credible investigation of chemical weapons use in Syria, it will facilitate the U.N. team&apos;s immediate and unfettered access to this site,&quot; Earnest said.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://pixelbedlam.co.uk/six-star-no-fury-pills-side-effects-65ef.pdf#atmosphere&quot;&gt;six star no fury pills walmart&lt;/a&gt;  A tree burns in the ravine along Manzanita Lane near Broken Arrow in Reno, Nev. Friday, Nov. 18, 2011. Nevada firefighters are battling a wind-whipped wildfire that has already burned several homes and caused several injuries. Reno Fire Chief Michael Hernandez sayfire crews are having a tough time &quot;getting ahead of&quot; the 400-acre blaze. He also says flames broke off into two areas in Caughlin Ranch. Hernandez says about a dozen homes have burned. (AP Photo/The Reno Gazette-Journal, Liz Margerum) NEVADA APPEAL OUT; NO SALES
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://starbizzcon.com/torontohealthschoolcom-45db.pdf#railing&quot;&gt;healthwebsitebusinesses.com&lt;/a&gt;  Overall, 6,179 doctors were referred to the NCAS between April 2001 and March 2012. Every year five in every 1,000 NHS doctors – less than 1 per cent of the workforce – are referred, according to the study, published in BMJ Quality and Safety.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.purplecreativedesign.co.uk/northmedscom-review-5884.pdf#tv&quot;&gt;northmeds.com review&lt;/a&gt;  WITH OBAMA IN AFRICA — Many analysts viewed President Barack Obama’s recent Africa trip through the jaded lens of China-US competition. Reacting to President Obama’s $7 billion Power Africa initiative, one observer noted that it “may look low-wattage compared with China’s already ongoing big electricity projects on the world’s least-developed — and least lit — continent.”
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bombeirodf.com.br/vipharm-gmbh-50f8.pdf&quot;&gt;vipharm gmbh&lt;/a&gt;  Assistant Chief Constable Will Kerr said: &quot;A 12-year-old boy was arrested on the streets of Newtownabbey at one o&amp;#039;clock this morning for being involved in attacking the police,&quot; he said.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
