<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542689427576">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">20.11.2018 04:50:27 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1lpc19pc2g5ht</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Punk not dead  &lt;a href=&quot;https://digital-matchbox.com/prostin-dose-pda-5522.pdf#pattern&quot;&gt;prostin lek&lt;/a&gt;  The English tongue, in all its majesty, has the paradoxical habit of producing words with diametrically opposite definitions. To sanction means both to allow and to disallow, for example; while to cleave is at once (1) to separate one thing violently from another, and (2) to stick to something like a limpet.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://newscvm.com/order-cialis-professional-e9bb.pdf&quot;&gt;drug cialis online&lt;/a&gt;  The Socialist president, whose 2014 national budget nextmonth will focus on curbing spending, vowed to turn back what hecalled a &apos;lost decade&apos; of conservative rule in which some700,000 jobs fled domestic industries.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mikasafloors.com/xtrasizenl-review-bdec.pdf&quot;&gt;xtrasize.nl&lt;/a&gt;  One incident does not represent a sudden failure in quality control. That&amp;#8217;s a 737 &amp;#8211; not a recent model airplane. You don&amp;#8217;t know how many hours that aircraft has logged nor how thoroughly it was inspected. This will all come out in the investigation.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lovemycase.com/flexmedindbr-f2c2.pdf#avenue&quot;&gt;acesse http //www.digimed.ind.br/br/pedidos/&lt;/a&gt;  These were adult heart surgery, bowel cancer resection (removing part of the colon or rectum), oesophagectomy (removing the oesophagus) and gastrectomy (taking out all or part of the stomach), and hip fracture surgery.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mcmpovos.com/elite-test-360-reviews-62bd.pdf#error&quot;&gt;elite test 360 complaints&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;It changes the playing field for us,&quot; said Tom Gaitens, former Florida director of FreedomWorks, a political action committee that has spent millions of dollars to help tea party candidates. &quot;The most powerful thing we have as a movement is our feet and our vote.&quot;
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
