<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542570901601">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 19:55:01 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.8l568n9f23sy</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>What do you want to do when you&apos;ve finished? &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mcmpovos.com/maxipatch-uk-62bd.pdf#render&quot;&gt;maxipatch uk&lt;/a&gt;  AMSTERDAM, Sept 13 (Reuters) - It would be the envy offorgers: a technology that can mint near-perfect reproductionsof Vincent Van Gogh&apos;s paintings at a rate of three a day, withdifferences only experts can detect.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://accentresurfacing.com/acheter-deltasone-en-ligne-4110.pdf#cooler&quot;&gt;acheter deltasone en ligne&lt;/a&gt;  TUESDAY, Aug. 20 (HealthDay News) -- Highlighting the harm caused by bullying, a new study finds the effects of childhood bullying last into adulthood and can lead to problems such as illness, job difficulties and poor relationships with others.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://sjofartsbygningen.no/alpha-max-10-pure-no2-7ef0.pdf#rain&quot;&gt;alpha max 10 amazon&lt;/a&gt;  KPMG, which previously forecast self-driving cars hitting dealers in 2019 with a more developed infrastructure in 2025, found consumer interest jumped significantly if the car included the ability to turn that technology on or off, and it meant significantly lower commute times due to dedicated highway lanes. Those surveyed were willing to pay a premium of about 15 percent, or almost $4,000 on a $25,000 vehicle equipped with such technology.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.chris-cancercommunity.com/where-to-buy-rogaine-extra-strength-b01a.pdf#oxygen&quot;&gt;is it safe for a woman to use men&amp;#39s rogaine&lt;/a&gt;  The euro was flat on the day, changing hands at$1.3472. Support at its August high of $1.3453 held throughoutthe Asian session, even as the European unit was pressured by adisappointing German survey overnight.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.chris-cancercommunity.com/kamagra-elado-debrecen-b01a.pdf#cling&quot;&gt;kamagra nasl kullanlr&lt;/a&gt;  He&apos;s currently on his Believe world tour, where he&apos;s performing on the Asian leg until Oct. 12. Up next for the pop star is the Latin and South America, followed by several dates in Australia at the end of the year.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
