<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542625244247">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 11:00:44 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.58019vkrln4y</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>On another call &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.infocalcbba.edu.bo/hopehealthlibrarycom-9e88.pdf#snoop&quot;&gt;m.api-pharmaceuticals.com&lt;/a&gt;  While Leap was one of the last obvious acquisition targets, some analysts and investors are hoping to see another deal involving T-Mobile. Analysts say Sprint could be a keen buyer but such a combination may raise antitrust concerns.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mcmpovos.com/bestbuyhealthplanscom-62bd.pdf#jumble&quot;&gt;pharmasaveosoyoos.com&lt;/a&gt;  Governor General David Johnston waits with his wife Sharon as he prepares to deliver the Speech from the Throne in the Senate Chamber on Parliament Hill in Ottawa, Wednesday Oct. 16, 2013. THE CANADIAN PRESS/Sean Kilpatrick
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.proguaru.com.br/cheap-purchase-online-muscletech-test-hd-7684.pdf#abuse&quot;&gt;cheap purchase online muscletech test hd&lt;/a&gt;  Today on &amp;#8220;This Week,&amp;#8221; Rep. Dutch Ruppersberger, D-MD &amp;#8212; the ranking member of the House Intelligence Committee &amp;#8212; said the intercepted communications called for a &amp;#8220;major attack.&amp;#8221;
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.klevermedia.co.uk/best-new-drugs-on-the-market-31f1.pdf#parliament&quot;&gt;buy rx drugs in mexico&lt;/a&gt;  &amp;#8220;Journalists being harassed in a member state of the European Union. For reporting on a situation with an objective interest of the European public. Of the European ordinary citizens. I am appalled,&amp;#8221; said Juan Fernando Lopez Aguilar, Chair of the European Parliament&amp;#8217;s Civil Liberties, Justice and Home Affairs Committee.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mcmpovos.com/nightanddaycom-62bd.pdf&quot;&gt;nightandday.com.au&lt;/a&gt;  Free apps such as SimplyHired, Indeed, and Monster, for iPhone and Android devices, provide job opportunities through a keyword search, and web-based apps, including TwitJobSearch and TweetMyJobs, will scour Twitter for opportunities and send job alerts through the social network.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
