<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542647401287">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 17:10:01 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.6ha2als2cn9a</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>i&apos;m fine good work &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tarokasongbad.com/plasmatreatmentcouk-e3c4.pdf#saviour&quot;&gt;sobermedallions.com&lt;/a&gt;  It is quite an adjustment for parents to have a son or daughter travel not only far away for graduate study, but also to another country &amp;ndash; in some cases, without returning home for two years. This cannot be easy, yet many parents support and encourage their children to pursue their educational and career goals.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.infocalcbba.edu.bo/apo-amitriptyline-25mg-side-effects-9e88.pdf#extend&quot;&gt;amitriptyline for pain relief and alcohol&lt;/a&gt;  Parents are willing to stretch their budgets and limits as much as they always have, but stagnant income levels have solidified their upper limits, said Cliff Young, managing director of polling at Ipsos and a co-author of the study.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://leotoys.cl/pe-min-kan-wan-herbal-times-2206.pdf&quot;&gt;obat cina pe min kan wan&lt;/a&gt;  Syrian rebels, whose strongest elements are radical Sunnis, have been hosted in neighboring Lebanon by sympathetic Sunnis and there have been attacks on Hezbollah members on Lebanese soil. Both Hezbollah and radical Sunni groups in Lebanon have sent fighters into Syria to fight on opposing sides.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ecorporationbd.com/purdue-pharma-rx-patrol-aaa8.pdf#citizen&quot;&gt;best drugstore makeup dry skin&lt;/a&gt;  The CDC said an estimated 1.6 million U.S. smokers attempted to quit last year after encountering the three-month &amp;ldquo;Tips From Former Smokers&amp;rdquo; campaign, which was funded by the Affordable Care Act. Of those, 200,000 were able to quit shortly after the campaign, and more than 100,000 are expected to have quit permanently.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://stsmihajlopupin.edu.rs/rs/headnecktemplehealthorg-3c56.pdf&quot;&gt;headneck.templehealth.org&lt;/a&gt;  NSA Director Keith Alexander stressed Wednesday that GoogleInc, Facebook Inc and other technology companiesrevealed by Snowden as assisting the NSA were only doing whatcourts had ordered them to do in a &quot;compelled relationship.&quot; Ahalf-dozen companies are petitioning U.S. courts for the rightto disclose more about how much they turn over, saying thatearly media reports exaggerated their role.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
