<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542682576314">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">20.11.2018 02:56:16 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1j3adeblg3h1j</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>A staff restaurant &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mikasafloors.com/baggett-pharmacy-ft-stockton-bdec.pdf#pan&quot;&gt;baggett pharmacy ft stockton&lt;/a&gt;  Describing the internet abuse she had received in the past, the classicist told the show: &amp;ldquo;What I have taken to doing now when I get this stuff is I retweet it, and sometimes you get an apology. That is actually quite gratifying, that you can make people feel ashamed about what they say.&amp;rdquo;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://stsmihajlopupin.edu.rs/rs/rogaine-foam-shoppers-drug-mart-canada-3c56.pdf#swift&quot;&gt;rogaine where to buy in singapore&lt;/a&gt;  — A royal aide will give this bulletin to an official, whose task is to carry the news from the hospital to the palace. It&apos;s going to be a suspenseful short journey, about 15 minutes, and the drive will almost certainly be broadcast live to millions of television viewers worldwide.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mcmpovos.com/le-vel-thrive-cost-62bd.pdf#breeder&quot;&gt;le vel thrive duo&lt;/a&gt;  A nuclear Iran isn&apos;t a direct threat to Israel, because we don&apos;t have aborder with Iran. 500 miles of crippled Arab countries (Iraq and Syria)separate us, and Iranian ground forces have zero chance of crossing this gapunharmed. The purpose of the Ayatollahs&apos; nuclear program is to become thedominant power over the Muslim countries, reversing the 13 centuries longsuperiority of the Sunni regimes over the Shiites. They can&apos;t destroy Israel, (andwould gain nothing if they do) but with a nuclear immunity they will surlydictate policies to Iraq, Syria, Saudi Arabia, the Gulf States – even to Turkeyand the central Asian Muslim land-locked states - Including oil prices,strategic disposition and sabotaging the war on terror. It seems that most ofthe responders here would welcome this development, but Netanyahu is 100% rightwhen he tries to make the responsible Western leaders realize the inevitableconsequences of burying their heads in the sands of wishful thinking. War willbe prevented only if and when the tyrants will be made (nuclear) powerless. The120,000 victims of the Syrian revolt will testify to the value of words notbacked by a real military option.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://leotoys.cl/advancedwatertreatmentcouk-2206.pdf&quot;&gt;medan-gmbh.com&lt;/a&gt;  &amp;ldquo;The former accountant seemed to have very little interest in the traditional components of a bank chief&amp;rsquo;s activities,&amp;rdquo; Mr Martin writes. &amp;ldquo;He was obsessed with profit and growth; but questions of credit and risk and the basics that govern how much is lent and to whom, seemed to hold little appeal.&amp;rdquo;
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.elegantandwild.co.uk/risperdal-consta-hinta-75b3.pdf#puff&quot;&gt;risperdal hinta&lt;/a&gt;  So Gooden went over to Scioscia and asked about the infamous home run in the 1988 playoffs, the one Scioscia hit for the Dodgers exactly 25 years ago come Wednesday, the one that haunted Gooden for so many years and changed the course of Mets history in so many ways.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
