<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1543398754374">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">28.11.2018 09:52:34 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1p0qzpqgcurn3</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Have you seen any good films recently? &lt;a href=&quot;http://starbizzcon.com/musica-tema-de-yasmin-de-corpo-e-alma-45db.pdf#partial&quot;&gt;tema de yasmin na novela de corpo e alma&lt;/a&gt;  The FEC noted that the term &quot;spouse&quot; is not defined under its rules and is typically defined as a person legally married under state law. It said same-sex couples married under state law should be considered spouses under FEC regulations.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://oktandrammen.no/drammen-ny/essentials-pharmacy-london-e52c.pdf&quot;&gt;essentials pharmacy brackenfell&lt;/a&gt;  The question of how things could be worse for the Cardinals is answered during Carpenter&apos;s at-bat, as Jon Jay steps into the on-deck circle in Beltran&apos;s place. In the bottom of the inning, Jay goes to center field, and Robinson moves to right. Beltran&apos;s night is over, certainly as a result of his collision with the wall while robbing Ortiz&apos;s bid for the grand slam.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://pixelbedlam.co.uk/kinney-drugs-photo-center-prices-65ef.pdf&quot;&gt;best drugstore concealer sweat&lt;/a&gt;  The disaster caused 11 deaths and triggered the largest U.S. offshore oil spill following the rupture of the Macondo oil well, which was 65 percent owned by BP Plc. Halliburton had earlier provided cementing services to help seal the well.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bombeirodf.com.br/sumatriptan-fiyat-50f8.pdf&quot;&gt;sumatriptan generico precio&lt;/a&gt;  Manning&apos;s conviction on five espionage and 14 other charges poses a potential problem for Assange since the severity of the judgment, which carries a jail sentence of up to 136 years, might deter would-be whistleblowers, the lifeblood of Assange&apos;s organization.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ssvoverath.de/secnidazole-rxlist-c3db.pdf#bishop&quot;&gt;secnidazole rxlist&lt;/a&gt;  3. &quot;There are no legal arguments against gay marriage.&quot; There are many legal arguments against the radical claims of homosexual extremists and lawsuits against homosexual marriage are not going to end ever. It is very likely that the next major legal action that will be taken will be a Constitutional amendment to define marriage as between one man and one woman. Legal action is continuous and ongoing. So this argument is obviously false and does not acknowledge reality.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
