<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542616365586">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 08:32:45 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.3i0xqm3qusft</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>An envelope &lt;a href=&quot;https://oporajeyo.com/prostalobium-capsules-bf45.pdf#blocks&quot;&gt;hilde hemmes prostalobium plus&lt;/a&gt;  KABUL, Oct 11 (Reuters) - U.S. Secretary of State John Kerryand Afghan President Hamid Karzai narrowed differences ininitial talks on Friday on terms for a future U.S. militarypresence in Afghanistan after 2014, a U.S. official said.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.casadeadoracao.com.br/index.php/bpi-krill-collagenes-bac9.pdf#meaningless&quot;&gt;bpi krill collagenes&lt;/a&gt;  A high court in South Korea court ruled last year thatregularly paid bonuses should be counted as part of a workers&apos;&quot;base pay&quot;, which is used to calculate overtime and pensionpayments. The supreme court is currently reviewing the ruling.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://muv.asia/wwwmedicineusaskcaadmissions-bf28.pdf&quot;&gt;www.medicine.usask.ca/psychiatry/clinical/child/forms.php&lt;/a&gt;  The Association for Financial Markets in Europe said top BNPParibas banker Frédéric Janbon would succeed its chairman, Gaëlde Boissard, in September. Janbon began his career with France&apos;sNo.1 listed bank in 1988, trading options and swaps. He has heldvarious positions in derivatives sales and trading in London,Paris and Tokyo.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.casadeadoracao.com.br/index.php/micro-bionicle-bac9.pdf&quot;&gt;micro bionic hearing aid&lt;/a&gt;  Lone has joined the British lender as its regional head forglobal corporates for Middle East, North Africa and Pakistan(MENAP), a Standard Chartered spokesman said in an emailedstatement on Tuesday.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.wychwoodcabinetmakers.co.uk/glendale-medicalcom-e0f9.pdf#deprive&quot;&gt;swisherinternalmedicine.com&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;The courts have just affirmed facts that too many New Yorkers know to be true: Under the Bloomberg administration … millions of innocent New Yorkers — overwhelmingly young men of color — have been illegally stopped,&quot; de Blasio said. &quot;The overuse and misuse of stop-and-frisk hasn&apos;t made New York a safer city, it has only served to drive police and community further apart.&quot;
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
