<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542359186796">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">16.11.2018 09:06:26 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.j1hxvx9f4bn0</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Could I order a new chequebook, please? &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.md-interiors.co.uk/stmap_a6a40.html?levitra.satibo.b12&quot;&gt;edex and alcohol&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;Our goal is always to try to find the right balance between protecting the security and the privacy of our citizens and this work is going to continue as well as our very close consultations with our friends here in France,&quot; Kerry said.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ascfinancialadvisers.co.uk/stmap_55530.html?diarex.naprelan.levitra.adapalene&quot;&gt;medikamente.apotheken.de&lt;/a&gt;  She still has ways of keeping the old country alive. Sitting down in the place next door, I notice she&amp;rsquo;s carrying a musical instrument. &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m learning how to play the oud,&amp;rdquo; she tells me, a traditional instrument similar to a lute. &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m being taught by an 85-year-old who has been playing since he was 17.&amp;rdquo; She met him by chance on a plane and they became friends. &amp;ldquo;He&amp;rsquo;s very cool,&amp;rdquo; she says, adding, &amp;ldquo;he&amp;rsquo;s got some stories to tell. He&amp;rsquo;s a bit like my father.&amp;rdquo;
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.klevermedia.co.uk/stmap_31f10.html?tadora.ornidazole.calcium.cialis&quot;&gt;harga cytotec pill malaysia&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;Perhaps men in this situation feel guilty for not doing their fair share or perhaps the unequal division of household tasks creates tension between them and their partner?&quot; the researchers posit.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.elegantandwild.co.uk/stmap_75b30.html?crixivan.amiodarone.prograf.cialis&quot;&gt;price chopper pharmacy oswego&lt;/a&gt;  Olimpia coach Ever Almeida, a club legend as their former goalkeeper, is not thrilled that their first-leg lead is being attributed mainly to the force of tradition. &quot;We won with football,&quot; he said, &quot;and not because of the importance of our shirt.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dollingstownfc.com/stmap_68650.html?viagra.zoloft.pentoxifylline&quot;&gt;rapidlab.biz&lt;/a&gt;  Years of tax breaks for the wealthy, a minimum wage untethered from the inflation rate and electoral districts drawn to maximize political polarization have reduced the quality of life for all but a small fraction of Americans and imperiled the nation’s standing as “a real superpower,” he said.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
