<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542541428011">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 11:43:48 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1wd0rvnqfdr4u</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>perfect design thanks &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lovemycase.com/promedsoftwarecom-f2c2.pdf#growing&quot;&gt;truecarehealthmd.com&lt;/a&gt;  Gossip maven Liz Smith, a former roommate, toasted her as “the girl who taught me my first Yiddish and who I used to call ‘Sam Spade, master detective’ because she always knew where the bodies were buried.”
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sarah-hyland.net/sildenafil-drugscom-79a8.pdf#abide&quot;&gt;drugs.com app&lt;/a&gt;  Josef Janning, with the German Council on Foreign Relations, says: &amp;#8220;She has often been compared to Margaret Thatcher in Europe, portrayed as someone cold. That is not the image that Germans have of her. Their pet nickname for her is &amp;#8216;Mutti&amp;#8217; &amp;#8211; someone close to us who cares for us.&amp;#8221;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://stsmihajlopupin.edu.rs/rs/shinya-koso-night-diet-3c56.pdf#leaflet&quot;&gt;shinya koso night diet instructions&lt;/a&gt;  The president has spent all or part of nine days on this picturesque Massachusetts island, mostly keeping a low profile while renting a house in Chilmark, a property valued at $7 million. He spoke publicly just once, condemning violence in Egypt.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.proguaru.com.br/djaglobalpharmacom-7684.pdf&quot;&gt;holderdrug.com&lt;/a&gt;  It is a common story, according to research from FidelityInvestments, which found that 4 in 10 couples who aren&apos;t retireddisagree about the lifestyle they expect in retirement. Morethan a third don&apos;t agree on where to live or have no idea wherethey want to live. One-third disagree about whether they willcontinue to work in retirement, according to a Fidelity surveyreleased at the end of September.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.casadeadoracao.com.br/index.php/lifetime-direct-medical-costs-of-childhood-obesity-bac9.pdf#entire&quot;&gt;direct medical supply weslaco tx&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;Slim and KPN know they will never get as good a price forthis asset as they will get right now,&quot; the person said. &quot;Thecompetitive environment in Germany is getting worse ... E-Plusis in an unsustainable position in Germany: too small, too fewspectrum holdings, and inability to invest to keep up with theother players.&quot;
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
