<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1543406258636">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">28.11.2018 11:57:38 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.pqhve0jq8jtg</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I didn&apos;t go to university &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bombeirodf.com.br/medicon-village-inspira-restaurang-50f8.pdf&quot;&gt;medicon village lund map&lt;/a&gt;  A member of the Sunni Islamist Ahrar al-Sham said its fighters had killed no civilians in the offensive. &quot;If someone uses a weapon against you, you have to fight them. If they do not, you must not kill them,&quot; said Abu Muhammed al-Husseini, the 30-year-old head of Ahrar al-Sham&apos;s political office in Raqqa.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://public-admin.co.uk/comprx-shirts-3c8d.pdf#raspberry&quot;&gt;comprx sp2&lt;/a&gt;  Cory was just outed for exchanging tweets with Lynsie Lee, a stripper from a vegan strip joint. No, not as in strip steak, but as in nonmeat eating, nonfeather-leather-wearing strippers. (Isn’t a stripper without a boa like a ballerina without a tutu?)
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.purplecreativedesign.co.uk/prix-mobicarte-orange-tabac-5884.pdf&quot;&gt;prix mobicarte orange tabac&lt;/a&gt;  The Australian Football League&apos;s championship match is scheduled for Saturday between the Hawthorn Hawks and Fremantle Dockers at the 159-year-old Melbourne Cricket Ground, with a crowd around 100,000 expected. The game is the climax of Australia&apos;s most watched and attended sport. By Dennis Passa. MOVED: 825 words.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://pixelbedlam.co.uk/ks-drugscom-65ef.pdf&quot;&gt;mednhealth.com&lt;/a&gt;  On Tuesday Saudi Arabia and the United Arab Emirates eachpledged $4 billion in aid to Egypt, where the army overthrew theMuslim Brotherhood&apos;s Mursi a week ago after huge streetdemonstrations against the elected president.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sensors.co.uk/tmedsie-9874.pdf#retained&quot;&gt;healthforhealth.com&lt;/a&gt;  “When things get tough in your personal life, the first thing you want to do is get back to some kind of normalcy,” Justin Tuck said. “For him, football is some kind of normalcy. Hopefully, as a football team, we can give him some kind of joy.”
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
