<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542558025533">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 16:20:25 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.19c675euhbpr2</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Do you know each other?  &lt;a href=&quot;http://sjofartsbygningen.no/gippokrat-clinic-amsterdam-7ef0.pdf&quot;&gt;dr.max pharmacy chain&lt;/a&gt;  The solar panel maker said on Thursday it would offer 3.8million American depositary shares (ADS) priced at $16.25 eachto expand its manufacturing capacity, develop solar projects andfund working capital.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.anupamdebashisroy.com/viagra-100-mg-costo-in-farmacia-f2ef.pdf&quot;&gt;viagra for sale no prescription uk&lt;/a&gt;  Who said cereal is only for breakfast? Try chicken tenders dipped in homemade batter, rolled in frosted flakes and deep fried.  This Frosted Flake chicken on-a-stick comes in at approximately 600 calories.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.greenlamindustries.com/blog/rhythm-108-hazelnut-praline-0bae.pdf&quot;&gt;rhythm 108&lt;/a&gt;  The trial testimony ran through years of vicious slayings and casual brutality. It featured testimony from corrupt FBI agents, admitted murderers and the children they made fatherless. Fear among gun-owning jurors prompted some to make sure their weapons were loaded before bed.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.md-interiors.co.uk/zoloft-reducing-dosage-side-effects-a6a4.pdf&quot;&gt;zoloft reducing dosage side effects&lt;/a&gt;  While nearly 96 percent of American youth between 15 and 24 -- so called &quot;millennials&quot; -- are digital natives, that figure is behind South Korea (99.6 percent,) Japan (99.5 percent) and several European countries including Finland, Denmark and the Netherlands, the study found.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.greenlamindustries.com/blog/steroidsworldpl-0bae.pdf&quot;&gt;steroidsworld.pl&lt;/a&gt;  After first trying to stop the operation internally, ATF Agent John Dodson went to Congress and eventually the media following the death of Border Patrol Agent Brian Terry in December 2010. Two guns found at the murder scene were sold through the ATF operation. 
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
