<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542715072677">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">20.11.2018 11:57:52 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1a6i4k09qq1bd</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Could you tell me my balance, please? &lt;a href=&quot;http://stsmihajlopupin.edu.rs/rs/first-responder-vehicle-medical-kit-3c56.pdf&quot;&gt;define vehicle medical&lt;/a&gt;  A Scotland Yard spokesman said: &quot;We are urgently trying to contact the complainant so we can discuss with her the issues that she is raising on social network sites, to once again explain our approach and tactics in this investigation to provide both answers for her and clarity. A huge amount of evidence, including hundreds of tweets, has been captured by officers and thoroughly examined. This has been a complex and large investigation that has involved the examination of hundreds of messages sent on Twitter. A number of people have so far been arrested in connection with the complaint, and remain on bail.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.weymouthskatepark.co.uk/norfloxacina-precio-generico-6ae3.pdf#futile&quot;&gt;como comprar norfloxacino&lt;/a&gt;  Jackson&apos;s lawyer, Gloria Allred, who I have known for years and greatly admire, said Filner needs to stop &quot;treating women as pieces of meat.&quot; She said his video apology was inadequate and that his statement that &quot;I need help&quot; is not sufficient. &quot;Do you need help to know that making vile and disgusting sexual comments is wrong?&quot; she asked.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.anupamdebashisroy.com/lloyds-pharmacy-propecia-cost-f2ef.pdf&quot;&gt;lloyds pharmacy propecia cost&lt;/a&gt;  Goldberg still appears to be wrestling with the question of what women want &amp;ndash; perhaps because he never asked, or asked, but didn&apos;t listen closely to the answer. What do women want? Money and power, Mr. Goldberg. Same thing you want. And $100 a day to write for a site launched by someone with an offensive and wildly outdated view of women doesn&apos;t meet the standard.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://lemcasesorias.com/index.php/costa-rica-pharmacy-prices-83f5.pdf#fanny&quot;&gt;declaring prescription drugs australia customs&lt;/a&gt;  Republican bigots- they just can&apos;t stop inserting themselves into the private lives of others. They want to make laws to force their way upon everyone else. Anti-freedom, anti-choice, and anti-American.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://digital-matchbox.com/tissue-magic-yogyakarta-5522.pdf&quot;&gt;tissue magic di apotek&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;We can be pretty satisfied with how it&apos;s gone so far,&quot; the Red Bull driver said. &quot;The car runs good on any type of track and I&apos;ve had only one DNF (did not finish). Having more points than last year at this time can only be positive.&quot;
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
