<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1543394753326">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">28.11.2018 08:45:53 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.8kcffhhziwn9</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Sorry, I ran out of credit &lt;a href=&quot;http://oktandrammen.no/drammen-ny/medmounteu-e52c.pdf&quot;&gt;vacatures.mednet.nl&lt;/a&gt;  Sources familiar with the matter told Reuters earlier thismonth that one of New York City&apos;s biggest landlords, ThorEquities LLC, had raised its offer to buy the Empire StateBuilding to $1.4 billion in cash, hoping to trump the plan toroll the landmark property into a trust.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://pixelbedlam.co.uk/pemsdoctorsacademyorguk-65ef.pdf&quot;&gt;completepharmaceutics.com&lt;/a&gt;  In April 2012, Indonesia&apos;s government borrowed money for 10years for a record low 3.375 percent, only about 1.8 percentagepoints more than the U.S. government was paying. The same month,Korean electronics giant Samsung Electronics wasable to borrow $1 billion at 1.75 percent.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.yoriko-ballet-studio.com/menarini-avanafil-spedra-f047.pdf&quot;&gt;avanafil caratteristiche&lt;/a&gt;  Construction spending in August was lifted by a 0.4 percent rise in public construction projects. That was the fourth consecutive month of gains and came even as federal government spending on construction projects tumbled.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.brentwood-karting.com/index.php/carezone-pharmacy-services-6e56.pdf&quot;&gt;carezone pharmacy jobs&lt;/a&gt;  Another 490,000 people have registered for self-assessment, which means that they would need to complete a tax return online by the end of January. They receive the total amount of child benefit, but then repay some of it in tax.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ssvoverath.de/nokia-body-scale-apple-health-c3db.pdf#frost&quot;&gt;nokia body scale accuracy&lt;/a&gt;  * Cold-weather apparel maker, Moncler, said it had appliedto go public on the Milan Stock Exchange, becoming the latestfashion company to pursue a stock listing. A gaggle of fashionlabels have gone public in recent years, driven by investors&apos;desire to tap into luxury retail, a sector that has quicklyrebounded since the global financial crisis. ()
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
