<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542552015353">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 14:40:15 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.19lhfd281adhp</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Could I have a statement, please? &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.proguaru.com.br/is-it-bad-to-take-ibuprofen-while-breastfeeding-7684.pdf&quot;&gt;is it bad to take ibuprofen while breastfeeding&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;States are ceding accountability for their own financial management,&quot; said attorney Sharon Levine, representing Council 25 of the American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees. &quot;By turning it over to the federal government and hiding behind the bankruptcy process, we lose that accountability, which is a cornerstone of the state constitution.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lucky-websolutions.com/oxytetracycline-cvs-0a7b.pdf#drawing&quot;&gt;tetracycline cvs&lt;/a&gt;  More important than mere words and phrases have been theactions of governments around the world. One country afteranother has accepted the U.S. injunction to stop relying onexports for recovery and instead to promote domestic consumptiongrowth, if necessary financed by debt.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://leotoys.cl/boulevard-92-slimming-vest-body-shapers-2206.pdf#stayed&quot;&gt;puori pw1&lt;/a&gt;  U.S. export prices fell 0.5 percent in August, the sixthstraight monthly decline, while import prices remained flat.Expectations were for export prices to rise 0.1 percent andimport prices to climb 0.4 percent.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tarokasongbad.com/accutanetruthinfo-e3c4.pdf#rifle&quot;&gt;potassiummetabisulfite.com&lt;/a&gt;  Of the thousands of ways the wealthy in America force American youth into hopelessness is by the H1B Visa program, a law written and lobbied for by American corporations, just as they have written the tax code.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://laser-eye-surgery-reviews.org/int-medcom-6a83.pdf&quot;&gt;aimilhealthcare.com&lt;/a&gt;  Texas has been among the Republican-led states most fiercelyopposed to Obamacare, but its monthly rates came in below thenational average, HHS said. With 76 plans to choose from inAustin, a 27-year-old would pay $169 per month for thelowest-cost mid-tier one. In Dallas-Fort Worth, that monthlypremium was $217, from 43 plans available, the report said.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
