<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1543383445121">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">28.11.2018 05:37:25 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.r6gxg2mi4437</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Have you got any qualifications? &lt;a href=&quot;http://starbizzcon.com/stmap_45db0.html?b12.montelukast.cialis.emulgel&quot;&gt;naproxen side effects yahoo&lt;/a&gt;  Emmy-nominated Robert Duncan, who scored &quot;The Last Resort,&quot;a TV show about a U.S. nuclear submarine crew, said that viewerswho watch several episodes of a show in a row on platforms suchas Netflix were changing the art form of television soundtracks.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bombeirodf.com.br/stmap_50f80.html?suminat.intimax.levitra.tofranil&quot;&gt;pottsville physiotherapy nsw&lt;/a&gt;  Mize has had other serious health conditions since she was cured of Hodgkin&apos;s disease in the 1970s: Her thyroid was removed in the late 1980s due to noncancerous &quot;knots&quot; on it, and she was diagnosed with ductal carcinoma in situ in 2009. She is just one example of why some experts have started calling cancer a chronic disease, one that requires long-term follow-up care.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://starbizzcon.com/stmap_45db0.html?protonix.tadarise.viagra&quot;&gt;viagra stores in kolkata&lt;/a&gt;  The NFL agreed Thursday to spend $765 million to settle a lawsuit from more than 4,500 former players &amp;#x2014; what became known in football circles as The Concussion Lawsuit. On the surface, $765 million sounds enormous &amp;#x2014; three-quarters of a billion! &amp;#x2014; but in the NFL world, it amounts to tip money. The total settlement figure is about 8 percent of the league&amp;#x2019;s revenue from last year, or around one month of income.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://teerandaz.com/stmap_131c0.html?livial.viagra.ornidazole&quot;&gt;mail order pharmacy in new jersey&lt;/a&gt;  Some Russian organizing officials call Putin team &quot;captain&quot;. He seems to have reveled in the difficulties, building venues from scratch, persuading wealthy tycoons to fund construction and coping with floods and mudslides around Sochi last month.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://public-admin.co.uk/stmap_3c8d0.html?cialis.viprofil.voltaren&quot;&gt;micardis generic cost&lt;/a&gt;  In June, Bank of Tokyo-Mitsubishi agreed to pay New York state $250 million for deleting information from $100 billion in wire transfers that authorities could have used to police transactions with sanctioned countries like Iran.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
