<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542626701297">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 11:25:01 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1tmuz1he6yx8z</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I&apos;m sorry, I didn&apos;t catch your name &lt;a href=&quot;http://reflectiveteens.com/adhdcomau-213a.pdf#silence&quot;&gt;adhd.com.au&lt;/a&gt;  One of the keys to being a great journalist is transparency. And so, Don Lemon has finally decided to come clean. The CNN anchor reveals in his memoir, &apos;Transparent,&apos; that he is gay. &quot;People are going to say: &apos;Oh, he was molested as a kid and now he is coming out,&quot; Lemmon said in an interview with The New York Times, acknowledging that details about his personal life will probably garner more headlines than his insights on the journalism industry. Lemon, 45, recognized that while his sexual orientation won&apos;t be news to his colleagues, it will be to his audience &amp;#150; a fact that has left him &apos;scared.&apos;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.weymouthskatepark.co.uk/pillfind-librarycom-6ae3.pdf&quot;&gt;en.anspharma.com.br&lt;/a&gt;  Ohio has joined an agreement among states and sellers where retailers voluntarily collect the sales taxes. By 2015, Ohio will collect $60 million a year through the agreement and could collect more than $200 million if the bill passes, according to its tax commissioner, Joe Testa. Extra revenue will be used to drive down the personal income tax rate, he said.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tarokasongbad.com/neon-pharmacy-open-sign-e3c4.pdf#attendant&quot;&gt;neon pharmacy cross sign&lt;/a&gt;  For example, the &amp;lsquo;many worlds interpretation&amp;rsquo;, developed in the 1950s, would argue that when the box is opened, the observer and dead-and-alive cat split into two realities, in one of which the observer sees a dead cat and the other an alive one.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://globalelite.tv/wddsportcombr-b1c8.pdf&quot;&gt;wddsport.com.br&lt;/a&gt;  Rookie general manager Rick Hahn is dealing &amp;#8212; we hope that&apos;s the right word &amp;#8212; with his maiden trading deadline. He has until Wednesday at 3 p.m. to prove he&apos;s up to the task of manufacturing some productive moves.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://contactconsultoria.com/index.php/homeremediesfororalthrushcom-a511.pdf&quot;&gt;cleaner.skin-care-healthy.com&lt;/a&gt;  The only players who should be debating “who is the best basketball team in the city” are the kids from Lincoln High School and Boys &amp; Girls. It’s a cute argument for teams in the PSAL. When it involves the two professional teams separated by one famous bridge and a few games in the standings, it is beyond silly.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
