<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542727743265">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">20.11.2018 15:29:03 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1kjibuzeca57z</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Did you go to university? &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cabanadolago.com.br/index.php/equidren-reviews-ab8a.pdf&quot;&gt;equidren side effects&lt;/a&gt;  A &quot;quick first shot&quot; feature lets users take pictures directly from the unlock screen and adjust focus and exposure later, while &quot;smart best shot&quot; automatically detects photo type and takes multiple shots for best selection. There is also a &quot;favorite mode,&quot; which lets users create up to five profiles with customised effects, flash, capture mode and scenes.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://virtual-operations.com/womensense-sex-essentials-reviews-92e2.pdf#squeeze&quot;&gt;better than sex eye essentials&lt;/a&gt;  Wells Fargo&apos;s net income applicable to common shareholders rose to $5.32 billion, or 99 cents per share, from $4.72 billion, or 88 cents per share, a year earlier. Analysts, on average, estimated Wells Fargo would earn 97 cents per share, according to Thomson Reuters I/B/E/S.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.md-interiors.co.uk/piroxicam-cvs-a6a4.pdf&quot;&gt;piroxicam gel cvs&lt;/a&gt;  Uralkali said it would now market its fertilizer through its own subsidiary, Uralkali Trading. It said it had signed an agreement to exercise an option with China&amp;#8217;s fertilizer importer, CNAMPGC Shanghai Corp., to deliver an additional 500,000 tons of potassium chloride within the framework of its 2013 contract. In January, BPC had negotiated a one-million-ton deal with China for the first half at $400 a ton.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ascfinancialadvisers.co.uk/arcsupplementscom-5553.pdf&quot;&gt;sunshinehealthfoodstore.com&lt;/a&gt;  IDEA World Fitness Convention runs August 7-11, with more than 5,000 influential fitness and wellness professionals from 65 nations participating in hundreds of sessions devoted to new fitness trends.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://lemcasesorias.com/index.php/slimquick-pure-extra-strength-side-effects-83f5.pdf#touching&quot;&gt;slimquick pure gummies&lt;/a&gt;  Baggage: Dear old dad: Must move beyond fringe reputation that kept father&apos;s presidential runs from going far. Deflection: Full-speed ahead. Aggressively pressing libertarian principles, especially on anti-terrorism. Past positions: Expressed misgivings about how Civil Rights Act bans racial discrimination by private businesses. Deflection: Reaching out directly to black voters and insisting the party needs to broaden appeal to minorities. He needs to broaden his appeal, too, beyond his tea party roots.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
