<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542860817270">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">22.11.2018 04:26:57 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1522sg74cja89</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Will I have to work shifts? &lt;a href=&quot;https://laser-eye-surgery-reviews.org/electric-six-i-buy-the-drugs-is-it-illegal-to-buy-canadian-drugs-6a83.pdf&quot;&gt;price chopper pharmacy gardner&lt;/a&gt;  By 10pm, she&amp;rsquo;d made her way through all the intra-company messages and alerts, and now turned to her own OuterCircle account. She hadn&amp;rsquo;t visited in six days, and found 118 new notices from that day alone. She decided to plow through, newest to oldest. Most recently, one of her friends from college had posted a message about having the stomach flu, and a long thread followed, with friends making suggestions about remedies, some offering sympathy, some posting photos meant to cheer her up. Mae liked two of the photos, liked three of the comments, posted her own well wishes, and sent a link to a song, &amp;ldquo;Puking Sally&amp;rdquo;, that she&amp;rsquo;d found. That prompted a new thread, 54 notices, about the song and the band that wrote it. One of the friends on the thread said he knew the bassist in the band, and then looped him into the conversation. The bassist, Damien Ghilotti, was in New Zealand, was a studio engineer now, but was happy to know that &amp;ldquo;Puking Sally&amp;rdquo; was still resonating with the flu-ridden. His post thrilled all involved, and another 129 notices appeared, everyone thrilled to hear from the actual bassist from the band, and by the end of the thread, Damien Ghilotti was invited to play a wedding, if he wanted, or visit Boulder, or Bath, or Gainesville, or St Charles, Illinois, any time he happened to be passing through, and he would have a place to stay and a home-cooked meal. Upon the mention of St Charles, someone asked if anyone from there had heard about Tim Jenkins, who was fighting in Afghanistan; they&amp;rsquo;d seen some mention of a kid from Illinois being shot to death by an Afghan insurgent posing as a police officer. Sixty messages later the respondents had determined that it was a different Tim Jenkins, this one from Rantoul, Illinois, not St Charles. There was relief all around, but soon the thread had been overtaken by a multiparticipant debate about the efficacy of that war, US foreign policy in general, whether or not we won in Vietnam or Grenada or even WWI, and the ability of the Afghans to self- govern, and the opium trade financing the insurgents, and the possibility of legalisation of any and all illicit drugs in America and Europe. Someone mentioned the usefulness of marijuana in alleviating glaucoma, and someone else mentioned it was helpful for those with MS, too, and then there was a frenetic exchange between three family members of MS patients, and Mae, feeling some darkness opening its wings within her, signed off.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
