<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542597044546">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 03:10:44 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.co4hz282ru7l</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>This is your employment contract &lt;a href=&quot;http://reflectiveteens.com/embermedbillcom-213a.pdf&quot;&gt;cafeinesupplement.nl&lt;/a&gt;  Management has offered a 12 percent pay raise over four years to the workers. According to management, the BART workers earn on average $79,000 a year, plus benefits. The unions peg the average worker salary at $64,000.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.artistparama.com/buy-viagra-in-canada-no-prescription-5168.pdf&quot;&gt;precio del viagra generico en mexico&lt;/a&gt;  The bank agreed to pay $100 million and admit its traders acted recklessly, the CFTC said on Wednesday. The bank was instructed to send the funds to accounts receivable at the CFTC&apos;s division of enforcement.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tarokasongbad.com/cialis-daily-use-vs-viagra-e3c4.pdf#intentional&quot;&gt;pfizer viagra online in india&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;It is the actors that are supposed to be running countries and upholding the rule of law that are seen as the most corrupt, judged to be abusing their positions of power and acting in their own interests rather than for the citizens they are there to represent and serve,&quot; Transparency International wrote.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://oporajeyo.com/scifil-online-bf45.pdf&quot;&gt;order scifil&lt;/a&gt;  The Standard &amp; Poor&amp;rsquo;s 500 index rose for the 10th out of the last 11 trading days. It now stands four points shy of its all-time record high, set on Aug. 2. The Dow Jones industrial average has now risen on six of the past seven trading days.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.greenlamindustries.com/blog/cadastro-para-comprar-lexapro-mais-barato-0bae.pdf#alley&quot;&gt;lexapro 10 mg precio&lt;/a&gt;  The Polish president attended a memorial cermony in the western Ukrainian city of Lutsk to mark the 70th anniversary of a notorious massacre during World War II when more than 100,000 people were killed.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
