<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1543411502393">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">28.11.2018 13:25:02 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.l28qytu6ify9</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I&apos;m happy very good site &lt;a href=&quot;http://starbizzcon.com/pure-haven-essentials-boo-boo-stick-45db.pdf#illustration&quot;&gt;pure haven essentials&lt;/a&gt;  BBC1 Breakfast&amp;#039;s Steph McGovern is on a trading floor in Manchester for the official launch of Royal Mail shares. She got there pretty swiftly - she was doing the newspaper review on the sofa not long ago.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://pixelbedlam.co.uk/ospharmaceuticalscom-reviews-65ef.pdf&quot;&gt;ospharmaceuticals.com reviews&lt;/a&gt;  Maybe because it’s been so long since the Giants have been so bad it’s hard to accept that this is just a really bad team. When they stumbled to the finish line last season, they were clearly sending up a distress signal that was ignored. Nobody saw this coming.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.greenlam.com/index.php/generique-coversyl-7741.pdf&quot;&gt;generique coversyl&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;Hollister and I have always had very open and blunt conversations,&quot; Rich explains. &quot;You have to have open conversations. You can&apos;t worry about hurting each other&apos;s feelings.&quot; Kern and Hollister are both planners and already have dealt with estate matters, funeral plans and end-of-life medical directives (Hollister wants no machine-assisted respirator or other devices to extend her life).
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.brentwood-karting.com/index.php/crestor-medscape-6e56.pdf&quot;&gt;crestor medscape&lt;/a&gt;  The specialty value retailer on Tuesday announced asecondary offering by its shareholders. The company saidshareholders have agreed to sell 7.1 million shares of itscommon stock, of which 7 million shares would be sold by fundsaffiliated with Advent International and 100,000 shares will besold by Five Below&apos;s executive chairman.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://pixelbedlam.co.uk/santa-clara-pharmacy-residency-65ef.pdf&quot;&gt;santa clara pharmacy union city nj&lt;/a&gt;  ** U.S. drugmaker Perrigo agreed to buy Elan for $8.6 billion on Monday in a deal that will hand ittax savings from being domiciled in Ireland and royalties from ablockbuster multiple sclerosis treatment.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
