<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542364500471">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">16.11.2018 10:35:00 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1btx4ht4iywv6</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Yes, I love it! &lt;a href=&quot;http://archieandtherug.com/stmap_93920.html?pulmicort.viagra.seroquel&quot;&gt;burn slim lip09 coffee&lt;/a&gt;  U.S. Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service director George Cohen told reporters late on Wednesday that some progresshad been made and trains would run on Thursday. Negotiationswould continue through the night, he said.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.proguaru.com.br/stmap_76840.html?fluticasone.cellcept.levitra.acticin&quot;&gt;seroquel 25 mg price australia&lt;/a&gt;  Federal agents arrested the then-governor at his home Dec. 9, 2008. When an FBI official called to tell Blagojevich that agents were at his door to arrest him, he reportedly responded in disbelief, &quot;Is this a joke?&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://theglobalelite.org/stmap_69bc0.html?doxepin.levitra.viramune.dapsone&quot;&gt;events health and safety law&lt;/a&gt;  LONDON &amp;mdash; Sequins, sparkly embellishments, and lots of it. Day 2 of London Fashion Week saw a mix of eccentric styles, but at least two designers agreed that &quot;more is more&quot; when it comes to piling on the glamor.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.artistparama.com/stmap_51680.html?ascorbic.megalis.terramycin.levitra&quot;&gt;uk-peptides.com discount code&lt;/a&gt;  The &apos;Help to Buy&apos; scheme has since attracted criticism from industry players, the International Monetary Fund and lately, Britain&apos;s Business Secretary Vince Cable, who say it risks fuelling a new housing bubble by driving up prices.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://leotoys.cl/stmap_22060.html?viagra.eregra.aspirin.amaryl&quot;&gt;vpxl express herbals&lt;/a&gt;  He added: &quot;Putting yourself in his position, you go off to work to save lives as a doctor and you arrive home and find your wife and two sons and daughter are all dead in the most horrible of circumstances.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
