<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542651184169">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 18:13:04 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.8tqkobncmi55</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>It&apos;s OK &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sarah-hyland.net/functionalmedicineassociates-79a8.pdf&quot;&gt;discoverhealthmd.com&lt;/a&gt;  Chuka Umunna, Labour&apos;s opposition spokesman, said: &quot;The Â£250,000 housing perk the Royal Mail board gave its chief executive â nearly 10 times the average salary â will be totally unfathomable to its customers. The decision to award this housing assistance in the first place is surprising and calls into question the judgement of the Royal Mail&apos;s board.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ecorporationbd.com/retaildoctorcomau-aaa8.pdf#olive&quot;&gt;medasf.org&lt;/a&gt;  In the North-east, Merseyside and South-west this premium is as high as 14 per cent or over Â£3,000 a year.However, in central London, the East and South East, the average public sector worker gets paid less than their private-sector equivalent.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://sjofartsbygningen.no/nutritionsupplementnet-7ef0.pdf#mighty&quot;&gt;nutritionsupplement.net&lt;/a&gt;  The absence of a financial backstop to help banks once their problems are laid bare may prompt the ECB to delay the tests of banks altogether, a move that could postpone supervision and damage the euro zone&apos;s image internationally.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lucky-websolutions.com/motrin-coupons-2015-0a7b.pdf&quot;&gt;tylenol or motrin for baby cold&lt;/a&gt;  Fulham could only half clear a Palace corner and the ball was worked back out to Jason Puncheon, on the left, whose cross was headed home by Mariappa with a fine leap which saw the 5ft 11in defender outjump 6ft 6in Brede Hangeland.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://leotoys.cl/green-magnitude-cancer-2206.pdf#admirable&quot;&gt;green magnitude review&lt;/a&gt;  Detroits bankruptcy, which could result in the reduction of pension benefits for more than 23,000 retirees, has generated a backlash among some former employees and Detroit residents who resent the the appointment of an emergency manager who was not elected by city residents.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
