<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542523142679">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 06:39:02 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1vxhjxlk7n5tp</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>It&apos;s a bad line &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.infocalcbba.edu.bo/perfect-bar-pumpkin-nutrition-9e88.pdf#former&quot;&gt;zone perfect bar target&lt;/a&gt;  The ex-employees &amp;#8220;obsessed&amp;#8221; over the details of fake documents they created to make them look real, including long discussions over what fonts and paper to use and where to place asterisks, Schwartz said yesterday.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lucky-websolutions.com/ospreymedcom-0a7b.pdf#containing&quot;&gt;demeds.de&lt;/a&gt;  On-demand car service app is bringing back its ice cream truck on-demand service in 33 cities on Friday from 11 a.m. to 5 p.m. Though no cash is required -- as everything is paid with your Uber account on your iPhone or Android -- the company says demand for ice cream trucks &quot;will be very high and availability very limited.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lovemycase.com/train-the-trainer-methoden-f2c2.pdf&quot;&gt;the trainer method&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;In looking into this character and what happens to him andthe transformation, I really believe that everybody is capableof good or bad,&quot; Cranston, who won three best actor Emmys forhis portrayal of Walt, said at last month&apos;s Television CriticsAssociation panels in Beverly Hills.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.casadeadoracao.com.br/index.php/parkwood-pharmacy-hours-bac9.pdf&quot;&gt;parkwood pharmacy&lt;/a&gt;  In a bid to help cops catch the hate-filled coward, the Daily News is offering a $10,000 reward for information leading to an arrest and conviction. Anyone with information should call Crime Stoppers at (800) 577-TIPS.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.elegantandwild.co.uk/rxmartcomau-75b3.pdf&quot;&gt;ultramotor.com&lt;/a&gt;  A: Hungary is a busy junction and has been occupied frequently. Having had the Turks, the Austrians and the Russians here is usually seen as a tragedy but it had wonderful musical pluses. Also, the presence of so many Jews, Roma gypsies - a treasure house of musical inspiration. Hungary has a rich folklore like other East European countries. The difference is that here it was elevated and integrated by a very high level intellectual community in Budapest, including great people like Bartok, Kodaly, Weiner, Ligeti and many others.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
