<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542623325034">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 10:28:45 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1a2ubjkjfvr7r</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I need to charge up my phone &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.weymouthskatepark.co.uk/ciprofloxacina-500-mg-infeccion-urinaria-6ae3.pdf&quot;&gt;is cipro good for uti infection&lt;/a&gt;  Severe thunderstorms produced very large hail in eastern North Dakota. A cooperative observer near Lisbon reported conglomerate hailstones 6 inches in diameter. The hail smashed windows, caused very heavy damage to cars, punched holes in buildings, and damaged or destroyed 16,000 acres of crops.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://digital-matchbox.com/kidneyhealthlycom-5522.pdf#ashes&quot;&gt;online-healthresearch.com&lt;/a&gt;  This theory was originally coined by Shanan Peters, of the Department of Geoscience, University of Wisconsin, and Robert Gaines of the Geology Department, Pomona College. The pair used geochemical data to establish that ancient marine sediments caused expansion of &amp;#8220;shallow epicontinental seas.&amp;#8221;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://reflectiveteens.com/delano-regional-medical-center-fax-number-213a.pdf&quot;&gt;delano regional medical center linkedin&lt;/a&gt;  POTISKUM, Nigeria - Suspected Islamic extremists attacked an agricultural college in the dead of night, gunning down dozens of students as they slept in dormitories and torching classrooms, the school&apos;s provost said, reporting the latest violence in northeastern Nigeria&apos;s ongoing Islamic uprising.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ecorporationbd.com/cymbalta-generic-cost-without-insurance-aaa8.pdf#clearly&quot;&gt;is 90mg of cymbalta a high dose&lt;/a&gt;  DENVER — Criminal charges against two cantaloupe farmers over a deadly food-borne illness send an emphatic message to fruit and vegetable growers to crack down on safety, federal regulators said Friday.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.weymouthskatepark.co.uk/lipo-6-hers-uc-comprar-6ae3.pdf&quot;&gt;lipo 6 hers uc&lt;/a&gt;  &amp;#8220;The government is determined to raise standards across the banking industry to create a stronger and safer banking system,&amp;#8221; British Chancellor of the Exchequer George Osborne said in introducing the government&amp;#8217;s response. &amp;#8220;Cultural reform in the banking sector marks the next step in the government&amp;#8217;s plan to move the whole sector from rescue to recovery.&amp;#8221;
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
