<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542555323309">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 15:35:23 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.vshgtd5wmn08</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Could I borrow your phone, please? &lt;a href=&quot;https://zoeydeutch.net/hocks-medical-supply-tipp-city-8f08.pdf&quot;&gt;hocks medical supply jobs&lt;/a&gt;  -- Dutch pension group PGGM to acquire control of gasdistributor Northern Offshore Upstream Gas Pipeline System,which is jointly controlled by French gas and power group GDFSuez and EBN B.V. (notified Sept.17/deadline Oct. 22/simplified)
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.anupamdebashisroy.com/grypharminstorg-f2ef.pdf#wrinkle&quot;&gt;irxmedicine.net&lt;/a&gt;  Operating profit from Jackson National Life, Prudential’sU.S. business, jumped 32 percent to 582 million pounds in thefirst half, helped by sales of Elite Access, a variable annuityproduct. Thiam said the company will benefit from the retirementof America’s 77 million baby boomers, adding that he remains“open minded” to the future of the U.S. division including apotential sale.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://virtual-operations.com/navage-nose-cleaner-australia-92e2.pdf&quot;&gt;navage&lt;/a&gt;  (The Tennessean, Shelley Mays/ Associated Press ) - Chris Boyd, left, appears in a Nashville criminal court hearing on Friday, Sept. 13, 2013 in Nashville. Boyd received an 11-month, 29-day suspended sentence for criminal attempt to commit accessory after the fact, a misdemeanor. If he successfully completes his unsupervised probation, his record will be cleared. He also has agreed to testify truthfully if called as a witness in the rape cases against his former teammates.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mikasafloors.com/biaxin-xl-500-mg-bdec.pdf&quot;&gt;buy clarithromycin 500mg&lt;/a&gt;  This week Ms Taittinger, 51, will officially open her own winery in Sillery, just six miles from Taittinger&amp;rsquo;s cellars in Reims, the result of five years of preparation. The building, which she describes as being &amp;ldquo;not a glamour place, but a very modern technical centre&amp;rdquo;, will process the grapes and store the bottled product, all in her own cellars. Previously she had to rely on other winemakers to produce on her behalf.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ascfinancialadvisers.co.uk/what-information-is-most-important-to-teach-a-client-who-abuses-prescription-drugs-5553.pdf#opposing&quot;&gt;best drugs app iphone&lt;/a&gt;  The date of the fire on Aug. 7 coincided with the 15thanniversary of an al Qaeda attack on the U.S. embassies inNairobi and Dar es Salaam and investigators said at the timethey could not rule out terrorism.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
