<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1543373743848">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">28.11.2018 02:55:43 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1c6rxu8yi2buy</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Sorry, I&apos;m busy at the moment &lt;a href=&quot;http://pixelbedlam.co.uk/stmap_65ef0.html?levitra.donepezil.augmentin&quot;&gt;toprol xl goodrx&lt;/a&gt;  Yes. I think that&apos;s absolutely right, Doug. Let me just say on the USA TODAY circulation front, and then Victoria will chime in here, that as we mentioned with Hilton, we are managing the transition there. I mentioned the point where we are now -- obviously, as we look at the travel space and hotels, we absorbed the behaviors of consumers, and clearly, many more of them want to see USA TODAY on their iPad or their smartphone. And so we put together a Digital portal for Hilton for about 3,000 of their hotels called The Point. We have a number, I think I mentioned about 160,000 or so folks that are -- daily, who are looking at that site. And so we&apos;re managing down the print delivery on -- for instance, at a Hilton, as we transition to more focus on our digital delivery of news and information. So I think you&apos;ll see that the print will continue to decline, but we&apos;ll be continuing to pick that up. And we are paid for that, not as a circulation number but as a specific cost for the portal and the number of rooms that we serve, et cetera. So it&apos;s not a traditional circulation number that you will see there. But, Victoria, you have more detail.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
