<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542691213611">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">20.11.2018 05:20:13 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1nmkfgvurs6bw</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Not in at the moment &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.layeredonline.com/aspire-36-canada-dd54.pdf&quot;&gt;aspire 36 canada&lt;/a&gt;  Until last month, Texas was one of 16 jurisdictions under the Voting Rights Act of 1965 required to have its election changes pre-cleared by either the Department of Justice or the Washington District Court. Congress had determined that these jurisdictions had a history of using election laws to prevent or deter minorities from voting.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.artistparama.com/isle-of-dogs-trailer-imdb-5168.pdf&quot;&gt;isle of dogs cast trailer&lt;/a&gt;  House Republicans on Thursday began lining up 11 more billsto fund targeted programs. They are to fund nutrition programsfor low-income women and their children, a program to securenuclear weapons and non-proliferation, food and drug safety,intelligence-gathering, border patrols, American Indian andAlaska Native health and education programs, weather monitoring,Head Start school programs for the poor and other aid forschools that rely heavily on federal assistance.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.artistparama.com/apollo-peak-5168.pdf&quot;&gt;apollo peak&lt;/a&gt;  Olbermann will be bringing his opinions, and controversial past, back to ESPN to host a late night talk show on ESPN2, based in ABC’s studio overlooking Times Square. The show, called “Olbermann,” will debut August 26, airing at 11 p.m. Monday-Friday.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://stsmihajlopupin.edu.rs/rs/hurricane-spin-scrubber-reviews-australia-3c56.pdf&quot;&gt;hurricane spin scrubber lazada&lt;/a&gt;  One wonders what Republicans most fear: That the plan will crash under its own weight or that it will be successful in giving the uninsured coverage and injecting some common sense into a health care system that has long been a drag on the American economy.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://digital-matchbox.com/marion-pharmacy-winnipeg-mb-5522.pdf#pressing&quot;&gt;marion pharmacy&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;There are productive negotiations going on with theRepublican leader. I&apos;m confident that we&apos;ll be able to reach acomprehensive agreement this week in time to avert acatastrophic default on the nation&apos;s bills,&quot; Reid said on theSenate floor.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
