<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542659532309">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 20:32:12 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.m67cxc5f71i3</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Canada&gt;Canada &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ecorporationbd.com/designer-whey-protein-powder-strawberry-review-aaa8.pdf#parade&quot;&gt;designer whey protein powder reviews&lt;/a&gt;  Located just north of Munich, the birthplace of Oktoberfest, the Weihenstephan Brewery is no novice to brewing, with roots in beer-making going back to the year 768. Weihenstephan became licensed in 1040 and is recognized as the world&apos;s oldest working brewery. Its Festbier is a true German brew, with malt and Noble hops from the Hallertau region in Bavaria. The result is a full, rich-bodied, mildly hopped seasonal lager. Crisp and refreshing, its appearance of a deep gold color is a bit lighter than most Oktoberfest lagers, but otherwise its full carbonation, 5.8 percent ABV and 26 IBUs (International Bittering Units) make it a perfect fit for the style. Hearty foods such as roasts, poultry, game and cheeses will complement the carbonation and maltiness of this brew.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://accentresurfacing.com/femmed-libido-canada-4110.pdf#what&quot;&gt;femmed libido canada&lt;/a&gt;  (Medical Xpress)—UC Irvine microbiologists have learned how a probiotic bacterium used to treat irritable bowel syndrome can soothe gut bacterial infections caused by Salmonella, paving the way for potential relief from f ...
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://theglobalelite.org/alberta-seniors-physiotherapy-69bc.pdf#contend&quot;&gt;seniors physiotherapy&lt;/a&gt;  LexisNexis holds legal, print media and public-records information dating back decades; Dun &amp; Bradstreet aggregates business and credit data on companies; Kroll gives corporations background data about prospective hires, including employment and health histories and drug-test results.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ecorporationbd.com/where-to-buy-flagyl-over-the-counter-aaa8.pdf&quot;&gt;does flagyl cause burning&lt;/a&gt;  Marchionne confirmed that Fiat was freezing plans to investbillions of euros to build new Alfa Romeo and Maserati models inItaly pending clarification of a recent court ruling thatdeclared part of Italy&apos;s labour laws unconstitutional.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://archieandtherug.com/promescent-cost-9392.pdf#favour&quot;&gt;promescent men&apos;s health&lt;/a&gt;  Berry, who has recently been busy promoting her new thriller &quot;The Call,&quot; was photographed enjoying some much needed vacation time with her family during a quick getaway to Hawaii. The star kept her look simple, wearing a dark pair of shades and a loose kaftan over a black two-piece.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
