<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542608869081">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 06:27:49 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.crsp1glznur</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I hate shopping &lt;a href=&quot;https://zoeydeutch.net/anishpharmacom-8f08.pdf#collar&quot;&gt;pharma-energy.com&lt;/a&gt;  Bwin.party, which offers sports betting and online games, is focusing on fewer, higher-paying customers to increase its average yield per player. That metric rose 7 percent to 9.6 euros ($12.7) in the first half of the year. The company did not give a long-term yield target.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sarah-hyland.net/buspar-10mg-street-value-79a8.pdf&quot;&gt;can you take 20 mg of buspar&lt;/a&gt;  The rights groups said French laws had been violated and called for a judicial investigation into the reports on U.S. surveillance that appeared in Britain&apos;s Guardian newspaper, the Washington Post and German news magazine Der Spiegel.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.casadeadoracao.com.br/index.php/supplementedcouk-review-bac9.pdf#ana&quot;&gt;supplemented.co.uk&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;We understand from Ineos and Unite&apos;s press statements thatthere is an intent to keep the utilities necessary for thecontinued operation of FPS at this stage but we are awaitingformal confirmation of this,&quot; a BP statement said.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.klevermedia.co.uk/acetaminophen-ibuprofen-naproxen-sodium-31f1.pdf&quot;&gt;tylenol vs ibuprofen for flu&lt;/a&gt;  For several years, the IAEA has been investigating suspicions that Iran may have coordinated efforts to process uranium, test explosives and revamp a ballistic missile cone in a way suitable for a nuclear warhead.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.greenlamindustries.com/blog/blmediende-0bae.pdf&quot;&gt;www.blmedien.de/fachbuch&lt;/a&gt;  The 5-cent increase, worth about $400 million a quarter, wasabout 3 cents more than analysts had expected. The new sharerepurchase program, with no expiration date, would replaceanother set to expire on Sept. 30.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
