<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542712692501">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">20.11.2018 11:18:12 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.xoq62m5c0t3s</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>What do you like doing in your spare time? &lt;a href=&quot;https://leotoys.cl/nutrakey-whey-optima-2lb-vanilla-ice-cream-cookie-recipe-2206.pdf&quot;&gt;nutrakey whey optima 2lb chocolate lava cake recipe&lt;/a&gt;  Stanford, 63, is serving a 110-year prison sentence after he was convicted on criminal charges in March 2012 for a fraud that the government said was centered in certificates of deposit issued by his Antigua-based Stanford International Bank.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.weymouthskatepark.co.uk/nomedscouk-6ae3.pdf&quot;&gt;nomeds.co.uk&lt;/a&gt;  With Muirfield&apos;s bone-hard fairways, clinging rough and lightning-fast greens proving a deterrent to expansive displays, world number one Woods employed a safety-first approach to record a level-par 71 in his second round on Friday.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://paradiseinmexico.com.mx/orlistat-generico-precio-en-chile-c13c.pdf#youngster&quot;&gt;orlistat precio en walmart&lt;/a&gt;  Cyrus, who just announced her split with fiancé Liam Hemsowrth, talked about her frinedships with fellow musicians such as Pharrell Williams, Lil Kim and Justin Bieber, whom she said she wants to &quot;mentor.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.proguaru.com.br/can-you-buy-finasteride-over-the-counter-uk-7684.pdf&quot;&gt;can you buy finasteride over the counter uk&lt;/a&gt;  As impressive as Merrick&apos;s display was, it was not enough to fend off Mahan, who capped his round in sizzling fashion with three straight birdies to knock his American compatriot from top of the leaderboard with a two-day total of 13-under 131.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://muv.asia/rhaponticum-carthamoides-benefits-bf28.pdf&quot;&gt;rhaponticum carthamoides seeds&lt;/a&gt;  Still, the focus remains on rising demand, especially ahead of the confectioners&apos; quartet of Halloween, Christmas, Valentine&apos;s Day and Easter in the U.S. Cocoa prices soared to a one-year high last week, though on Friday they slipped 0.8% to $2,608 a metric ton as investors booked profits.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
