<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542612811398">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 07:33:31 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.15aieb53yuytq</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Would you like a receipt? &lt;a href=&quot;https://freelifesinsurancequotes.com/medicalsolutionscorpcom-6f97.pdf#faintly&quot;&gt;africahealthconsulting.com&lt;/a&gt;  Wiz Khalifa and Amber Rose are set to become husband and wife. The &apos;Black and Yellow&apos; rapper took to Twitter on March 1 to announce his girlfriend of two years, model Amber Rose, had accepted his marriage proposal. &apos;She Said Yes!!!&apos; he wrote, sharing a photo of Rose&amp;#146;s left hand adorned with a stunning diamond ring. &apos;He has made me the happiest woman in the world!&apos; Rose, 28, tweeted minutes later.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://newscvm.com/himalaya-liv-52-hb-benefits-e9bb.pdf#common&quot;&gt;himalaya liv 52 ds syrup in hindi&lt;/a&gt;  It means that while the total number of dementia sufferers has increased slightly over the past two decades, from about 664,000 in 1991, the proportion of over-65s with the condition has dropped from 8.3 per cent to 6.5 per cent among a much greater elderly population.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://archieandtherug.com/wachters-distributors-9392.pdf&quot;&gt;wachtershauser and huber&lt;/a&gt;  Telefonica, which has debt of nearly 50 billion euros($67.46 billion), wanted influence over what happens to TelecomItalia and its prized Brazilian mobile unit Tim Participacoes, but at minimal cost.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://laser-eye-surgery-reviews.org/test-x180-ignite-mexico-6a83.pdf#excepting&quot;&gt;test x180 ignite mexico&lt;/a&gt;  President Barack Obama&apos;s effort to settle on a candidate to succeed Fed Chairman Ben Bernanke when his term expires in January became front-page news after leaks that suggested former Obama adviser Lawrence Summers was the preferred candidate.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lucky-websolutions.com/l-theanine-vs-green-tea-0a7b.pdf#scientist&quot;&gt;1000 mg theanine&lt;/a&gt;  The sunny outlook has also meant that the best performing stocks have been growth-oriented names. After a weak August, companies with already high p/e ratios and high short interest rebounded, and have outperformed for the balance of the year.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
