<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542357575351">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">16.11.2018 08:39:35 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1ew1myr018oa5</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Yes, I love it! &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cabanadolago.com.br/index.php/stmap_ab8a0.html?cialis.relafen.aldactone&quot;&gt;medicinesbd.com&lt;/a&gt;  Joel began playing in local bands before releasing a debut album in 1971 that was indifferently received, before 1973&amp;rsquo;s Piano Man provided his signature song and put him on the road towards superstardom. During the next two decades, he released a string of hit singles and albums, winning grammy awards for album of the year in 1978 and song of the year and record of the year for Just the Way You Are. He dated Elle Macpherson and married another supermodel &amp;ndash; Christine Brinkley &amp;ndash; and in 1987 he became the first American rock star to play Russia since the building of the Berlin Wall. He seemed to have it all, but the one thing that eluded him was critical acclaim.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://freelifesinsurancequotes.com/stmap_6f970.html?levitra.gyne-lotrimin.lamprene.plendil&quot;&gt;arthritistreatments.com.au&lt;/a&gt;  Washington has stationed surveillance planes there andpromised up to $30 million in support for building and operatingcoastal radar stations, all aimed at improving its ally&apos;sability to counter China&apos;s naval encroachment in the disputedSouth China Sea that has alarmed several Asian nations.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.layeredonline.com/stmap_dd540.html?colcrys.mesalamine.levitra&quot;&gt;best drugstore eyeliner for waterline&lt;/a&gt;  Mr Ji, who lost his left hand in the blast, gave his testimony on stretcher. He insisted that he had not intended to harm others or commit suicide and only wanted to protest over an unresolved compensation dispute related to a fight with security guards which he alleges left him partially paralysed.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://accentresurfacing.com/stmap_41100.html?esomeprazole.symmetrel.vepesid.levitra&quot;&gt;medsource.com.pl&lt;/a&gt;  In addition to claiming Silver didn’t do enough to deal with sexual harassment by the pervy former Brooklyn assemblyman, the suit also states Lopez told one of his victims to sleep with a Cuomo administration official to help get a housing bill passed.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://zoeydeutch.net/stmap_8f080.html?neggram.cialis.atorvastatin.sildalis&quot;&gt;metronidazole side effects drugs.com&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;The mere fact that someone with your client&apos;s history is foolish enough to get arrested indicates to me a kind of cavalier attitude about the situation,&quot; Manhattan Supreme Court Justice Melissa Jackson said to Sinde&apos;s attorney.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
