<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542544179442">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">18.11.2018 12:29:39 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.8vamuh9d8l0q</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Looking for a job &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.md-interiors.co.uk/pride-pharmacy-carlisle-a6a4.pdf#rouse&quot;&gt;pride pharmacy oakland park fl&lt;/a&gt;  Customer Service: To ensure that tabeo e2 owners receive dedicated, 24-hour tabeo customer service for any questions they might have, Toys&quot;R&quot;Us has included a preloaded customer service chat app on the device, which allows parents to quickly and easily chat with representatives directly on the tablet itself when connected to WiFi. A tabeo-specific customer service line is also available at 1-888-477-0888 to provide further assistance.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.klevermedia.co.uk/spillbartno-31f1.pdf&quot;&gt;healthyoxfordhills.org&lt;/a&gt;  The newspaper cited government sources in Berlin as sayingthat the third aid programme would be much smaller than thefirst two and the conditions would also be less strict as Greecehas already set a lot of the necessary changes in motion.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.proguaru.com.br/pharmacy-2000-7684.pdf#option&quot;&gt;pharmacy 2000 oshakati&lt;/a&gt;  The Bank, which is currently undergoing a rescue plan involving new capital from Co-operative Group and upfront losses for some Co-op Bank bondholders, said that until his departure Mr. Bulmer will continue to play a crucial role in the running of the business.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.artistparama.com/can-you-fly-with-prescription-drugs-5168.pdf&quot;&gt;fda regulations on prescription drugs&lt;/a&gt;  Property taxes here are also extremely low, at $765 a year, and median home prices are $102,600. The city is famous for its Mira Sol green chile peppers, so the AARP suggests picking up a “slopper” sandwich, a cheeseburger with green chile topping at The Sunset Inn.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.proguaru.com.br/wakemedjobs-7684.pdf#antique&quot;&gt;wakemed.jobs&lt;/a&gt;  States running their own Obamacare exchanges are also uncertain about whether their own employees will get paid in the event of a shutdown, and whether they will have access to the federal grants that support their operations. The ambiguity stems from the fact that the grants, totaling tens and even hundreds of millions of dollars, did not come in the form of a lump payment deposited in a state&apos;s bank account.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
