<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542486707640">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">17.11.2018 20:31:47 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.jnsl2aietg91</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>Yes, I love it! &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.klevermedia.co.uk/suecacomedoriacombr-31f1.pdf&quot;&gt;med.li&lt;/a&gt;  Local factors that trigger or inhibit storm formation occur on spatial scales too small for global climate models to simulate. That&apos;s why the researchers focused on broader environmental conditions that are known to favor a buildup of the sprawling, towering thunderheads that mark severe thunderstorms.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.layeredonline.com/gvicom-dd54.pdf&quot;&gt;gvi.com.mx&lt;/a&gt;  India joins the U.S., Russia, France and Britain in building its own carrier. The carrier was launched at the Kochi shipyard in southern Kerala state, but it still needs to be outfitted and extensive trials held before it is inducted into the Indian navy in 2018.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ecorporationbd.com/caverta-online-uk-aaa8.pdf&quot;&gt;buy caverta uk&lt;/a&gt;  This may not be the case with his comments on the role of women in the church. When asked whether he might support the ordination of women as priests, the pope gave the stock response. &quot;The church has spoken and said, &apos;No,&apos;&quot; Francis said, referring to John Paul II&apos;s statement that because Jesus chose only men as his disciples, the church was not able to ordain women.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://theglobalelite.org/mackie-pharmacy-spey-road-69bc.pdf&quot;&gt;jp mackie pharmacy giffnock&lt;/a&gt;  The rental market “has reached a state of equilibrium,” Citi Habitats president Gary Malin told the News. “Over the past year, we have seen only modest price adjustments from month to month in either direction.”
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://virtual-operations.com/kamagra-online-bestellen-paypal-92e2.pdf#stage&quot;&gt;kamagra bez recepty&lt;/a&gt;  Greek authorities arrested Golden Dawn&apos;s leadership this weekend after the slaying of anti-fascist rapper Pavlos Fyssas &amp;#8212; allegedly by a party volunteer in front of a crowd. Doctors, activists and victims greeted the news with relief but argued authorities should have acted much earlier, saying the killing was the culmination of a months-long increase in the brutality and brazenness of attacks by extreme right street gangs.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
