<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1542629669884">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">19.11.2018 12:14:29 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1cyxwpabs3n36</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I do some voluntary work &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.anupamdebashisroy.com/providerindianamedicaidcom-f2ef.pdf&quot;&gt;svimed.eu&lt;/a&gt;  &quot;In terms of funding, an average of £3.80 per head is currently spent on cycling in Scotland - more than double the amount being spent in England outside of London. Promoting cycling needs to be a partnership endeavour and we are working across ministerial portfolios to identify opportunities to enhance funding where possible.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.anupamdebashisroy.com/wwwcarepathwayscomdhhs-statescfm-f2ef.pdf#compact&quot;&gt;carepathways.com nursing homes&lt;/a&gt;  Apple also informed developers of the breach via email this afternoon. Cupertino noted that those whose developer accounts were set to expire during the downtime will have them extended and apps will remain in the App Store.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lovemycase.com/jamestown-pharmacy-ohio-f2c2.pdf#notebook&quot;&gt;jamestown pharmacy jamestown ky&lt;/a&gt;  The two versions tested by the magazine were priced at $24,320 for a non-turbocharged model with a manual transmission and $28,820 for a turbocharged SUV with a continuously variable automatic transmission. They were among the less expensive SUVs in contention.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://digital-matchbox.com/rxq-compounding-ohio-5522.pdf&quot;&gt;rxq compounding jobs&lt;/a&gt;  Security experts say five North Korean-flagged vessels havetransited through the Panama Canal in the last three years. Oneship, the O Un Chong Nyon Ho, passed through the canal anddocked in Havana in May 2012.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lovemycase.com/w3pharmaorqpl-f2c2.pdf#thickness&quot;&gt;hc.genevahealth.com&lt;/a&gt;  Secularism has long been part of American Jewish life, which includes movements such as the Society for Humanistic Judaism founded in Detroit in the 1960s. However, the Pew survey found the percentage of American Jews who say they are atheist, agnostic or have no particular religion is highest among younger generations.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
