<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2432" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1363280116832" lastModified="1543385733610">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; SV1)</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bone-update</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">28.11.2018 06:15:33 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.zs50rmpw5wlu</hopsession>
    <user>default</user>
    <pvcount type="float">85.0</pvcount>
    <body>I&apos;m not interested in football &lt;a href=&quot;http://oktandrammen.no/drammen-ny/hawthorne-pharmacy--medical-equipment-company-e52c.pdf#or&quot;&gt;hawthorne pharmacy &amp; medical equipment company columbia sc 29201&lt;/a&gt;  Financial industry lobbyists and people inside the agencyhave been furiously speculating who would succeed him, and theNew York Times reported on Thursday that President Barack Obamawas vetting Massad as a candidate.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.brentwood-karting.com/index.php/driclor-reviews-feet-6e56.pdf#drawer&quot;&gt;driclor australia&lt;/a&gt;  Last month the Prime Minister said he would &quot;back up&quot; schools that ask people to remove Muslim veils, saying if schools wanted to implement a particular dress code, he believed the Government should back them.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.brentwood-karting.com/index.php/ads-itnet-6e56.pdf&quot;&gt;xanax-best-offer.com&lt;/a&gt;  A red-lipped, kimono-clad geisha vanishing around a corner. Riverside cherry trees bursting into cloudlike bloom. Zen gardens with raked sand and haiku-inspiring rock formations. There are perhaps few more evocative city names than &amp;ldquo;Kyoto&amp;rdquo;. While Tokyo is all high-speed trains, flashes of neon and skyscrapers, Kyoto moves to an altogether different rhythm.
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://starbizzcon.com/integrated-pharma-services-limited-45db.pdf&quot;&gt;integrated pharma services inc&lt;/a&gt;  But the stimulus was never intended to be a permanent source of money, said former New Hampshire Sen. Judd Gregg. He opposed the stimulus, calling it at the time &quot;a great deal of money not well spent.&quot;
 &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bombeirodf.com.br/starwaypharmcom-50f8.pdf#orchestra&quot;&gt;starwaypharm.com&lt;/a&gt;  Ford, which in July lifted its 2013 guidance to an unchanged pretax loss in Europe of about $1.8 billion from $2 billion, recently closed two ancillary plants in the UK and plans to shut its Genk assembly line in Belgium at the end of 2014.
 </body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>http://beagleboard.org/bone-update/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
