<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="2801" name="Page" prototype="Page" created="1372191685830" lastModified="1527546510248">
  <hop:parent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/5.0 (Macintosh; Intel Mac OS X 10_12_5) AppleWebKit/537.36 (KHTML, like Gecko) Chrome/58.0.3029.110 Safari/537.36</http_browser>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <uri>bad-to-the-bone</uri>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <time type="date">23.05.2017 12:53:36 UTC</time>
    <pseudoparent idref="0" prototyperef="Root"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.1doyt4mssbu6w</hopsession>
    <user>jkridner.wordpress.com</user>
    <pvcount type="float">22076.0</pvcount>
    <body>&lt;div style=&quot;float:right;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://bit.ly/2rwqa3e&quot; style=&quot;width:120px;height:240px;&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; marginwidth=&quot;0&quot; marginheight=&quot;0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;&lt;em&gt;Bad to the Bone&lt;/em&gt;: Crafting Electronics Systems with BeagleBone Black, Second Edition&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.morganclaypool.com/doi/abs/10.2200/S00675ED1V01Y201509DCS046&quot;&gt;
Published by Morgan and Claypool&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;November 2015, 417 pages&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Authors&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Steven F. Barrett, University of Wyoming&lt;br /&gt;
Jason Kridner, Texas Instruments
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Abstract&lt;/h3&gt;    
&lt;p&gt;BeagleBone Black is a low-cost, open hardware computer uniquely suited to interact with sensors and actuators directly and over the Web. Introduced in April 2013 by BeagleBoard.org, a community of developers first established in early 2008, BeagleBone Black is used frequently to build vision-enabled robots, home automation systems, artistic lighting systems, and countless other do-it-yourself and professional projects. BeagleBone variants include the original BeagleBone and the newer BeagleBone Black, both hosting a powerful 32-bit, super-scalar ARM Cortex A8 processor capable of running numerous mobile and desktop-capable operating systems, typically variants of Linux including Debian, Android, and Ubuntu. Yet, BeagleBone is small enough to fit in a small mint tin box. The &quot;Bone&quot; may be used in a wide variety of projects from middle school science fair projects to senior design projects to first prototypes of very complex systems. Novice users may access the power of the Bone through the user-friendly BoneScript software, experienced through a Web browser in most major operating systems, including Microsoft Windows, Apple Mac OS X, or the Linux operating systems. Seasoned users may take full advantage of the Bone&apos;s power using the underlying Linux-based operating system, a host of feature extension boards (Capes) and a wide variety of Linux community open source libraries. This book provides an introduction to this powerful computer and has been designed for a wide variety of users including the first time novice through the seasoned embedded system design professional. The book contains background theory on system operation coupled with many well-documented, illustrative examples. Examples for novice users are centered on motivational, fun robot projects while advanced projects follow the theme of assistive technology and image-processing applications.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Key Features:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Provides detailed examples for all BeagleBone variants, including the 
        newest &quot;next generation&quot; BeagleBone Black
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
        BeagleBone is a low cost, open hardware, expandable computer first 
        introduced in November 2011 by BeagleBoard.org
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
        BeagleBone variants, including the original BeagleBone and the new 
        BeagleBone Black, hosts a powerful 32-bit, super-scalar ARM Cortex A8 
        processor
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
        BeagleBone is small enough to fit in a small mint tin box
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
        &quot;Bone&quot; may be used in a wide variety of projects from middle school 
        science fair projects to university courses and senior design projects 
        to first prototypes of very complex systems
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
        Novice users may access the power of the Bone through the user-friendly
        BoneScript environment    
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
        Seasoned users may take full advantage of the Bone&apos;s power using the 
        underlying Linux-based operating system
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
        A host of feature extension boards (Capes) and a wide variety of Linux 
        community open source libraries are available
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
        The book provides an introduction to this powerful computer and has 
        been designed for a wide variety of users
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
        The book contains background theory on system operation coupled with
        many well-documented, illustrative examples
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
        Examples for novice users are centered on motivational, fun robot
        projects
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
        Advanced projects follow the theme of assistive technology and image 
        processing applications
    &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Resources&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jadonk/bad-to-the-bone-examples&quot;&gt;Examples
    from the text&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;div style=&quot;clear:both;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</body>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.8</http_language>
    <is_xhtml type="boolean">true</is_xhtml>
    <http_referer>https://beagleboard.org/bad-to-the-bone/edit</http_referer>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
