<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="helma.xsl"?>
<xmlroot xmlns:hop="http://www.helma.org/docs/guide/features/database">
  <hopobject id="4320" name="jkridner" prototype="Page" created="1542645769173" lastModified="1594847758243">
  <hop:parent idref="199" prototyperef="Page"/>
    <http_remotehost>127.0.0.1</http_remotehost>
    <property propertyname="hck.sssn">SVROYytnZHQwdS80aUY5RVVqN2pRUGlXYzZJeGpOeHRXL1F2WW1vRW1ITVdsdkE2K29oVXRmakZMdDFlZktmN3g4MWhsaFpYclgyM3R3MVJUbGZpSG41MTZQVk5IN2hHa3hITkh5YStjUXo0aGJWZ1RIb3ZUbGhhRm41emZkWDNHTlZtZ3pQUU9LK0pRaEF1eVorUTAvdTM3d3Y0QW50MGV3TEZuRGh0N0RVRVVFU3F4U0FYbXlPS0Nlay9ZQmtRLS1KYkRYamczR21nQ3ltRzBKNStvbnB3PT0=--4625fa5cd3693174863335c3fc44f82e5b357980</property>
    <property propertyname="hck.rut">BAhbCFsGaQJGn0kiQSQyYSQxMCRxenouRzBhelRHM3NiOFY4dFVJc08uR3dZaHpPVzdnUnhZbDc0UVJaUVFVb2IzejJvNDdFLgY6BkVUSSIXMTU2ODczMzU4Ni40ODQ5ODU0BjsARg==--711a801a6a561986adfa8f215a428458c139456c</property>
    <http_language>en-US,en;q=0.5</http_language>
    <uri>jkridner</uri>
    <http_browser>Mozilla/5.0 (Macintosh; Intel Mac OS X 10.14; rv:77.0) Gecko/20100101 Firefox/77.0</http_browser>
    <time type="date">15.07.2020 21:15:58 UTC</time>
    <property propertyname="hck.usi">1</property>
    <hopsession>127.0.0.a6eu4bgndojb</hopsession>
    <tk_tc>kPzQSUP3yUazAsQ/</tk_tc>
    <mcpopupclosed>yes</mcpopupclosed>
    <body>&lt;h1&gt;Jason Kridner&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/static/images/jasonkridner_web1_1.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;In my own words&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hi, I&apos;m Jason Kridner, co-founder of the BeagleBoard.org project. We want to help people make appliances where technology serves you, rather than building applications to run on someone else&apos;s platform and serves them. Open source hardware and software are our tools. Education and collaboration are our process. Driving access to technology without barriers is how we hope to make a difference.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;In the words of someone else&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jason Kridner is a founder of the BeagleBoard.org Foundation and
an over 25 year veteran of Texas Instruments working in embedded systems.
The BeagleBoard.org&lt;sup&gt;®&lt;/sup&gt; Foundation is a US-based 501c3 non-profit
existing to provide education in and collaboration around the design and use
of open-source software and hardware in embedded computing. Jason leads 
the development of and maintains open-source development tools such as
BeagleBoard&lt;sup&gt;®&lt;/sup&gt;, -xM, -X15, PocketBeagle&lt;sup&gt;®&lt;/sup&gt;, BeagleBone&lt;sup&gt;®&lt;/sup&gt;, Black, Blue,
and AI. Kridner has been a featured keynote speaker and 
instructor at many industry and educational events including Maker Faires,
American Society of Engineering Education Conferences, Embedded Linux Conferences, Collaboration 
Summit, Android Builders, OSCON, CES and others.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Email: &lt;span id=&quot;email1&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Webex: &lt;a href=&quot;https://ti.webex.com/meet/jdk&quot;&gt;Jason&apos;s meeting room&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Telephone: 713-234-0535&lt;br /&gt;
Meetings: &lt;a href=&quot;http://calendly.com/jkridner&quot;&gt;Create a meeting&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Twitter: &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/jadon&quot;&gt;@jadon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
IRC: jkridner @ &lt;a href=&quot;/chat&quot;&gt;#beagle&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
BeagleBoard.org: &lt;a href=&quot;/about&quot;&gt;About&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    var email1 = &quot;jkrXXXidner@beaXXXgleboard.oXXXrg&quot;.replace(/XXX/g,&apos;&apos;);
    var email2 = &quot;chXXXristi@XXXbeagleXXXboardXXX.orgXXX&quot;.replace(/XXX/g,&apos;&apos;);
    $(&apos;#email1&apos;).html(&apos;&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:&apos; + email1 + &apos;&quot;&gt;&apos; + email1 +&apos;&lt;/a&gt;&apos;);
    $(&apos;#email2&apos;).html(&apos;&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:&apos; + email2 + &apos;&quot;&gt;&apos; + email2 +&apos;&lt;/a&gt;&apos;);
&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;!--
Jason Kridner is a 27 year veteran of Texas Instruments working in embedded systems. Jason&apos;s experience includes production evaluation and monitoring, digital silicon development and prototyping, audio and video signal processing, software for file storage and standards-based peripheral communications, and device and data security solutions. Jason&apos;s roles span individual contribution, team leadership and organization-wide technologist. Jason was instrumental in bringing open source software methodologies into multiple teams at Texas Instruments.

Jason serves as President on the board of the BeagleBoard.org® Foundation, a US-based 501c3 non-profit existing to provide education in and collaboration around the design and use of open-source software and hardware in embedded computing. Jason leads the development of and maintains open-source development tools such as BeagleBoard®, -xM, -X15, PocketBeagle®, BeagleBone®, Black, Blue and the upcoming BeagleBone® AI.

Jason also serves on the board of the Open Source Hardware Association, a US-based 501c3 non-profit which aims to foster technological knowledge and encourage research that is accessible, collaborative and respects user freedom.

Jason has been a featured keynote speaker and instructor at many industry and educational events including Maker Faires, American Society of Engineering Education Conferences, Embedded Linux Conferences, Collaboration Summit, Android Builders, OSCON, CES and others.
--&gt;</body>
    <pseudoparent idref="199" prototyperef="Page"/>
    <pvcount type="float">0.0</pvcount>
    <http_referer>https://beagleboard.org/about/jkridner/tide</http_referer>
    <tk_ai>/+sVSxw43ZTLicf5ZGKorU0P</tk_ai>
    <doxygen_width>300</doxygen_width>
    <http_host>127.0.0.1:8080</http_host>
    <lang>en-us</lang>
    <user>default</user>
  </hopobject>
</xmlroot>
